We're back, Ben.
Hey, everybody.
So day two, Galaxy livestream.
We'll do a quick round of intros just for everyone
that's new to the chat.
I'm Matt, working developer experience at SpaceX.
I'm Roshan, work on product at SpaceX AI.
Hello, I'm Potato, also known as Lauren.
I work on Potato things.
No, I work on Grok Bot at SpaceX AI.
And for those of you that are just joining us yesterday,
we started building our business.
And it was really about getting our accounts set up,
brainstorming, aligning on an idea.
We decided that we would try to build
an experiential pop-up business.
And so we spent most of the day going through that vision,
getting things configured, putting out
some prototypes and some demos.
And then I think the team might have changed our minds
overnight.
Yeah, I feel like we bit off more than we
can chew with the pop-up idea.
We had a couple of guests that I
feel like they gave us really good advice on how difficult
it is to, SF has a lot of restrictions and licensing.
And I don't know, I think we felt
like it wasn't going to be very entertaining to show on stream,
all that kind of work.
Yeah, well, that and we put some agents on this overnight.
We got some good advice and let our agents cook a little bit.
And I think we came back with a bunch of feedback
that, well, maybe this isn't something we could totally
and completely do in two days.
And for everyone who's been watching,
we think it'd be a lot more fun if you all could join in
fun and maybe we could build something that we could all
use together.
The agents told us to pivot.
Yeah, pivoting.
And I think part of building a business
is kind of like picking something
you're really passionate about and that you've done before.
Yeah, maybe you guys want to start talking about what
we're thinking.
Yeah, so we're excited about this new idea
where we're going to think about how we can create a way
for everyone who's watching, everyone who's here in person
as well to create their own RockBot templates
and then be able to do some fun things with those RockBot
templates.
And well, the most fun thing we could think of
is making a gaming company.
And so we're going to try building a game or a gaming
business here as our new business with maybe a game
that we start out where we all get to play with our RockBots
together and starting out with that as our first vision.
And so what we thought we'd do to kind of kick off
this morning, I think we have maybe half an hour,
20 minutes or so, is kind of walk you through and do
some live whiteboarding for how we might be able to bring
this vision together.
And then I think Warren is going
to walk us through a little bit of the MVP plan.
So we'll start out with that and then kick over to some talks
and then keep building and have that be our focus today.
Is that sound good?
Yeah, let's do it.
Cool.
Can we get my screen up on the stream?
So we did some thinking about what we should build.
And well, here's a blank whiteboard.
Zoom in.
I'll zoom in.
Way too small.
So what we initially thought about
was that it'd be really cool to find a way to bring RockBot
templates into the fold.
And Lauren, do you want to explain what RockBot templates are?
Yeah, so RockBot templates are a way
to share the bots that you've created with the world.
And we have lots of great examples
on the bot marketplace that you can find in the RockBot
application.
But essentially, yeah, it's a way
to share your bot with somebody else.
And it includes their skills, their routines,
selective memories that are a little bit more engineering
so you don't leak anything.
But yeah, it's a great way to share your expertise.
If you spend some time creating a really smart bot for doing PM
things, you can share that and somebody else can benefit.
Totally.
And so the idea here is that maybe we
could take those RockBot templates
and bring them to bear in a really fun way
to encourage you all to create some bots
that you're really excited about.
Maybe be able to share those with others
in the community a little bit.
But our idea is more about thinking
about how we could bring those bot templates to life
a little bit.
And so what we're thinking of doing
is actually putting together a little game where
you can take your bots and have them face off
against each other.
And I think it'd be fun.
So we're going to draw a little bit of an example of what
we're thinking about.
And what we're thinking about initially
is that we'd start out with a RockBot template.
So we get Roshan's screen.
Oh, yeah, let's do that.
Yeah, there you go.
So you basically, you can create a RockBot template
today by just creating a bot in RockBot
and then saving it as a template.
And then having something we do with that template where we
basically make it so you can convert this
into a character in a game and then compete head
to head against other people who've also uploaded and created
their own characters.
And this is our core idea, is that really we
think we can make something really simple where everyone
can engage together, get a chance to play together,
and really keep it fun and lightweight
and iterate on this idea as we go.
And so our initial plan here is that we
want to start by making it really easy to take a RockBot
template and convert it into a character.
And what better way to do that, we thought,
than being able to build a team of bots?
And so we're going to think of something
like this, where perhaps you can go in and create a bot.
Maybe we'll give some stats to these bots.
So I was thinking something like stat A,
maybe we could take some inspiration from some
of our favorite games, like Prisma, Dex, Intelligence.
Maybe do those three stats for each bot.
And then I've always been a big fan of abilities in games too.
And so maybe we also give each of these bots an ability.
And that ability lets them use one of these stats.
So maybe you could have a bot that has a charisma ability,
or a Dex ability, or maybe an int ability.
Yeah, I think we'd want to give the ability a cool meme
as well.
Because I feel like if we just show charisma ability,
that feels a little bit too techie, maybe.
Yeah, that's a good point.
It'd be interesting.
For example, one of my favorite bots, Shameless Plug,
is Dr. Eggbot.
And I would imagine Dr. Eggbot has a cool skill,
like Unslop, or one of the skills I made.
Like, it kind of adds a bit of flavor.
But under the hood, maybe it uses one of those stats
to do something that could be interesting.
Yeah, I like that.
And so maybe it's like you start a bot
and you kind of draft your team around it.
So you upload a template.
We can help you generate a character.
Maybe we add some randomness to it.
So every character looks a little bit different.
Kind of gives you a little avatar in the game.
I think it could be fun.
So you get some visuals there.
And then maybe just to start off and keep this simple,
we have your main bot, and then a few additional bots
that are drafted into your team.
So you get this team of three bots
that you're starting out with.
Does that seem like it could work?
Yeah, so I guess let's imagine what it would look like.
So I sign up.
I add Dr. Eggbot to my team.
And then I have, I don't know, Tragbot and what's
another bot that you know.
We have our Outbound Prospecting bot.
Outbound Prospecting bot.
Kind of a long term, long name.
Outbound bot.
And so I have this team of bots.
And I guess, how do we determine the stats
that they get?
Yeah, I think we should think through that.
We could probably do some.
We probably want it to be deterministic, right?
So when you upload a bot into, and generate a character
from the bot, you basically get the same stats every time.
And so you can mint a bot into a character.
And that kind of persists.
Oh, that's interesting.
Yeah, so maybe we come up with some ways
that we give a range for these stats.
One thing that I've seen work really well in games
like this is where you have a total stat pool.
So maybe we start with a total stat pool of 100 max.
And then we basically split this into those three stats.
We could maybe actually put an LLM against the description
of the bot.
So if you describe a bot as being really charismatic,
or being really social, and maybe its job
is to coordinate people.
That maybe gets a higher charisma bonus,
or something like that.
Or maybe a bot that's really good at connecting
to a bunch of different services,
gets a high dexterity stat.
Because it's kind of moving all around.
But it's still fixed, right?
So it would be all the three stats
would still total up to 100.
Yeah, I like that.
So maybe for an example, we'd have something like this.
70, 30 is 100.
OK, I guess we'll need a minimum.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Because it'd be weird to have a zero stat.
Maybe we do 10 as the minimum?
Sure.
Or one.
Or why not one?
Yeah, let's just go all the way to the bot.
One and then max is 98.
Yeah, one and max 98.
98, two, two, one, one.
Good point.
And it could be just random, I guess.
One more thought I have that could be really interesting.
Because it'd be really fun if there was a way for when
you create a bot for that to be almost like.
Because if you play games like Diablo or those action RPG
games, the items that you pick up have, I think, rarity.
That could be really interesting here.
Because I'm imagining, wouldn't it
be so cool if Dr. Eggbot was a legendary bot?
Come on, it has to be legendary.
It has to be legendary.
It has to be, right?
I kind of like that.
Yeah, so maybe we could have some randomizer
where we have a rarity modifier that
changes what this total stat pool could be.
So the base version is 100.
But then we could have rarity that
boosts the total stat count.
So for total stat points, maybe we
could come up with a base, rare, ultra, legendary,
or something like that.
And kind of having that be the way we split this up.
And maybe we do something like 100 points for base.
We can come up with the exact numbers.
Yeah, I like that.
I guess another question I have is,
well, we're pivoting to doing a game studio.
And I guess if we're keeping it somewhat realistic,
the game needs to maybe make some money.
So I'm kind of curious.
For games, I think a lot of gamers
do not like pay-to-win type mechanics.
So I'm kind of curious if you have any ideas on how do we
monetize in a way that doesn't make this just
pay-to-win game?
I definitely agree with not doing pay-to-win.
I feel like that's, as a person who loves to play games,
that's the worst thing in the world,
where it feels like a lot of those mechanics
where you have to come back and try for the next day
or get your limited number of turns.
And so I think we should make this a little less power.
Maybe you're not paying for power,
but maybe you are paying for a lot of fun upgrades.
Because a lot of the virality of this
could be where you build your team,
and then you share your team on social,
or draft your team.
And maybe over time, we'll start out
with a basic version of this.
But you could imagine you could upgrade your bots
and maybe find upgrades over time.
And so maybe you could pay for cosmetics.
That could be kind of fun.
Or maybe being able to pay for potentially access
to different battlefields or arenas or something like that.
That could be interesting.
I'd pay $1 for a cool hat.
Yeah, I would totally pay $1 for a cool hat.
Or like my cool hat.
I'm the only one who had it.
That could be a fun way to use some other APIs, too.
Maybe using the Rock Imagine APIs
to build some really cool visuals
and making them almost unique items that are unique to you.
So I wonder if we should try to play with those ideas.
Cosmetics and unique items.
We should write some of these down.
So we have it for our whiteboard.
I guess I'm also imagining the bots
are facing off each other.
And they're in some kind of arena or something.
Yeah, I like that.
Or some battleground.
I don't know.
Something like a stadium.
Exactly.
A stadium.
Yeah, a stadium school.
I guess you could tie it like what you have with sports.
You can have what do you call advertising on the...
So some type of songwriting in the stadium?
I mean, that's like the classic model, I guess.
I like that.
It doesn't really affect the gameplay.
But there's a lot of eyeballs on that space.
Yeah.
Because one thing I think could be interesting
is for the ability for someone to watch somebody else's game.
So let's say you and I get matched up.
And maybe there's a link or something that we can share.
And someone can watch the replay later.
So maybe there's something like that
where it helps with the monetization as well
or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, I like that.
We can figure that part out.
I think this part actually creates a really nice flywheel
where you have folks who are willing to put ads
into the game.
But it doesn't change the dynamics of the game.
But really because hopefully we can grow this really big
and get a bunch of eyeballs on it.
And that would be a great way to create a flywheel
for the different stadiums or whatever we decide to call them
and then have those be fed back in.
So I like that a lot.
I feel like we have a few ideas here.
And like any good company, we should prototype some of them.
And maybe one of the things that I've noticed too about,
especially starting 0 to 1, is you really just
care about growth and getting users as soon as possible.
And then we can layer in the monetization as we go
and as we get a feel for how the product comes together.
And so I think the last thing we should figure out
is what's the core mechanic of the game?
So we've talked a little bit about these bots.
And they have stats.
And so they have these abilities that maybe they can use.
We'll give them cool names as we talked about.
But one of the ideas that we were kicking around
is maybe we could have these bots face off in some way.
So you can assemble your team and pit it
against another team and pit some of these abilities
against each other.
What do you guys think about that?
Let's do it.
That sounds fun.
Yeah.
So I just started drawing this out here as an example of that.
And obviously we have some sample stats here.
Maybe we could mix some of these around
where you had a bot who had a charisma ability.
And it faces off a bot that has an intelligence ability.
And these stats come to bear for how those things go head
to head against each other.
And I think they're pretty simple versions of the game.
But basically we would start out
with facing off stats once against each other.
And we can add some cool dynamics
for how we modify the stats or give you maybe
how these abilities we could use an LAM to help generate
what they are.
So maybe you get a special boost that you roll when you first
create your bot.
And then every one of these head to head things
feels like it's a bit of a different one.
And then you go watch the replay.
And I feel like there's something here.
So maybe we start out with something really simple
where you have your team of bots and you set your lineup.
And then we create some lightweight matchmaking
where you get paired against another team of bots.
They set their lineup ahead of time.
Or maybe as part of the matchmaking flow.
And they just face off against each other
with some of these stats.
So it sounds like what we're talking about is
if you have a business, you're selling a product or a service
or maybe a good.
And the product here is a game that you can interact with.
And so the business is a game studio
that creates the product, a game.
And then all of the other aspects of building a business
are pretty much the same.
So it's like, OK, distribution.
How do we get people to discover this game?
Well, I guess we're on a live stream.
So that's pretty good.
But then also we could have SEO and AU.
So maybe that's something I could start working on.
We need a nice landing page.
We need a way for people to find us.
We might think about running some ads.
We might have a special guest joining us
after the next break that could help us out
with some of that stuff.
Exciting.
I wonder who that could be.
We were like, maybe we hire a fourth teammate.
I don't know.
Anything's on the table, right?
We might run some ads.
Did we get seed funding?
Can we get an intern?
I mean, the question is, how do you get somebody
without seed funding?
And maybe we'll answer that question later.
So yeah, I think that's a good start of distribution.
And then we have maybe the other aspects, which
are customer service.
How do people reach out and learn more?
Maybe there's an email.
Maybe there's a phone number even that you could call.
Or we source the chat comments.
Maybe our way of interacting with the community
is just directly through X. We pull in the chat API
or something.
That's super cool.
Yeah, and we can just hear what people are saying in chat.
Yeah, I like that.
There's probably also going to be some things here
on customer support and handle questions.
All the things the classical business would need,
to your point of how do we put together
the operations of the business.
And that can be a really fun way to bring a bunch of rock
bots to bear, right?
Just like how are our rock bots helping us
run the whole business, too?
So we get a little bit of that angle.
I think that'd be really cool.
Sweet.
OK, so I think we have a bunch of buckets here.
We have some monetization stuff.
We have some thoughts on features.
We have some thoughts on product needs.
And then I wanted to just redraw down here
how we're thinking about the core flow.
So I think for the MVP, our core flow
could just be you take your rock bot template,
you get to draft your team, you set your lineup,
and then you get to compete against another lineup.
And we'll have to do some algorithm work,
I think, which will be really fun to figure out how we
actually handle the core game loop
and ensure that these are balanced matches
and that folks are able to feel like they're winning,
creating some incentives to come back.
But I think if we start with this,
we could really layer on a bunch of complexity to it.
You could imagine we have stat upgrades,
we change the abilities.
We could potentially even create different arenas
that folks are competing in and then
change the properties of those over time.
And I feel like we have a lot of room
we could play with on this.
And one thing that I've always felt with ideas like this
is that it's really great to have a tight version that we
can start with and have that be what we build with upfront
and then evolve that and give us plenty of room to evolve.
And so this feels like one where we just
have so much potential room for creativity.
It's what I'm getting.
Maybe I'm just getting really excited about the idea,
but I feel like we have a lot we could work with here.
I think so.
I think there will be a lot of chances
to do some cool engineering things too.
And Dr. Eggbot, for example, brings in one of my plugins,
PSAC, got to shamelessly plug it again.
I think it'd be kind of cool to show off
some of the engineering workflows
that I use all the time to work on projects and apply it
here.
But I do think there's a lot of, this idea
has a lot of room for us to show off
all the aspects of creating a product and the business
and operations that go around it.
Because you could easily substitute this for an app.
It's like a similar process.
Or if you had a physical business,
all of the digital operations that go on
around that physical business.
Exactly.
Yeah, cool.
Lauren, do you want to take us through some of the thoughts
on how we could MVP this?
Because I feel like maybe.
Yes, actually.
I was typing while you were talking.
Prompting while we were talking.
And I have a rough plan if we look at my screen.
Cool.
So we'll get Lauren's screen up.
Yeah, while we wait, I guess I'll just talk through it.
So we did some discussion earlier,
so I had some idea of what the plan would be.
And I used P-stack again to do my.
So P-stack, if you're not aware, is my plug-in
that has a bunch of my skills that I've developed
for doing engineering work.
And one of the things that P-stack includes
is a planning playbook.
So it's a bit long.
I'm not going to go through the whole thing.
But you can see that it's pretty detailed.
It has checklists on things.
How to verify the application.
It's got some pseudo code in there for the types.
Because I think a part of how I like to work
is thinking a lot about data structures and the types
and function signatures.
So all of that is over here.
I don't want to cut you off, Lauren.
But I think we actually have our first talk going live
on sales and engineering right now.
So we're going to cut over to the main stage.
And we'll jump back into this.
Yeah, we'll be right back.
Everybody, is my mic on?
Cool.
Awesome.
Welcome to day two of Grok Bot Galaxy.
I'm super excited to be here.
My name is Amrita.
I am a field engineer here at Cursor.
And we have a really great suite of workshops for today.
We're starting off with Grok Bot for Sales Engineers.
And then we'll have Grok Bot for Sales later today,
Grok Bot for SDRs.
We have one specific for customer support.
And then throughout all of this, we'll
be following along with Matt, Lauren, and Roshan
on how their company is going.
So super exciting day.
Thank you all for tuning in.
And yeah, let's get started.
All right, so today's session is Grok Bot for Sales Engineers.
What I'm planning on doing with today's session
is kind of similar to the other ones.
I'm showing three bots.
These are three bots that I actually use on a day-to-day.
Two of them will be in a demo project.
So you'll see kind of how it works in sort of a sandbox
scenario.
And then one of them I'll show I actually use every day.
So I'm going to do a quick overview of Grok Bot
for curating particular customer kind of case study slides
when I need to do external facing calls.
I'll do a quick overview of Grok Bot for folks who maybe this
is the first time tuning in or tuning into the Grok Bot
Galaxy event.
So we'll do a quick overview about Grok Bot.
I'll talk a little bit about why we created it,
what makes it different from some of the other products
out there.
And then we'll get into the use cases
that I'll talk about and then a demo.
So I'm going to go ahead and save them for the last 15 minutes
or so.
And we'll have some build time for folks in person.
So I'm happy to come around and see how you all
are using Grok Bot.
There are little coasters, I think,
at your table that show you different use cases of how
we use Grok Bot.
So if you want to scan the back,
there's a QR code that kind of shows you
a template of a Grok Bot you might be interested in.
OK.
We showed this slide yesterday.
But I want to kind of hone in on exactly what this means
where we're moving towards a world that's
task-based and one-off kind of request to an AI tool,
and more so a team of bots kind of at your service
working together on a task.
So we're really going from a chat bot type world
to more like a team of colleagues.
And what's nice about this is when I think about Grok Bot,
I think about a tool that actually gives me
finished work.
And that's the beauty of it is it's not
meant to be something that you have to constantly babysit
or something that is always just at your computer
that you always have to keep your laptop open for.
It's literally meant to be like a teammate where it can work
maybe while you're on vacation.
You're away.
It can work while you're asleep.
It can work because you can talk to it on your phone
like you would a normal colleague.
And so we're going towards a world
where that's going to be happening all the time
for all different types of domains.
So whether you're in sales, you're in product,
you're in engineering, you're going
to have a staff or a team of bots at your service that
can help you basically accomplish work that maybe you
didn't have time for before, maybe you're not
looking forward to.
But you're also having them ready to go
with the context and memory that you're providing them.
OK, so for folks who haven't seen Grok Bot before,
first I recommend downloading it.
It's on Android, iOS, and the Mac.
So if you haven't downloaded it yet, please do.
And it's the best way to see it and try it out
for yourself.
There's a couple main things to highlight here.
The first is the interface itself.
So if you've used iMessage or maybe any form of a chat
or texting interface, you'll see that it looks pretty similar.
On the left is where all your bots live.
And as you can see, you can message them like teammates.
So you can say good morning to your bots, you can thank them.
You can basically go back and forth with them
because they have this long-lived memory
that it's able to learn from what you've said before.
If maybe you've told it that you
didn't like how it did something a particular way,
it keeps that in its memory, and it's
able to do better the next time around.
And we'll see an example of that actually in this demo.
You will also see that bots have their own computers.
And so this is kind of what I mean where bots are like
colleagues, is no longer do you have to maybe connect each bot
to every single service or provider
that you want to have access to.
Your bot can do a lot of that for you.
An example that we did yesterday was a bot making its own Google
form.
An example that I've heard from the crowd
is a bot logging into MongoDB and kind of analyzing
your database and making sure that everything
is up to snuff.
And then I think another cool thing about computer use
is you can monitor what it's doing in the computer itself.
So if, for example, I want to take over its computer,
I totally can.
I can also control from an enterprise level
what it has access to in that computer.
So if for some reason I don't want
it to access a particular website
or I don't want it to download a particular thing,
I can always keep that in my admin controls
so that you don't want the bot making decisions
that you wouldn't take yourself.
And then automations and routines.
That's a huge one.
And I think it's something that people constantly
look for with AI tools is, hey, how can I automate
or have a repetitive task be done without me
having to think about it?
A common one that I have actually
is I subscribe to a bunch of different AI newsletters
and podcasts.
And I've started not to keep track of all of them.
And so every morning, I'll have bot actually
look through my email, find the newsletters that
are relevant to me, and then just create them
in a daily digest and summarize them in Slack.
And then it just messages me every morning saying, hey,
here's what you missed from these podcasts, these newsletters.
And it helps me keep up to date.
But it's also something that I no longer have to think about.
Similarly, there's a very common morning brief, morning
digest for your work if there's Slack messages
that you've missed overnight.
I do like to highlight that for distributed teams,
GrokBot is really a game changer
because you can go from having to wait on work being
done from other teammates or other tools
to just having something that's really always on and always
at your service.
And so that's kind of the beauty of GrokBot
is that it's really great for distributed teams.
But also, it's a multiplier.
It's a force multiplier for you wherever you are.
And then the last thing is sharing your bots with others.
So you see here on these kind of little coasters
that we have QR codes.
That's for public bots that are
available on the marketplace.
If you want to share bots with your team at work,
you can do that as well.
For example, we have bots that are specific to the sales
team that we all share.
There's bots on the engineering team
that they share with us as well.
And so bots are meant to be multiplayer.
They're meant to be used and shared.
And also creates a sense of consistency across the company.
You want to make sure that, let's say, the sales bot is not
using different resources that maybe someone else's sales
bot is.
So having that consistency of bots is also very important.
OK, I touched a little bit on some of this,
like why GrokBot and what makes it different.
I think the main things to highlight here
is it's very easy to use.
I think a lot of tools, when you first spin it up,
you don't know where to start.
You don't know how to connect things.
GrokBot kind of learns all of that for you.
You'll see it actually when we work with a bot from scratch
today.
It will basically ask me, hey, what am I being used for,
and how can I best help you?
And we'll also do something cool.
We'll actually ask one of the GrokBots today
to spin up its own team of bots.
I'm basically going to ask it, hey, what bots do you
think would be helpful for you?
If I had to ask you to hire your own team,
what would be useful for you?
And a bot can actually make that decision.
And so bots spinning up other bots
or bots working with their other teammates
is what really makes GrokBot this multiplayer force
multiplier tool.
And then, as I mentioned, computer use and the fact
that it can do an entire task end to end.
One thing that I really like about GrokBot
is if I give it a task, and again, it's in the cloud,
so it's always on, I can come back and trust
that the task will be done.
It's not going to sit waiting for my approval.
It's not going to go back and forth
and like, should I do this decision?
Should I not?
It will finish the task, and then I
can tweak it or steer it however I want.
But the goal is that you're not just sitting and waiting
for it to do something.
You're actually coming back to finished work, which really,
really saves a lot of time.
Cool.
So as I mentioned, these are some sales engineer use cases
that I have seen at SpaceX, and also three of them,
actually, I'll be showing today.
And so the engineer technical resource,
David Gann will probably go more into detail about this
and his customer support session.
So if you're interested in that, definitely take a look.
But what's nice about this is we get a lot of customer
questions about security.
We get questions about how GrokBot was built,
how is memory being stored, what type of computer
is it using as a Linux VM.
All of these technical questions, some of them
are in our docs, but some of them
also are just in the implementation of GrokBot.
It's in the repository.
And so what I do with the sales engineer
is I actually have a expert.
I call him Sherlock.
And what he does is he basically has access to a repository.
So he has access to the GrokBot repository.
And so if a customer asked me a question, I can go ask Sherlock,
hey, a customer is curious, do we support X, Y, and Z?
Sherlock comes back.
But what's nice about this is I've actually
steered Sherlock to make sure that he doesn't ever
release any IP, that he phrases things in an easy understand
way, if I need to communicate this to maybe
someone more high level, someone that's not down in the weeds.
And so that's kind of the beauty of this particular GrokBot
is that it's meant to understand things technically,
but then phrase them back to me as to how I would tell
a customer.
And then competitive Intel.
This is a really fun one.
Competitive Intel is basically a bot that I created.
I named it Serena Williams because I'm a big tennis fan.
And she's also very famous for studying her competitors
and watching how they play.
But what Serena does is she actually
uses competitor products in her own computer
and then tells me, hey, by the way, this competitor is using
or is doing something different than how your product is.
Is that something that you want to put on your roadmap
or something that you'd want to change?
And we'll see an example of that today, actually,
of Serena actually going in trying out a competitor
product, giving me feedback on what's
different between my product and theirs,
and then maybe suggesting what actions I can take later.
Echo is something that I think Krista and Mark
will show in a later session.
It's basically live curating a deck during a customer call.
Really neat tool.
I don't use it often, but what I usually do
is before a customer call, I'll give it context.
I'll give it notes.
And then what I'll do is I have this giant master
deck of slides of anything from case studies
that we've done with customers to benchmarks, everything
in one master deck.
And based on the notes that I've
given it of what the customer is interested in,
it'll curate those slides and basically highlight
what's important in what the customer wants.
And then now I have a specific deck catered to that customer
that I can show later.
So we'll show an example of this today.
But in the build session, if you all
are curious about this type of bot,
I'm happy to build it out with you.
OK, cool.
Awesome.
So let's get started with the demo then.
We have three bots today.
We have Mimi.
She's going to be the slide customer proof point
researcher.
Mimi mentioned is my technical expert.
And then Serena Williams is my competitive Intel one.
And that will be fun to see.
So let's see how they do.
All right.
So the first thing I'm going to do
is I'm going to show you my bots.
They are right here.
I'm going to start with Mimi.
So what's nice about Mimi, you'll
see that I had a conversation with her over the past,
I think, couple days.
And the goal of Mimi, if I actually click on her here,
let me actually click into her description.
Basically, what Mimi does is she has access to a slide deck.
So you can see it here.
She has access to the slide deck once the computer connects.
And what she's able to do is she's
able to curate the deck and create customer case
studies for me.
So I have a bunch of slides about SpaceX.
And this is what I would present to a customer.
But what's nice about my case studies
is they all look the same.
So I have one, for example, for Starlink
and how they use SpaceX.
And this is based on a public blog post about how
Starlink uses the API.
And they all look the same.
They all have the same template, which
is problem, solution, impact, and then a quote
from the blog post.
And often what I do is let's say
I'm meeting with a hardware customer.
And I need to present to them an example of how
one of our existing hardware customers has used Cursor
has used SpaceX.
I basically give Mimi a blog post or maybe even
notes from a previous conversation with a customer.
And all I do is I basically tell her
to create a slide like this.
So we're going to do a live example of that.
You'll see that she did one for Jellyfish recently.
Jellyfish just did a blog post about how they use
Cursor for code review.
And so all I did was I say, hey, we actually go up here.
I said, I just want you to do your job for Jellyfish.
And here is the blog post.
And boom.
She went through.
She said, OK, here's what I'm going to do for Jellyfish
based on reading this blog post.
This is the problem.
This is the solution.
Impact, quote.
And then the nice thing about Mimi
is, again, because she has accessed her own computer,
she can create these slides for me and then take screenshots.
So she's like, OK, this is the Jellyfish logo.
She was able to actually go to the Jellyfish brand page,
get the right logo, and then put that on the slide.
And then this is the problem, solution, impact, and quote.
And so let's do an example of this live
and see how Mimi does.
So what I'm going to do, actually,
I'm going to go back to the browser here.
And I'm going to take this blog post.
I thought it was very apt because it's
a Salesforce blog post about how they use Cursor
to cut legacy code coverage time by 85%.
I'm just going to take this guy.
And I'm going to go to Mimi.
And I'm going to say, can you create another one
of these slides for Salesforce for me?
And I'll just link the blog post here.
And actually, I'll specifically just say blog post here,
so she knows.
And so what she'll do, and we'll come back
to this at the end of the session to see how she does,
is she'll be able to take this, create a slide from it,
and then actually insert that slide into the slide deck
here.
So again, what I'm opening here is Mimi's computer.
As I mentioned, I can take control of it.
I can click around in it.
But what you'll actually see, which is very cool,
is Mimi will have her own cursor in here.
So Mimi will start editing the slide.
She'll give me an update on when it's ready and how it's doing.
And then once she's done, she'll go ahead and present it back
to me, just like she did with Jellyfish.
So I'll let Mimi go here.
I just want to make sure that she can access this.
But while she's working, I'm actually
going to go to the other two bots, so Sherlock
and Serena Williams.
So I'm just going to switch my account here,
so you all can see the other two bots.
Here we go.
So RockBot versus engineers, these are the two bots.
I have something very similar to Serena in my other account
that specifically looks for RockBot competitors
and what they do differently.
But for today, I'm actually going to work in a booking app
that we at SpaceX just created as a demo project.
So the app that we actually have
is something called Flylo.
Think about it as a very simple flight booking app.
So basically, what we did is we've
created this entire company called Flylo.
They're meant to book flights for anybody.
You can upgrade your seat.
You can change your flight whenever you want.
Very similar to Expedia or Google Flights,
any other flight booking app that you see.
What's nice about this is we have
created a whole suite of engineering products
that power Flylo.
So there's a front end, there's a back end,
there's a web app, there's an internal app for the crew to use.
And what's nice is my RockBot, Sherlock Bot,
has access to all of these things.
So if I actually go back to Sherlock here,
you can see I gave him a description.
I said, you're a technical expert on Flylo,
and you support the website FlyloAir.com.
I gave him access to the particular repos,
so the booking back end, the booking front end.
And then I also say, if there's a customer issue,
I want you to be able to investigate and then
communicate what could be wrong to a customer.
So I worked with Sherlock a little bit yesterday.
I was just curious.
I was wondering, hey, how do we support a race condition
for maybe someone trying to book two flights at the same time,
or they're trying to book the same seat at the same time?
And so what you'll see is that Sherlock actually
uses cursor cloud agents under the hood, which
is what makes it really easy and what makes it
able for me to close my laptop,
is that Sherlock is basically able to say, OK,
I'm going to dig into how booking handles two people
grabbing the same flight at once.
You'll notice that it says here, all right,
Flylo doesn't let two different customers confirm
the same last cabin.
The protection is in Postgres, which is good to know.
And then it covers two different use cases, right?
A last remaining ticket, or if someone
is booking the same actual seat, what
do you do in those scenarios?
And then what's nice about this,
and this is what I would recommend for anyone working
in a customer facing or just support role, where
you have to respond back about how things work,
is this is what you should tell a customer,
is that we hold the last remaining cabin space when
you start checkout for 10 minutes.
And if someone else started first,
you'll get a compliment trying to book.
And so this is kind of what maybe I would even tell it.
I can say, all right, draft this and draft it in an email
and send it to this customer.
Or I can even say, OK, this looks great.
Can you actually send it for me myself?
And then I can give it a particular approval
to send an email or a Slack for me.
So this is the great thing about Sherlock
is that it's able to be a technical expert
and answer questions for me if I'm ever
confused about how something was implemented
inside of my product.
Now let's go to Serena.
So Serena, as I mentioned, is a competitive Intel bot.
And so what she's going to do is she's
going to use her own computer to test out competitor products,
see how they compare it to Flylo.
So I'm assuming she'll probably text out products like Expedia,
maybe Skyscanner, Google Flights, and then also
check and talk to Sherlock and see, hey, do we implement,
for example, this whole race condition thing?
Does Expedia implement that?
Or is this something specific to just how we do it?
Does Expedia do it better?
Do they talk about it in their technical blogs?
Something that I do whenever I'm kind of researching competitors
and want to try out what other products are doing
is I always read their change log, their feature releases,
their blogs.
Because it's kind of a way for me to see, OK,
what are they doing differently or how are they
implementing things differently?
And Serena can kind of do all of that for you.
In fact, you can even set up a routine here and say,
hey, Serena, every week maybe,
can you summarize what has happened recently
with the Expedia technical blog or with the Skyscanner
technical blog?
And let me know if they've shipped anything recently
that I should be aware of.
A very common, I think, tool in travel apps and websites
right now is like an AI travel agent.
So what we'll do actually is we'll talk to Serena and see,
hey, are you able to see that in some of these other products?
Are there products that are doing that right now?
And I'm actually going to have her talk to Sherlock
and see what would be the technical lift, actually,
of being able to build like an AI agent inside of Flylo.
So let's go ahead and get started here.
I'm actually just going to say, what are some competitor
products that you think are worth testing against Flylo?
And you'll see that what's nice about RockBot
is it thinks and it's able to kind of communicate
what it's saying if you ask it to.
But for the most part, it'll actually do a lot of its work
behind the scenes.
So I can always ask it sometimes, which is like,
what are you thinking or what's going on?
But sometimes what it does, and because it kind of operates
pretty fast, is it'll tell you exactly how it's
going to go about, for example, testing something
like this once it's done kind of percolating on this.
So as you can see, it's going to say, OK, I'm connecting.
I'm going to be able to find you some competitor products.
As you can see, it messaged Sherlock already.
So it said, hey, Sherlock, I'm doing some competitor product
testing against Flylo.
Quick baseline ask, what can the current Flylo booking code base
support today?
Do they support searching, fair selection, seats, bags,
any known gaps versus a typical booking flow
that I should weigh when I compare?
So again, I didn't really give Serena any context.
All I did was, if we go back to Serena,
all I did was give her a description,
and then she immediately was able to kind of understand
what she had to do.
But now she's going to give me some options here.
So I said, let's go with Southwestern Spirit.
Let's see how those booking experiences compare to Flylo.
And then as you can see, again, she
will work with Sherlock to kind of go back and forth.
So Sherlock is actually now going to say, all right,
Serena asked me for a Flylo booking flow baseline.
I'm going to pull what the code actually supports,
and then I'll reply back to her and let her know,
hey, we support these things, but maybe Southwest and Spirit
Airlines don't.
What I'll also do while Serena is working,
and this is a very cool part of RockBot,
is I can steer her in a particular direction.
So for example, if I want to say, I want her maybe not
to test just the booking flow.
I want her to test, like, what are the agenda capabilities that
are there in these flight booking apps right now?
I'm going to go ahead and just say, can you
see if there are any AI travel agent capabilities
in any of the competitor tools that we should be aware of?
And what you can also see here at the top right
is that Serena is actually doing the Southwest booking
flow on her own.
And so as I mentioned, a lot of times I don't get the time,
or I don't have the time, to be able to test out
booking or any sort of competitor products,
step by step, I don't get that developer experience.
And so what is nice is that I'm kind of outsourcing that
to Serena.
So she can tell me, hey, the Southwest booking experience
is actually great, and it's actually
a lot better than Flylo, and these are the ways
that Flylo can be better.
And I don't have to do this just for Southwest.
I can have Serena do this for a million different booking flow
websites.
And so if you're ever wondering, hey,
I don't have time to see what the competitors are
doing in my space or how they fare compared to my own product,
you should really spin up a competitive Intel product.
It's very powerful and also just really interesting
to see how these products do in comparison
to your own product here.
So we can see here, she's actually picking on dates
and actually trying to see how booking works in Southwest
versus Flylo.
What's nice about this as well is you can also
ask it to open up another tab and do the same thing in Spirit.
You can ask it to do it at the same thing in Expedia.
So if there's any particular things that you wanted to test,
you can actually explicitly say that inside of Serena Williams.
The bot.
OK, cool.
So as I said, I kind of steered her in a particular way.
Let's say I want to test something more than just
booking.
Let's say I also want to test the AI travel agent capabilities.
This basically allowed her to not abandon this per se,
but also just incorporate this as a part of what she's doing.
So as I mentioned, bots have memories and bots can learn.
But what's nice about that is they're also
able to remember if you've asked it multiple things at once.
I think sometimes what can be frustrating with other tools
is you ask it a question and then you're like,
actually, I want to do something else.
But the minute you ask it the second question,
it forgets exactly what the first question was.
And you can't really give it proper instructions
on how you want to incorporate both of those things.
Rockbot is actually able to really understand that.
So as you can see here, it did some initial discussions
into what the travel agent plays is for Flylo.
It tells me exactly what we offer.
And then it's also seeing where or what
I changed for Flylo here.
So she's able to understand my question immediately
and come back to me.
But at the same time, she's also still
doing the booking flow testing that I asked her to do earlier.
So it's a mix of both, which is really great.
And what makes it a fourth multiplier here
is that this bot is able to multitask and do
many things at once.
I'm going to check in on Sherlock here and see how he's doing.
Looks like he's looking, again, at our booking flow baseline
and what we're offering as our product.
You can see here that the cloud agents are
being launched in cursor.
So one is being launched in, I believe, the back end, one
in the front end.
And I can always open them and see exactly how they're
being launched, what they're doing.
This is kind of the integration between Rockbot and cursor,
is once we're able to get any technical information
from the repo itself, we immediately
can talk back to Serena and give her information
as to how we've implemented something.
And this is great, again, when you want to talk to customers,
because a very common question I get
is competitive differentiation.
What makes one product better than the other?
How do you guys implement something differently?
And this is where I actually work with these bots together
so that they can talk to each other,
understand what the competitive threats are,
and then see what we do in our repo to kind of make that
or assuage those worries.
All right, so I'll let these two guys run.
As you can see, still doing the Southwest booking here,
which is good.
I want it to be able to get that full experience.
Let's check back in with Mimi and see how she's doing.
So we go back to this account here, and I open up Mimi.
Oh, let's go ahead and just resend that.
And that way, she'll be able to get the information
from that blog post again.
Hopefully, she'll be able to see that.
What's nice about having bots that talk to each other,
I'm actually going to switch back to Sherlock and Serena.
There we go.
Is once they have a conversation,
you can use that conversation as a template
for how you want them to interact in the future.
So I showed this yesterday, but if folks are curious,
instead of kind of going in between both of these bots
and kind of seeing what they're messaging each other,
sometimes what I like to do is I put two bots in a group chat
and then get that visibility of how they message each other
in one place.
So I'll actually put Sherlock and Serena Williams in a chat.
Oh, sorry.
Looks like it put two different people.
One second.
We'll do another group chat here.
Let's do Sherlock and, ah, Sherlock and Serena Williams.
There we go.
Looks like it's automatically putting me
in another person in the chat.
So if I add Sherlock and Serena Williams here,
basically what you can do now, if we go back to that,
where do we go?
Sherlock and Serena.
The two.
Go back here.
There we go.
Now both of them are in this chat here.
And now I can say something like, what have you found
is the key differentiator in our competitors
that would be significantly low effort
to build in the product?
And what they can do is they can basically
have a conversation with each other,
both based on what they've learned already.
So Sherlock now knows kind of that Serena cares
about the booking flow.
Serena now knows that I care about agenda capabilities.
And they're able to use the context of what
I've given it already and be able to talk to each other
about all of these things in one place.
And so you'll see here that Sherlock and Serena Williams
are going to work together now to come back
to me with an updated kind of response or a solution
on what they think would make sense.
And what's nice about this is you can basically
take the context of both these agents together
and then create a PR or a product doc
that you can then send off to your technical team.
And so you'll see here in the marketplace
that we have a lot of different bots that are published
by our team members but also publicly.
But then we also have plug-ins or tools
that you can connect to that make it really easy to kind
of plug in whatever you found out from your bots
into some sort of paper trail.
And so maybe what I would do here is once Sherlock and Serena
have come up with the plan of,
let's say they want to build a travel agent, an AI travel
agent because Southwest doesn't have one
and Expedia doesn't have one.
That would be our biggest kind of moat.
What I can do is I can connect it immediately
to Google Docs.
I can connect it to Atlassian or Confluence.
If you guys use a tool, maybe you guys use Microsoft OneNote
or a tool that doesn't actually have a plug-in or an MCP,
you can just ask Sherlock or Serena to log into that tool
on their computer.
And so we covered this a little bit yesterday
but I want to hone in on how important it is
that a tool not having an MCP or an API is not a blocker
because the bots have access to their own computers,
they can log into whatever tools that they want
or that you want on the computer.
And that makes it a lot easier to integrate with tools
that are historically very hard to integrate with.
For example, we get a lot of users that use Power BI
and have had trouble using AI agentically with Power BI.
Bot can log into Power BI on its computer.
Similarly, I think the MongoDB example is also great
where I don't believe we have a MongoDB plugin
but that doesn't mean that you can't use MongoDB
and not even RockBot anymore.
So again, remember that if you bought or plug-in
doesn't exist inside of this marketplace.
Your bot can still use it because it has access to it on its computer.
I want to cover one last thing while I'm here, which is you can see that I have some private skills set up.
This was one that I created yesterday, which is actually showing a bot how to do a slide deck animation.
What's cool about this is you can teach it multiple different skills, and it can apply those skills
at the right time depending on when it should be used.
So we can actually teach Sherlock a task or teach Serena a task.
For example, you can see here that she's doing something with her computer, with Booking Southwest,
so I'll let her keep doing that.
But let's say I want to teach Sherlock something.
Let's say I want to teach it how to...
Let me think.
Maybe how to go and see for itself if there is a technical post released
in the GitHub change log for a competitor.
So what I can do is I can just take over Sherlock's screen,
and I would recommend everyone actually doing something like this during the build session with me.
It's one of the biggest lever ways to use RockBot is actually by teaching it something
via video recording.
And I'm just going to say teach a task, and I'm going to go open up Google.
You can see it's pretty fast, and I'm going to say something like Expedia technical blog post.
And then I'm just going to go ahead and click this guy.
I know, ironic.
And then we're going to scroll in here, and you can see, okay, they have a medium.
Cool.
And then they have a bunch of stuff.
This is about GraphQL.
Maybe I want to search and see is there anything AI related here, and then look into that.
Looks like nothing really...
Oh, maybe this one, Reimagining Platform Engineering for Adjunctic Future.
Scroll here, see exactly what they're doing and are building.
And then that's it.
I pause it, and I'm done.
And now what's nice about this is Sherlock will now have all the details about that skill or that
video.
What I can do is I can say, okay, now use that skill and apply it to other competitors.
So do the same thing for Southwest or for Spirit or for SkyScanner or for Google Flights.
And now it's going to be able to know how to scan technical blogs, look for AI related things.
You can see here it says, okay, the recording is finished, learning the tasks from it.
And then I can even highlight particular things from that skill or that video
and tell Grokbot to particularly pay attention to those.
So I can say something like, and I'll use voice mode actually for this, I'll say,
notice that I specifically looked for AI related blog posts in my competitor products.
And I wanted to make sure that we are staying on top of our AI tooling inside of our own
product.
So I'm going to try and apply this to as many competitors as possible.
As you can see, I did this skill inside of Sherlock.
I could have done it inside of Serena as well.
It's kind of up to you on where you think the skill will be leveraged most.
But as you can see here in the marketplace, the skills are basically being used by all
the bots at all times.
So it doesn't matter where you create the skill.
The skill will still be learned and used by the different bots here.
Cool.
Okay.
So we're going to go back and see how Serena is doing.
Actually, let's check on our group chat where I basically asked them to come together
as a team and figure out, okay, where can we actually make a change or a difference with
this product?
So you can see Sherlock was saying, okay, from the code base side of things,
looks like every competitor treats this as basic table stakes, which is for managing
booking on the back end for trips.
And so that's one easy way that we can fix things.
Also, the second is a flexible date calendar.
Looks like this is live.
The front end client already has it wired, but it never calls it.
This would be a classic differentiator for us and very easy to wire up.
And then Serena says, okay, round trip and bags look big.
They're not low effort here.
The bags are in a scoo.
I'm curious which of managed booking versus calendar felt most people when you were on
those tools.
So they're working together here.
They're kind of figuring out what exactly is the biggest lift here or what would
be the easiest thing to implement.
I want to point out something here, which is that Sherlock tags Serena Williams in this.
And this is a cool way for bots again to communicate with each other is if Sherlock
wanted exactly something specific from a bot, you can either do that yourself.
So for example, I can tag Serena myself and say, hey, Serena, I'm specifically talking to you.
But the bot can also do that on its own as well.
And that's a really cool way for bots to communicate and specifically get information
that they need from a bot with memory and context on that information.
Okay.
So we have these two bots.
I think I mentioned earlier that I wanted to do something different, which is I wanted
to ask the bots what bots would be helpful to them.
And I do this sometimes when I'm working and I have a team, but I want to see, okay,
what can I do to help this team and to make it operate faster or more efficiently
or with better memory and context?
So what I'll do here is I'll actually go, let's go to Sherlock.
Sure.
And I can say based on the work that you and Serena, I'll tag Serena here, are doing,
what bots would be helpful for you to continue doing great work,
specifically around competitive differentiation and sales engineering.
And I'll say, go ahead and spin up those bots for me.
So this is a little known fact, which is bots can spin up other bots.
You can ask a bot to say, for example, if you have a chief of staff bot,
which is I think one of our most common bots, you could say, hey,
I want you to spin up three bots that you think would be the most helpful for my day to day.
And usually what the chief of staff bot will do is they'll spin up like an inbox manager,
maybe a scheduler and maybe like a calendar manager or something like that.
But I'm actually very curious here to see what the bot thinks
it would be helpful in this scenario and how exactly it chooses those bots to spin up.
And this is also great if you're starting out with rock bot for the first time.
Let's say you're a sales engineer, you work at a particular company,
you have some very particular workflows and you do demos,
you do particular things that are very specific and are not one-to-one with what I showed.
Go ahead and ask rock bot to spin up some bots for you and say, hey,
I want to be able to create a demo for a POC that I have with my AE in a couple weeks.
It's for this particular customer.
Spin up three bots for me that you think would be useful
in order for me to accomplish this task.
Rock bot is here to help you.
It's not here to add extra work or to give you extra managerial responsibilities.
It's here to tackle problems together on the same page.
And so that's kind of why I like having it spin up its own bots,
is because it's able to do that without me kind of having
to think exactly what I want those bots to be doing.
So good kind of trick if you want to work on multiple things or whether that be
competitive differentiation, creating demos, working inside of Salesforce.
You can do all those things with these bots kind of here.
Okay. We have about eight or so minutes left.
I want to check back in with Mamie and see how she's doing.
I know there was a bit of an outage earlier today.
Okay, cool. Looks like she's working.
She says, already on Salesforce from your last message,
I'm checking whether the pair is in yet.
I'm still building the Salesforce pair.
I'll send both screenshots when it's in the deck.
It looks like she's having trouble logging in again.
Let's see if we can go back in and log in for her.
So again, this is an example of how you can take control of logging into...
Oh, look, that looks great.
You can take control of logging into a slide or doc or anything in Google Drive for you.
Looks like it actually created those two slides perfectly for me.
So the logo was a little small, but at least it got the right logo.
Then what it also did is it took that exact same blog post that I gave it
and created a slide for me.
So it said, here's the problem.
Legacy repos were far below the coverage mandate.
This is the solution.
This is the impact.
And this is a quote from the blog.
Easy, done within the last 10, 15 minutes or so.
And now I have a nice template of a slide that I can give.
Let's say if I'm speaking to ServiceNow or any other Salesforce competitor to be like,
hey, by the way, we've done Curser with Salesforce and they had a great use case with us.
So we can do this one more time if you guys want to see it again.
We can just keep Mimi in the loop.
We have a good use case with Grab.
Grab uses Cursor.
Grab, Cursor, Case Study.
Let's see.
Here we go.
Another blog post published by Grab.
I'm going to go ahead and do this one last one.
Go back to Mimi here and say, great work.
Can you do one for Grab?
And again, as I mentioned with the steering, I could have sent all of these to Mimi at once.
I could say, hey, do Salesforce, do Grab, do this other customer story that we have,
and then she can create all of these.
And then what I could do, which is kind of what I showed earlier with the Echo
Grokbot, is when I have my customer call or I have to present these, I can tell Mimi,
hey, hide the slides or hide the case studies that wouldn't be relevant for this customer.
Let's say the customer is Uber.
They don't maybe they care more about the Grab case study than they do about the Salesforce case
study, something similar to that.
And so I can kind of send all of these off.
Again, I can do these from my phone.
I don't even have to have my laptop open.
Mimi can work on all of these case studies and all of these slides for me.
She knows exactly how to do them now, given that I gave her the exact template,
which is logo and then problem solution impact and quote.
And then I can just feel free to use these slides whenever I want.
And that's actually how I make a lot of my slides with Grokbot.
Is I ask it to follow a template because I don't want it to come up with anything too
sloppy or too wordy.
I know exactly how I want my slide to be organized.
But then once I have the content for it, for example, this blog post,
Mimi, the Grokbot, was able to be smart enough to take the most important
parts of this blog post, organize them into the right places,
put them into a Google slide for me, and then now I'm able to go to my
customer ready and prepped.
So it's a really beautiful end-to-end flow, kind of bringing it back to what I said
earlier, which is finished work is the best part of Grokbot.
Is you are no longer spending time reading through this blog, figuring out
what the main points are, putting that into a slide, designing the slide,
making sure everything looks nice, getting the logo.
Grokbot did all of that within the last 10 to 15 minutes.
And it can do that for as many different customers as you want.
So as you can see, it says, all right, grab next.
I'm going to check that the Salesforce status works and pull that engineering post.
I'm actually going to say Salesforce looks great.
You can go ahead and start working on grab.
And hopefully, by the time Q&A is over today, we can see the grab slide as well
in addition to the Salesforce slide.
But this is what I want to highlight when it comes to what makes my job easier is a lot
of times I have to create slides for sometimes 15, 20 different customers in a week.
And having Mimi as my slide guru, but also my customer proof point reader.
Actually, sometimes what I'll do is I'll ask her to crawl the web and just see
all of these blog posts like the Salesforce one, the grab one.
These are not published by cursor.
These are published by these companies.
And sometimes we don't really get updates as to when these companies publish these posts.
So sometimes I'll ask Mimi, I'll be like, hey, have there been any customer posts
recently about cursor or SpaceX recently that would be good to highlight in my deck?
And then if so, go ahead and create a slide for it.
And that's something that can easily become a routine.
And so really, really great and easy.
And I just love slides that look nice.
Everyone, I think, has seen a lot of slides that they all look the same.
They all use that same purple color because they're all AI generated.
But not anymore.
Not when you give RockBot the template, the memory,
the context of how you want things to get done.
And then it's able to work off of that.
Okay.
I'll let Mimi work on Grab.
I'll come back to her during the Q&A.
I do want to quickly go back to Sherlock and Serena and see how both of them are doing.
As I mentioned, I taught Sherlock how to use that AI kind of blog skills
that it's able to find out what our competitors are doing.
But you can also see here that these are the three bots
that my Sherlock bots spun up.
So if you remember earlier, I said, hey, based on the work that you and Serena are doing,
what bots would be helpful for you to continue doing great work?
And you can see it spun up those three bots for me.
So let's see what these bots do.
Battle card blare.
Competitive differentiation and sales engineering battle cards.
So this is useful.
So in addition to maybe just having customer case study slides,
maybe what I can do with battle card blare is she can work with Mimi
and create slides against my competitors.
So not only do I have case studies on what customers like Cursor,
I can do have case studies on what customers are different from Cursor
and what makes them different.
So this looks great.
It says it combines Serena's hands-on competitor product findings
with Sherlock's fly-low code base, produce short SE ready battle cards,
competitor claims, fly-low reality, et cetera, et cetera.
Looks good.
I'll probably keep her around.
Demo Drake.
Let's see what you're up to.
Sales engineering demo and talk track specialist.
Build confident, no hallucination demo scripts and call talk tracks
that map customer pain to the fly-low live flow.
Ground every claim in Sherlock.
I love this.
I think this is important is that it knows that Sherlock is a technical expert.
And so it refers to that going forward.
And then when competitive contrast is needed,
you can pull it from Serena or from battle card blare.
So this is what I'm saying is that you have this team now
that it's all working together on the same outcome and the same projects.
And that makes things so much easier when you have,
for example, so many different things to manage or to keep track of,
you get all of that here.
And then the last one is AI radar.
Let's see what this one is doing.
Okay.
Track competitor AI tooling from public tech blogs.
So this honestly is maybe a little too similar to Serena.
Maybe I need him.
Maybe I don't.
Maybe I don't want him because he doesn't have a Q alliterative name
like the other ones.
But you can see here that this one prefers to specifically go through engineering posts.
It opens each blog, finds the AI-related post.
So it's actually using that skill that I taught Sherlock earlier.
And then again, uses Sherlock as a source of truth always.
And then hands any testing or user flows to Serena to do on her own computer.
So as I mentioned, you can always spin up your own bots
just by asking them to do it.
A very, I think, common joke at Cursor or at SpaceX is if someone asks us,
can we do this?
I'm like, ask RockBot.
And a lot of times that's how we work is there are times where RockBot will say no.
In fact, I think that's actually a big advantage of the Rock model
is it's one of the few models I feel that actually pushes back
and will say, I cannot do something.
It won't always kind of just be sycophantic and tell me yes or yeah, of course.
You're absolutely right.
And so sometimes what I'll do is I'll use these bots as my helpers,
basically, to figure out what else I can do next.
And that's the beauty of RockBot.
I'll bring Mimi back up, but I think we are about to wrap up pretty soon.
Yeah, we'll do some Q&A for folks in person.
But thank you so much for joining, and I hope this was useful, everybody.
My check, my check, my check.
Hello, thank you very much for this workshop.
Just one question about when the bot is navigating through another desktop.
Yeah.
Imagine you're logged into your Facebook account, for example.
Yep.
Can it be blocked because you see it's a just bot,
and how can we avoid on getting banned from this website?
Yeah, it's a good question.
So I think we all saw that I'm not a robot CAPTCHA check earlier.
That has come up a couple of times.
And depending on the website and how strong their services are for detecting bots,
sometimes I can't get past those.
And so it really depends sometimes on the website.
What I do recommend, and obviously,
RockBot can be used for personal use cases as well as work use cases,
is for enterprises, we recommend our admins kind of blocking sites like Facebook.
Obviously, you don't really need to be using Facebook and other tools during work.
And so you have that option in RockBot is to block access to particular websites
on the RockBot's computer.
But yeah, my honest answer is that there are some sites that will be able to tell,
some sites that won't.
These kind of sessions that we're doing are mainly meant for the enterprise.
So my general rule of thumb is,
if you shouldn't be accessing a website like Facebook,
we probably want to just block it on the RockBot's computer.
Hi.
I wonder, because the RockBot can use the computer use,
and you say it will eliminate or reduce the use of MCP or MCP required websites,
where should the next move go,
like creating more MCPs for bots to use or not creating any MCPs?
That's a really good question.
I do think, so I think personally that computer use is going to become
a very, very big part of the AI space generally.
I mean, we've seen it with other models outside of Rock.
And so I do think that going forward,
a big part of how your work is going to get done is via computer use.
Do I think that MCPs are going to go away?
Absolutely not.
I mean, the way I describe MCPs usually is like they're APIs for agents, right?
And so a lot of times when I use an MCP, it's faster than a computer use.
Like if I want to, for example, just immediately create a Google Doc,
sometimes I'll opt to use the Google Doc MCP as opposed to computer use,
because right now it's faster.
But I don't know.
I have a big feeling that computer use is going to get a lot faster,
especially if the models get a lot better.
So there could be a world where computer use becomes
the main way of agents interacting with tools than in MCPs.
I will say that for now, MCPs are probably a lot easier to monitor
and to add guardrails to, right?
Like for now, in cursor and SpaceX, you can white list and black list particular MCPs.
So that's probably an advantage for MCPs for now.
But I'm assuming we'll start to see more guardrails
being put for computer use in the future as well.
That's a great question.
If there are no questions, I would love if anyone wanted to chime in and tell
or share how they're using Grokbot.
It could be for sales engineering.
It could be for not sales engineering.
I think some of the best ways I learn about Grokbot
is just hearing from how other people use it.
So if anyone wants to share anything or if anyone wants to chime in
on things they think this demo could help with, that'd be great.
Yeah.
A question from X.
If Grok has its own server and access to internal systems,
how do you guarantee that it won't make changes to production systems?
Won't make changes to production systems?
Yeah, I think so.
There's a very equivalent question that I've gotten,
which is how do we know that bots don't download malicious software
and do anything dangerous?
I think the guardrails that we offer within Grokbot Enterprise
are kind of the solution for it right now.
We're still in the process of hardening those and making them as,
you know, just I want to say as tough as possible
so that people can still use computer use
without feeling that anything dangerous might happen.
I will say that, you know, with AI, there's so many different ways
that something potentially harmful could happen.
And we've had ways to mitigate that.
Skills has been a very common one,
which is you add rules or guardrails,
again, making sure that no one deploys to production
when they shouldn't.
Something that I didn't show earlier
that I'll actually show right now
is if you go into your settings,
auto review is basically a tool that we use at Grokbot
to make sure that things are reviewed ahead of time
before Grokbot makes changes.
If I actually turn this on,
you'll see that I can make particular changes to Grokbot
as to how and when it can do things.
And so what I'll actually say is when Grokbot wants
to deploy to production,
when Grokbot wants to use an internal system,
instead of doing allow automatically,
I should always do ask first.
And those are some ways that you can actually mitigate
those harmful, you know, situations from Grokbot.
Cool.
I think we're going to take some more questions
from remote folks.
So I'm happy to stay up here.
But if anyone else from SpaceX wants to come and join me up here,
that'd be great too.
One more question for Max.
What do you do if there's no MCP server
and the tool you want to use doesn't run on Linux?
Sorry, can you read that one?
I'm going to put this.
Yeah.
What do you do if there's no MCP server
and the tool you want to use does not run on Linux?
My honest answer is there's no way right now,
unfortunately.
I wish I had a better answer for that.
But the truth is our VMs are Linux.
And so you can only run tools that are Linux on these VMs.
And if they don't have MCP servers,
then you won't be able to connect with them via a plugin.
I would be curious maybe to figure out what that tool is.
And we can figure out from there.
But that is the honest answer there.
Check two.
I'm seeing a lot of questions about token usage.
Can you elaborate?
Yes.
So tokens in Grokbot are similar to tokens in any other AI tool.
You use tokens by talking to Grokbot.
Grokbot uses tokens by talking to you.
And then tokens are obviously being used
when it uses its own computer.
The goal, I think, working at SpaceX,
is that we are training models that will be specifically good for tools like this
to make it so that you get the most out of your tokens with Grokbot.
And so Grok46, which came out, I think, a couple weeks ago,
was meant to be a model, and it is a model,
that is inexpensive but also highly performant.
So it's able to power all of these things.
In fact, I believe the underlying model for Grokbot is Grok46.
And so you will see how powerful it is, and also how inexpensive it is.
I think I was actually looking at my usage recently
of how much money it took for me to create some of these slides.
Some days, I think it took me to create all of this entire slide deck.
I think it took me between $20 to $30 for something
that maybe would have taken me four or five hours to create from scratch.
And now I can use it forever.
And so I do think that as the models get better,
we're trying to optimize for getting the most out of the product
via your tokens.
But yeah, everything in Grokbot is just consumption-based.
So it's just based on how you talk to Grokbot, how Grokbot uses the computer.
And you can customize that.
For example, if you prefer a particular style of Grokbot talking,
if you think maybe it's too verbose, tell it that.
And then that can also help your token usage as well.
So you can actually adjust how much compute it does,
or how much it spins?
I don't think you can adjust its computer use.
That, I think, is out of your control.
What I think you can adjust is how it talks to you.
So I think I-
Lauren is currently offline, which is kind of sick.
So we're going to try something new out, basically.
What Lauren's going to do is explain to me how to build this.
And I'm going to walk through what I was doing during the break
and how I'm using kind of Cloud agents.
This will be good, because Lauren can then tell me how to do it better, basically.
Yeah, and a backseat driver.
A little bit of a backseat driver.
So if you want to, we can cut over to my screen.
And I'll walk through kind of my setup and what we've been doing so far.
Yeah, screen imminent, I'm sure.
Yeah, I think if you have Dr. Eggbot installed, you have an engineer bot.
And we have the plan that we wrote earlier already committed to the repo.
So I'm thinking maybe to start-
I think it'd be interesting to use like potato mode out of Pstack to do some prototyping.
Just like really quick and loose prototypes that,
you know, we don't need a login screen.
You don't need even a database right now.
We can just hard code a bunch of things just to visually see how the game plays.
And then we can kind of iterate from there once we get your screen up.
Still working through some AV issues.
So what I've been working on kind of during the break-
Okay, sweet. We have my screen up.
I've been using kind of the way-
This is kind of Lauren's setup, right?
So I have Dr. Eggbot that creates new bots for me.
And I have my sort of founding engineer bot that's working on a landing page.
So basically what I did was I said, you know, I think before we cut out,
Lauren had walked us through kind of her plan, which-
So we had our repo and we had docs and plans and Lauren was talking about our MVP, right?
So Lauren built this document with her agents context.
And one way to share information is just to point my agent at that context as well.
So I said, hey, take a look at that document. That's going to be our game.
Our first goal is to make a landing page.
And so given that it's a monorepo reader plan and propose like a nice lander stack
with my project planning skill.
So I typically look at my project planning skill.
I basically say, this is what I want for every new project I create.
And if I'm owning the landing page, I want basically an official-
I like to use scaffolds because like we got to move fast here.
We're not writing our own stack.
So usually something like T3, tan stack.
If it's like a React Native app, maybe Expo,
Next, really like, or if it's just simple, it could be V.
And then I have a bunch of other like opinionated UI guidelines and styling guidelines
that I like to spin up in my new projects.
And then I also really like this make interfaces feel better skill.
I find it's pretty good for like UI polish and some of the smaller details.
So I said, hey, just like start reading these things and also Lauren shared context
and then make a plan with our end skills for what a lander would look like.
Are those skills published anywhere, by the way?
Before I share them out.
These are project planning is my personal skill
and then make interfaces feel better is a design skill.
Man, it's gonna be tough.
I wish they had like the author gave me credit,
but someone on Twitter made this and it's really good.
So I don't want to say the wrong person off the top of my head.
But make interfaces feel better.
If you look that one up, you should find it pretty easy.
So my sort of MVP here is just like a button-based lander with create next step.
And I kicked this off kind of without anybody else knowing.
So Lauren can critique my sort of like architecture here,
but it's like basically pretty lightweight.
And one of the things that I always like to include in my new projects is like
OG meta tags and just like basic site meta information.
If you're unfamiliar, meta information is like the,
if you Google search a site, like the title and the description,
and then also the image if you like post something on Twitter that you see.
So it adds a really nice kind of level of polish.
So what it did was I like approved this and it was actually nice
because Grokbot made the right correction,
which was that it actually started to applying like
subtract before you add principles, like simplify things,
like removing auth, removing a wait list.
We were literally just want like a V1.
And then I kicked it out to a cursor cloud agent
with a PStack prompt to start working.
So like my agent will start using potato mode to find,
is that the correct terminology?
Like should I say use PStack? Do I say use potato mode?
Yeah, I would say use.
So in Grokbot, you can type slash potato mode.
So you can also do that. You would like use slash potato mode.
Okay, I see.
But yeah, you can actually,
even if you're just saying use potato mode,
your agent or bot should be smart enough to know what that means.
Since it has access to the PStack plugin,
it can see like, oh, that's what you meant.
So yeah, and I have cursor configured.
Obviously, we're using Grokbot for most of the building,
but Grokbot is essentially a lightweight harness,
and cursor is a coding harness.
And so it can be useful for Grokbot to do some of the conversation
in the back and forth,
and then use cursor to do the actual engineering and the coding.
And all of these agents are running in the cloud.
So similar to Grokbot,
actually none of this is happening on my desktop,
which is kind of nice.
You can see my workspace is still getting set up here,
and some of the environment setup is still being done.
But in the meantime, basically, we have our lander getting spun up.
And then the other thing I was working on in Grokbot
was with my sort of creative director bot here.
I was thinking about visuals, right?
Like, what is our game going to look like?
So there's a really awesome tool out there called Dialkit,
which allows you to customize UIs.
And it's open source.
It's really great for designers.
And I was like, oh, well,
like what if we started prototyping assets,
and then we use these sliders to be able to play around with like flat
SVG tokens.
And I've never built a video game before.
You probably heard Roshan and Lauren talking about video games.
I'm like, I don't even really know about game design.
I'm like a total noob to video games.
So I'm like, hey, do research on how these things work.
I've used Phaser before for some cool visualization stuff.
So I'm like, OK, start there.
I know what that thing is.
And from there, Grok Bot's backing
into these technologies.
So every research project I do, every time
I'm trying to build something, I'm like, OK,
if I don't know about it, help me understand it.
And Super AutoPets, which might be misspelled here,
like Miss Capitalized or whatever,
is something that Lauren recommended
that we look at for inspiration for light and fun graphics.
And so from that, I backed into, through the same engineering
process, an asset playground.
And that's also working in cursor.
So we have our asset playground.
And then we also have the lander that should be running here
as well.
So that's kind of where I'm at.
Maybe, Lauren, you can direct me
on how to start with Dr. Eggbot here
to spin up another engineering bot that
builds the infrastructure.
Yeah, I would ask Dr. Eggbot or even your chief of staff
to talk to Dr. Eggbot if you want.
It depends who your main bot is and where all the context is.
So for example, from my setup, I
have my chief of staff, Steve, who has all the context
about the project, all our credentials,
what the game we're building is.
And then Steve works with our other bots.
But you could tell, basically, I would say something like,
tell Dr. Eggbot to create a engineering bot for me.
This engineer will, what do you say,
use P-stack and potato mode to spawn cloud agents
to work on our game.
And you can say that the job of the engineer bot
is to the job the engineer bot is to orchestrate these cloud
agents and supervise them and check their work.
For the first phase of what we're doing today,
we're going to do some prototyping.
That's not all the engineer bot will do,
but we'll focus on quick, lightweight prototypes just so we
can get a visual feel of how the game plays before we start
building out the real.
We don't need login yet, when we don't even
know if the game is fun.
So I want to iterate really fast on the MVP of the game
and have the sliders you were talking about,
where we can tweak things, like the visuals or even the game
constants could be interesting.
But yeah, let's start with a bot that does that.
And Dr. Eggbot, try not to make this engineer
too prototype focused, make it durable enough
that it can do prototyping, but also the serious engineering
work will do later.
Cool.
Transcribing.
You've got to love it.
It's so riffing.
Yeah, my favorite pattern as well is add to the end,
restate this in your own words before you start working,
just so you can confirm, because that's
a big blob of text.
I feel like that's what if you were talking to somebody
and you wanted to make sure that they understand what you said,
you could say, hey, restate this in your own words.
I mean, that would be kind of awkward to tell someone.
It's awkward, but that's what active listening is.
That's true.
While you guys were doing that, I actually
got the visual playground running locally.
If we want to take a look at that, maybe see
if we want to play with some of these sliders.
I'll juggle some of this stuff, and we can maybe cut over
to Roshan's laptop and see what he's working with.
Yeah, can we switch to my screen, please,
if we get the chance?
I know this was something you just kind of put together
pretty quickly, Matt, and I haven't used this before,
but it looked like we could maybe
play with some of the properties here.
And I love these sliders.
This is really fun.
So we can maybe tweak some of the icons.
Obviously, this is a really lightweight,
and we probably want to think about how we evolve
these icons a little bit.
But we have some good initial cut of the structure.
I guess maybe what you guys think.
These are the bots.
These are the bots, it looks like.
And so maybe we have bots like this.
Oh, interesting.
Do you mind zooming in?
It's kind of hard.
Oh, yeah, let me zoom in.
Yeah, totally.
How's that?
You probably want them to look more like bots, right?
Yeah, I think currently they look too abstract.
I kind of like it.
We should make it look good.
That's interesting, actually.
I didn't think about the color having a meaning.
Yeah.
But that could be kind of cool.
Do we think we should maybe we should prompt?
Do you have a bot that was helping with the visual system?
And I wonder if we should prompt that one too, maybe?
I would say my suggestion is let's just
get the most basic prototype up first so that we can actually
all contribute to the code base.
I think it'd be kind of complicated to build this part.
And the prototype at the same time.
But I think it's a good start.
And another thing we might want to have this system do as well
is tweak some of the in-game constants that we set.
We mentioned earlier that there's this rock, paper,
scissor thing that goes between Prisma and Dex.
And I wonder if the bonus being 22%
if we can tweak that on the fly and just replay a game
and see how it feels.
That lets us get into this really nice iteration loop
where we don't have to wait for the agent to go off
and do something.
We can actually just tweak the values in real time
and see the result live.
And it gives us really nice quick loop to make.
We need to shorten the time to fun.
And I think something like that would.
Yeah, I like that.
And that'll also give us some ability
to test different mechanics maybe as well.
So if we had a playground where we could tweak some things
and see the impact on the game, tuning the game state
and game behavior will be really important here too.
So yeah, yeah, yeah.
How's your bot doing?
My bots are working.
In progress.
Do you want to open them up?
And we can just take a look and we can kind of introspect.
Cool.
So yeah, I don't know.
What are we doing here?
We're sticking on Russian screen.
We're going over to my screen.
I'll switch over to math screen.
Oh, I think we're on.
Yeah.
Should we cut over to math screen?
Show us bots.
Awesome.
There we go.
Perfect.
OK, cool.
So I'm working on some preview deploys here.
So I think we're just going to do a quick preview, which
is what Kursar is working on in the background.
This was the prototype.
So Dr. Eggbot is still kind of working on restating this
in its own words here.
Yeah, we're having some.
So hopefully we'll have an update there.
It's still waking up this morning.
The founding engineer is working on this preview deploy.
And we should have that up shortly.
And we also have our growth engineer,
who's working on a few other things.
Maybe something a little fun that I worked on this morning,
completely irrelevant and not related to building things,
is I got all the Bufo meme Slack emojis in our Slack.
So what I did was I actually had a Grokbot rip those
off the website and download a directory of PNGs.
And then rather than uploading, setting custom Slack emojis
myself, I just asked Grokbot to find a way to use computer use
to go and add all the Bufo emojis.
So now we have a complete pack of 1,200 Bufo emojis in Slack.
So while the rest of the team was doing work,
I was kind of goofing off.
And this is the life of a dev rel, basically.
So yeah, that's a few other things.
We also have our knowledge-based bot
that started working on updating our notion with our company
doc.
So now we're working on our game design studio.
We still have some objectives, but we're
documenting the pivot.
And eventually, what our go-to-market strategy
might be, it pulled the product plan with the core loop
into notion.
And so with our knowledge worker bot here,
we're managing some of those things as well.
Yeah, so now we're waiting on the bots to get to work here.
Seems like we might be chugging along.
So some of the things I'm thinking here to do,
basically, I'm working on the landing page.
And then up next is probably AEO SEO stuff and maybe ABI
testing stuff.
So these are the next things I'll
direct my bot to work on.
And then whatever marketing looks like,
which I think we can figure out based on our lean-in
to existing distribution.
Only thing about our ads infra as well.
These are some old notes, I think.
And yeah, maybe we could cut off my screen momentarily.
Computer shovel is not fun.
Sweet.
Yeah, and I think we're just going
to be cranking on building out that stuff for a little bit.
So yeah, if you're just joining in,
we're working on our game studio and our first game.
We're just cranking along this morning.
Live build time.
Day two.
I just had a bot do some updates to Notion as well.
So I think we'll check that knowledge base going.
Put in the diagram that we drew earlier today.
So we have that as a reference for any future bots that
need to learn about the business.
That'll hopefully help a little bit.
Cool.
I guess while we're waiting for our bots to work,
I wonder if I can go on a bit of a tangent
and talk about some engineering things.
Try to do my talk.
Yeah, I mean, we can just work or you can do the talk.
It's up to you.
We don't have to be talking all the time.
We've got to get some stuff done too.
All right, guys.
I think we're having some technical difficulties.
We're going to be right back with you in a bit.
Welcome back, everyone.
You're watching us spend 72 hours building a game studio
and a game for the game studio.
That's what we're doing.
So we had some computer issues, but I think we resolved it.
And if we can bring my screen up, I can drive the prototype.
Let's actually build it.
OK, so I'm going to be using cursor.
And again, if you're not familiar with Grokbot and cursor,
so cursor is like more of the coding tool and Grokbots
for general bots, I guess, for doing knowledge work
and things like that.
They work really well together.
But now I want to iterate really on the engineering work.
So I'm going to switch to cursor for a minute.
And I've kicked off a local agent.
And so far, I have to start over a little bit
because this agent doesn't have all the context
that the bot has.
So what we do have is the docs that we've
committed to the repo.
And I've got it to restate in its own words what the game is.
So I can just double check that it understands the game.
So I'm going to just read through and see if it makes sense.
So we've got a short competitive loop.
So it play logs in, imports a bot.
We get a three-player roster.
The lineup is hidden for your opponent.
Match another account.
Could it copy Elo part, which is really important?
Yeah, the Elo part is interesting
because I have never designed a matchmaking system.
But I've played games like Marvel Rivals that
have some papers out there.
So I'll just maybe just use that as a reference.
I'm sure we will iterate over that.
But we're just going to keep it simple for now.
But the Elo rating is essentially like a score,
almost like a chess rating, where the more games you win,
your score goes up.
There's a factor as well, depending
who you get matched against.
The score might rise by a smaller amount or a bigger amount
and so on and so forth, just to keep it
interesting for the matchmaking.
And then there's a bunch of sign-in stuff
that I want to skip for the prototype.
So I'm going to tell it some notes here.
Let's just say for the prototype, let me move this bigger.
Let's skip sign-in for now.
Just focus on the game loop so we can iterate.
And then use potato mode prototyping.
I want to have a few different prototypes
to choose from.
And then let's keep everything local for now, no DB required.
And I also want to say include some debug panels, where
I have sliders and input boxes to tweak game variables
constants for the quick iteration loop.
You have a prototyping section of potato mode, right?
That's when you say use potato mode prototyping.
That's how the agent knows what to do there.
Yeah.
Go, go, go.
And so the idea of prototyping for me is that the thing that's
important for me right now is like,
or at least when I think about games,
that the point of the game is that it's fun.
And all of the other stuff is not even important
if the game isn't fun.
So I want to just really cut it down to just the core loop.
And actually, that reminds me that we're
going to need some bots from seed, some bots from xAI,
marketplace, as our default set of bots.
And I think, yeah, let's just go with that.
But while that's working, the point of prototyping for me
is to quickly get to the fun part.
And I asked it to build those sliders
because I wanted to be able to tweak things in real time
and just replay the game so we can just quickly
see if it's actually fun.
And if it's not, we can think about how to make it fun.
Yeah, I like that strategy.
I feel like it sort of gives us the ability to not just
build a prototype, but let us tweak the prototype
without having to prompt a bunch back and forth all
at once and give us the little playground
that we can use to actually tweak our MVP in live.
I feel like that will let us iterate a lot quicker,
which is great.
Yeah.
Something cool, I guess, I can talk about as well,
is just how potato mode works, if you've never used it before.
So potato mode is, how do I explain it?
It's kind of like a router skill.
So the skill itself has not really
in many very specific instructions,
except that for different scenarios,
we use these skills and these principles.
So in P-stack, we have these things called principles, which
describe some principle.
So for example, experience first is
this really short skill that talks about choosing delight
when you're implementing things.
Instead of implementation convenience, choose user delight.
Every feature needs to be justified.
Ship less, but ship better.
Prototyping, right?
So design decisions are cheaper in throwaway HTML than production
code.
So I feel like that's really important, again,
so we can kind of iterate quickly.
And it looks like our agent is going
to iterate on just a simple in-memory object
with some seeded bots through slot lineup.
And OK, now it's going to, oh yeah,
this is something that potato mode also does,
is that it has a architecture skill that's called architect.
And this skill will use different models to come up
with different plans.
So as you can see, we have four different models here,
Fable, Sol, Grok, and Composer.
And we're essentially going to erase them
and see who can come up with the better architecture.
And we'll pick the best one and merge
in any other interesting ideas from the other one.
And hopefully, these are quick enough.
But we're going to wait for the other candidates
to finish before judging.
But I don't know if we really need this for the prototype,
but I'll let it run anyway.
But this is pretty helpful in general,
because different models excel at different types of tasks.
And when it comes to things like architecture,
sometimes you want to think about,
like you may have different constraints
or different criteria that you may not have thought about.
So having different models kind of swarm on them
and think about them can be pretty helpful.
But I'm going to actually say, let's skip architect.
And while you're typing there, for those who are joining
or are just hopping into the stream,
we are in the middle of our three-day sprint here
to ship and launch a real product.
We're working on a game studio with our first game being
built live.
And you're watching Lauren demonstrate
how to use Potato Mode, which is a plugin that's
available for Crockbot and Cursor
to help drive your own software development projects.
And so, sole stuff you can go and use on your own.
And yeah, we're just cooking and building
a really quick prototype as soon as we can,
so we get a feel for how that works and feels,
and hopefully be able to iterate from there.
Yeah.
And I'm just telling my agent to skip the architect skills,
since that's going to be a little bit slower.
And we're just prototyping anyway,
so I don't actually care about the architecture at this point.
I'm telling it to use Crockbot for the first prototype.
And then we're going to run it locally
so we can actually play it.
And if you're not familiar with Cursor,
Cursor has an inbuilt browser, which is really nice.
Oh, I have a favorite in here, subway surfers.
I won't play that.
Yeah.
Sometimes when you're just waiting for an agent,
what do you do, right?
You go scroll X, or you play a little game.
And I just so happen to have subway surfers in there.
But let's see how fast it can go.
We can also just, oh, there you go, Crock's completed.
It came up with, oh, it came back with a design.
You can take a look at the design
and see what it came up with.
So the throwaway prototype is going
to be just vanilla HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
Makes sense to me.
Keep it simple.
Everything's going to be kept in memory.
We'll have three different UI variants
that we can try out and toggle between them,
which is nice as well.
It's going to fetch the list of bots from the marketplace
as our mock seed data.
And then we have some.
This code's not very interesting because it's just vanilla.
But it makes sense to me.
It's data-driven.
So let's see.
It's coming with some data shapes as well.
So that's something that we talk about in the potato mode
skills, is thinking a lot about data structures
because that determines pretty much everything.
So it's got a bunch of types set up here.
All makes sense to me.
Oh, it's even come up with state transitions as well.
Almost like a state machine.
Very brain farted from it.
But yeah, I can't wait to see what it builds.
Oh, this design's pretty comprehensive actually.
It's very long.
It's also got alternatives to consider.
Let's see.
Three independent page prototypes, each with a copied suit in combat.
Live computing result with no snapshot.
Well, these are just like implementation details.
I don't care about this right now.
Maybe I'm curious, Lauren, like when you're typically working with these bots,
when are you sort of actually inspecting the output versus sort of letting the bots cook?
Like how do you think about sort of, you know, interacting versus delegating?
Um, that's actually a really interesting question because for more mature code bases,
I feel like, so like when I work on Grok Bot itself, for example,
a lot of my time has is now spent on sort of Grok Bot architecture.
And I'm not really, I'm not really observing or micromanaging the agents as much because
a lot of development has already gone into creating an agent friendly architecture for those bots.
But for a new project like this, I actually want to be kind of in the loop so I can observe, right?
Like what are the mistakes that my agents keep making?
And it looks like it already has that here.
It sounds like because we're in the more zero to one early life cycle of the project,
it's a little more important for us to be in the weeds, kind of like reading the output,
making sure the agents go off in the wrong direction and kind of come back later.
Yeah.
Okay, so how does this work?
Got a pool of bots, some lanes.
Okay.
Oh, I see.
I guess it's just like, it's come up with some random.
Oh, yeah. Okay, that makes sense.
So yeah, this UI is extremely bad right now, but it's good enough for me to actually just like
think about the how the games actually going to work.
We have some seed bots here.
And actually, let me get this bigger so you can all see it.
So I'm gonna, of course, pick Dr. Eggbot.
And we talked about how the other two bots are randomly chosen.
It looks like we have three common bots.
So we didn't get very lucky.
Yeah.
And then we'll obviously come up with like proper visuals for this.
But the like right now you can reorder.
Do you guys have opinions on who should go first?
How should we order our team?
I like outbound prospecting first.
The salesperson in me.
Well, I'll say outbound prospecting has 72 charisma.
Okay.
But, but, but, but it only has, but the skill, the ability is hustle and it's dexterity based.
Dr. Eggbot has Riz.
I'm actually noticing a bug here where the numbers are more don't add up to 100.
Oh, yeah.
So let's actually fix that.
Um, so the stat, the total stats should add 200 for common.
I think what's cool about this process too is like we're building a lot of scaffolding.
And then eventually this is sort of scaffolding the agent can drive.
So if we kind of give the agent like, you know, some sort of playground,
it can also verify its own output in.
It probably won't look just like this, I think, but I think we're sort of like
starting to build a lot of foundation here.
It's really cool.
And actually, let me open this.
And the, oh, great.
Yeah.
Oh, it already did.
I'm gonna hide that more real estate here.
While we're waiting for the bot to make the changes.
It looks like it gave us a pretty good debug panel as well.
We can just like tune the advantage.
The slider is so wonky.
Look at that.
Oh, wait, is it reminds you of that website where you have people show examples of the worst
possible.
Yeah.
So that doesn't work.
That's a very weird slider.
But I mean, it's got the numbers right.
So common cap.
Yeah, it's got it all set.
The bug right now is that, okay, just reloaded.
Okay, now it adds up to 100.
Nice.
Okay.
So that looks correct.
Should we get the, oh, actually, let's show a design mode.
Let me, so in cursor, very, very, very cool feature
is if you open your app in the cursor browser, and you click on design mode, you can actually
click on the elements directly and tell your bot.
So the bot knows exactly what you're talking about.
And I can tell it here, there's this input is weird, and doesn't slide correctly.
Please fix.
And it lets you stay in the flow, right?
Because you can just quickly like, okay, that that is about it.
So when you like quickly add, you know, get that in there.
I don't know, like maybe, I think that's good for now.
I actually want to play the game.
So we have, okay, let's go with Dr. Eggbot.
Let's just go with the default and just fight and see what happens.
So in this first prototype, so I guess the way how games work,
I've never really built any games.
The way I imagine that they're coded is that you have obviously the graphics, right?
And then you have your main game logic.
And they don't necessarily have to be, I'd say like blocking each other, if that makes sense.
In this case, what I'm imagining for a game is the game could actually resolve instantly
once the matchmaking is done.
But we just show an animation, right?
And we play, like when we play a session, it shows like, yeah,
but later on, we can add graphics like, you know, Dr. Eggbot used Rids.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And as a cool animation.
I like that because I like the sort of the point of the initial game is that sort of,
once you set the lineup, the action resolves automatically, right?
And so we don't sort of need to wait for resolution.
So like, know the results as soon as the matchmaking step is done.
And so I think if that's the case, then really, just a matter of like figuring
out how we want to add some fun to that with animations or other things.
Yeah, it's actually kind of nice.
It'll give us the option to sort of build that over time and evolve it over time if we want.
So.
Right.
How do I make a new game?
New deal.
There we go.
Cool.
It looks like every time you're hitting that, it's randomizing our team a little bit.
Right.
Yeah, but is it randomizing your opponent?
I guess not.
Oh, there's different.
Oh, okay. Never mind.
I forgot it gave us different UIs to choose from too.
This is too.
Okay.
What do you think so far?
Like, do the mechanics make sense, I guess?
Yeah.
Do we think it's getting it right?
So I guess for the first, like, let's look at that first one with critique and research.
Is it charisma?
With the bonus, that looks like the bonus logic is there.
It looks like we have the base stats there.
Yeah, we can simulate a bunch of games, which is nice.
That's actually really helpful to be able to simulate that advantage slider.
I'm a bit changing.
Yeah, it's actually interesting because if we go back to...
We can actually see the bonus taking...
This actually turned the game around, where round one Dr.
Igbot actually lost with the 22% advantage since it was like Dex versus Int.
And so projects managers went up to 18.3 because of the advantage.
And so it won.
So I feel like the base logic kind of makes sense to me.
Yeah, I think so too.
I think we have the like core logic loop here.
It'd be cool to figure out like how do we start to translate this into
like something that is a bit more like of an actual prototype that we could play.
So maybe that would be the next thing.
Or what do you think would there be some more...
Yeah, I was wondering if we can do a workflow like, you know, use image generation
to come up with mock game screens for a game.
I guess like I keep going back to super autopads because I think it's like a really good reference.
Yeah.
Could be a good visual reference.
But look, oops.
But look up, drop up on the web for images.
For I guess a visual reference on robots.
Look like.
And I want to essentially have a few images we can use for just starting to brainstorm.
Okay, how is this game actually going to look?
Because the core logic makes sense.
But obviously we don't want to just play a game with like that looks like this Kanban board.
So let's get it to create some images first.
So we can start thinking about how it will actually look.
I'm curious if both of you have thought about how like a visual style.
Yeah, I was actually working on that a little bit in the background and have something.
It's very vibe coded.
And it's just like a little dots on a screen.
But I started to like the way it was evolving a little bit.
And I'm not you've also been you've also been thinking about visual styles a bit.
But yeah, I don't know if we wanted.
I think it's worth trying to generate something now that we have the scaffolding.
And then maybe we can apply some visual layers on top and kind of like apply the polish to it.
Yeah.
Cool.
What are the mock ups that you've been curious to look at them?
Yeah.
Well, I have a really likely.
Can we share a screen for a minute?
This is very vibe coded.
But I sort of was working with the bot in the background as well trying to see if I
could prototype something just to get a feel for how the core game loop might feel and
just think about the product experience.
And so in this case, the bot sort of made a binder of possible bots.
Can you zoom in?
Oh, yeah.
And you can kind of see like in this case, it rolled a few that are, you know,
legendary common, etc.
And just gave us some some screens for how this could look.
And I don't know, sometimes I find it helpful.
Maybe just like we can get some inspiration from a few other ideas.
But you know, we can unlock our bot order and kind of slide them around,
which I think is kind of cool.
And we could probably make this drag and drop.
You know, right now, it's not really a drag and drop.
And so you should probably think about how we do that.
But you know, we can choose different like if we have a team,
maybe we could have a team more than three.
But I think we're said we're going to start with three first, we kind of start with that.
And we can lock in our order.
And then I kind of like this visual as well,
kind of like seeing how the different bots would line up against each other.
It's a little like, you know, we could show some information about the rules
and maybe the conditions.
Again, this is sort of a really just a vibe coded prototype.
But you know, this could be a cool way to kind of show the lineup
and kind of what happens in the lineup.
So I like this.
I think this looks looks good.
Yeah.
And what's cool about these is, you know, each one of these can have its own replay
IDs and these kind of static assets that could be then shared later on.
And you kind of see the result as the next slide or like kind of here's sort of who
who versus who and then how the ELO is,
ELO score is calculated and then kind of getting a replay ID or something.
This is all obviously fake.
Yeah.
And then being able to maybe like go into your binder of cards
and kind of see who you've drafted so far.
So yeah, I don't know.
I feel like there's something here.
This might be maybe some useful inspiration.
Nice.
So actually, I think while we're building this,
we have an interesting story to cut out to.
One of my favorite local coffee shops actually is a big RockBot user.
Oh, yeah.
Good friend of mine Marcel, I bumped into him in the coffee shop one day
and he was using RockBot.
We ran a little store on him.
So I think when we get a chance, we're going to cut over to
the story of Icon Coffee in San Francisco in Potrero Hill
and how they're using RockBot to get more done.
Love it.
My name is Marcel.
I'm from Icon Coffee.
I'm one of the owners here.
I run the coffee program.
This is kind of serendipitous, right?
I live in the neighborhood.
I've been coming here for a few years
and I bumped into you in the coffee shop the other week.
And I saw you're using RockBot.
Yeah.
I think it was that same week my son started school.
All these emails come from the school
and here's RockBot, right?
And I'm like, you do it.
I gave it access to the parent portal
and all the messages come through
and the bot just kind of organizes for me.
I like to say like removing the noise
and just kind of focusing on the signal, right?
So after testing it out using my personal life,
I was like, okay, let's see what you can do at work.
You know, Icon is more than just a coffee shop.
We also have a roastery.
We source.
We roast.
And, you know, there's just a lot of moving parts.
So his name's always been Rex.
I'm always like, hey, Rex,
or, you know, we're always just hanging out
and just talking on the car.
And so Rex has always been kind of like my chief of staff
per se for here at the company.
We gave it API access to our POS system.
We're able to get reports, metrics.
I can be on my phone.
I can be on my computer and be like,
how did we do two years ago?
Like what kind of growth are we seeing?
Or when we were optimizing our menu for the cafe,
I took a picture of the menu, uploaded to RockBot.
These things right here,
we've only sold X amount in the last X amount of months, right?
I'm like, okay, that doesn't make sense.
Let's get it out.
My son's about to be 10.
That time is so precious.
An extra hour, two hours in my day
where I could just like, oh, I don't have to do that anymore.
Right?
This repetitive task is now, you know,
Homebot's got my RockBot's on it, right?
So it's just, it's lovely.
Definitely feels like living in the future, you know?
I think we're getting there one step at a time.
For sure, brother.
So yeah, I mean, I think it's super cool to see
how Marcel's using Bot not only in his personal life,
but also in his business.
What is your favorite thing to get from IKON Coffee?
Favorite thing?
I'm a huge Cappuccino guy.
Okay, okay.
Very good.
Very good espresso.
Very good milk-based beverages.
Okay, consider the recommendation.
Awesome.
Cool.
Well, I think when we left off,
we are making progress on our game studio and game
as our business that we're building over 72 hours here.
We have done some prototyping,
which is really great.
We kind of built a little bit of a debug tool
so we can kind of see the impact
of some of the various game mechanics
on the actual game we're building.
And then I think when we left off right before
showing IKON Coffee,
we were generating some images
for how we might think about some of the art style
and maybe being able to tweak that later on.
So maybe, Lauren, what do we have?
Yeah, let's get our screen back on.
I have some, I don't know if I like these mocks yet,
but like it's something.
I feel like right now it's very text-heavy.
But we can kind of tweak it.
I love how colorful it is.
Yeah, the colors are nice.
Yeah, I think it's a bit overwhelming at the moment.
Yeah.
But we can tweak it.
This is cool.
I actually really like this one.
Maybe the font size needs to be adjusted.
But you know how,
I don't know if you've ever played gacha games.
Probably not, Matt.
It's okay, I'll play games.
Sorry.
But the gacha game is like this
concept where it's usually a mobile game.
And the game is about like getting characters.
And then they have like different,
when you pull a character,
it has like a different variety.
And they have like a cool animation that shows up.
Maybe we could do something like that.
That looks kind of interesting.
I kind of like, I feel like this design is like really cute.
You see like our little grog bot has a little ribbon.
And again, very text heavy.
But yeah, I feel like we could work with that.
I like the idea of actually almost like having your team all be one color as well.
That might be a cool way to like make that look interesting.
So there's also this really cool.
This is like one of my favorite things.
There's this, someone made this CSS library that applies this cool visual effect to them.
And I was wondering if like maybe that could be cool to add to our bots as well.
Especially for the layers.
Especially I've got it going off and building the,
let's build that visual prototype now,
now that we have this seems to work.
Yeah, we can always skin, we can always like change the design later on too, right?
But I feel like if we can get sort of the container sorted,
then we can go in and tweak that.
Yeah, yeah.
Cool.
So yeah, I guess our next step is we're going to start actually building out the prototype.
Looks like we're also just making a quick,
a couple of quick tweaks here as well to the prototype.
Yeah, I'm telling it to,
oh, I told it to apply the Pokemon CSS.
So we'll wait for that to happen.
Cool.
And then I'm also asking it to start implementing,
like start working on the visual changes
to that you generated images.
I can start to see, I started to see some shinies.
We're getting set up.
Oh, wow.
That is very shiny.
Yeah, we might need to.
We might need to.
Oh my gosh.
It's kind of way too shiny, but we can play with that.
Also, it's like, it's yeah, like, why are they all reading those?
Yeah.
I don't know if the agent fully understood the assignment on that one,
but we can, we can, we can tell it to do that.
I kind of steered it badly, I think,
because I told it I got kind of nerd snipe like,
oh, it'd be kind of cool to add this CSS.
So what I want, what I wanted to do was like,
apply that to the visual prototype.
So now I'm telling it, okay, actually go off and,
you know, do the visual changes.
Cool.
So I actually like reading the thinking block.
I don't know if you ever do this, but it's collapsed.
I think there's a setting you can do in cursor to show them.
I like to have them hidden by default,
but sometimes I'll just click on them because I'm very,
I'm always curious to see like how the agents are thinking about things.
And fun fact is like, a lot of the skills I made were inspired
by just like looking through these thinking blocks.
Yeah.
Like just listening like, wait, why are you,
how did you determine that when you never actually looked at the code?
Yeah.
You know, so.
So I've also seen you share this advice, which I've used a ton,
which is like anytime you see the agent think incorrectly,
that's probably a good opportunity or chance for you to like build a skill
to fix it, right?
Versus just like, you know, I have this tendency when I'm prompting to,
you know, just say like, actually, no, do the next thing,
do the next thing, the next thing, and kind of get to a result
instead of taking the chance to take a step back and say,
well, wait a minute, like consider what you did wrong,
turn this into a skill or update an existing skill
that like helps me avoid the whole thing to begin with, right?
And I think I found that balance a really like interesting one to strike.
Yeah.
Oh, you see, it even applied the, I don't know if you can see this,
but it applied the shimmer to the uncommon cards.
So maybe a bit too much.
Well, we'll turn it down.
Yeah.
But okay, let me let me try and while it's building that,
let me just, we have, yeah, we can run it, run an example.
Let me just try it again.
So it, I'm wondering about balancing because like,
like if the bots have fairies and the bots are,
so one thing we did talk about is that once a bot has been generated into our game,
the stats are permanent.
Right.
And so even if somebody else shares that, uses that same bot,
you get the same bot.
Right.
And I'm just wondering like, how we balance that?
Because obviously you would always want the strongest bot in your team.
And so you would try to like, maybe someone shares it in chat,
like here's my legendary bot, big bot.
Right.
And now everybody puts that in their main roster.
That could be not so great, right?
Because like everybody would have a legendary bot now.
Yeah, that's true.
I wonder if we should separate the rarity from the actual bot,
you know, like you, you still get the same base stats,
but then whether or not the rarity part of it is just a randomness thing.
So for example, you could have a Dr. Eggbot,
then I could have a Dr. Eggbot that I happen to roll legendary on.
And that can be kind of interesting, right?
Because then you have like multiple versions of the bot where the core stats,
well, I guess the core stats would then be different, right?
Because yeah.
Yeah.
I think we'll just like a little bit of that for now.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, right.
Oh, they might be, might create an interesting game meta
where people try to find the best bots and then, you know,
like try and get the legendaries and that could be cool.
Yeah, it's like this like almost meta game of how do you find?
Right.
How do you find the best bots?
Yeah.
That could be interesting.
It'd be really cool if people were like creating new bot templates.
And well, that's the hope, right?
Is that people create a bunch of bot templates
and in the hopes of finding some of the best characters.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, we can always tweak that later on too, right?
I feel like that's something that would work for everyone, no problem.
So yeah, I guess that's the thing I would imagine is like,
I would always want a legendary bot.
Yeah.
Okay, so here we go.
We have some more visual game.
Real big visual.
Okay.
All right.
Now we got something.
Make that full screen so I can see the browser window full screen.
Yeah, good call.
Okay, that looks definitely more interesting than before.
Obviously, this part, I don't really like the leaves.
I think we need to put that in a separate screen, right?
Yeah, exactly.
You have your team and then we can get that implemented.
I feel like this is fine for a V1.
Right.
Also, I need to tell it to, so the shimmers are too severe.
It looks like a rainbow.
And I wonder if that's because...
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, this is way too severe.
I mean, I kind of like wacky though.
You know, I'm like, this might be like party.
I wonder if it just looks like that because the card is very small.
And so the gradient is not scaled.
Yeah, I think that sounds right.
Yeah, like you need to scale up.
Maybe the gradient on the rainbow needs to scale up.
The gradient needs to scale to the size of the card.
And then actually, I want to use Design Mode as well to like...
I'll just tell that what I'm talking about and cut and paste there.
Let's do that.
For those who aren't familiar, Lauren was talking about this a minute ago.
But Design Mode is a really cool feature in cursor where you can,
as you're seeing on the screen here,
interact with the actual elements on the page.
You don't have to pick a pre-existing div.
You can actually draw a box or draw a circle with a cursor around whatever you'd like like that.
How do I do this?
There you go.
What's really cool about this is you can actually...
Oh, I can do this.
Yeah, there you go.
That's what I was trying to do.
Draw an area, a screen area,
and actually prompt the Asian to do something with that space, which is really cool.
And then I want to say, can we move these lanes into their own page?
And so what else do we want to tweak?
I kind of think we only need three...
Well, we can do this later,
but I feel like we really want to nail the start with your bot
and only get three bots on your team versus having this whole pool.
But that might...
I mean, I think right now this UI is very debug.
Right.
For the debug purposes, I think this works.
We just want to make sure that the lanes and the lane results is really good.
Okay, let's actually try the planes.
Yeah.
Who should go first?
Can you zoom in a bit?
Awesome.
Cool.
Well, this one's actually really strong because it's got 77 charisma
and the skill uses charisma.
Yeah, I look at that.
That's like our best one.
That should not add up to 100 because it's legendary.
Oh, you know what?
Now that I'm thinking, I wonder if there's like a tweak we could make where...
I don't know if this would extend the game too long.
So right now there's only a max of three rounds.
But maybe the ordering would matter more
if your bot had like health points or something.
And so it could actually survive around and go on to the next round.
I think it could work, but should we try just doing a one round battle first
and maybe starting with that?
Like just this is it and you replay this and that's it?
What do you mean?
So when you said three rounds, what were you thinking about there?
Okay, now I put it into the new screen.
Okay, so let's just try this again.
We've got Dr. Eggbot, common,
my own engineer common.
We'll just go with the default and hit fight.
And we can see that...
Where is the result?
Oh, here we go.
Well, I won.
Yes, this is cool.
So the ability bonuses are in, which is causing that 22% bonus.
Yeah.
Dr. Eggbot did not win the first round.
I'm sorry.
All right, Dr. Eggbot.
But yeah, so in my mind, this is like actually the MVP
and that's the result and you're done.
Were you thinking that we had a few more rounds to it?
Yeah, you know what?
I'm actually...
Well, so what I'm trying to do is I'm trying to tweak the gameplay.
So it's fun.
Yeah.
I think right now, I'm actually not sure why I care about the order.
It just seems random.
Like there's no strategy really outside of just the order of the skill.
You know what I mean?
And so if you just happen to have a crappy card, a crappy bot,
or a bot that's not very...
Didn't roll very good stats,
then it's like you almost never want to play that bot.
Yeah.
So there's no strategy of thinking about like,
oh, maybe that actually this bot could be fodder or something.
You know what I mean?
So I wonder if there's something we could develop there.
Yeah.
I mean, the other way to do this,
which I think we had also brainstormed a little bit this morning is
each of these lineups,
we could actually change the conditions that the bots are fighting in.
Like we could have...
Let's say you have what appears to be a really crappy card or a bot.
We could actually make that bot be really good in a certain circumstance.
And you can imagine a circumstance where the stats are all swapped or something.
We can create all these different arenas or something like that,
where the arenas are then where one bot might be really great,
another bot might not be as much.
That could be another way we play with this.
Yeah.
This is quite cool actually.
I don't know what you call this, like this rotation effect.
It's kind of nice.
I like that a lot.
It just makes it look cool.
Cool.
Well, I think we've made some really good progress in the last few minutes.
Adding some visuals to it really helps the design.
Start to feel more real.
I think we're going to bring on a guest actually to chat a little bit with us
and just kind of spend some time jamming on GrokBot
and how they're using GrokBot.
So what we'll probably do is take a quick two to three minute break
and kind of go off stream.
And then we'll come back with a guest and keep building in parallel.
Nice.
Yeah, we'll try to make...
Welcome back, everyone. Thanks for having spent the day with us so far.
For those who are just joining, you're joining our 72-hour livestream
where we are using Grok Bot to build a business from scratch.
We've made some really fun decisions. We've made some pivots.
Catch back up on the replay if you haven't had a chance to see this morning's content.
I'm Roshan. I work on product at SpaceX AI.
Lauren and Matt, who are also on the team, are off building,
but we really wanted to make sure we could spend some time with folks
who are using Grok Bot in really fun and interesting ways.
And so we have with us now Karen Chang. Karen, welcome.
Hi. Thanks for having me.
Yeah, thanks so much for being here.
We know you are a cursor and Grok Bot power user.
I actually have a slide on the screen here if we can show that
with some of the incredibly cool stuff you've built.
And so, you know, we have a bunch of folks watching.
You are a creative technologist and filmmaker.
You have over 3 million followers.
You're creating a bunch of just like really fun use cases
with all of these tools.
And yeah, I'm excited to just spend some time digging into all this with you,
kind of learning from how you use all the tools
and maybe sharing some tips, hopefully, for some of our viewers.
Anything you'd want to add about kind of what you work on and what you do?
Yeah, let's dive in.
I can definitely chat through some of the stuff I've built.
I've been using Grok Bot since early days and got obsessed with it pretty early on.
And I thought maybe I would test the capabilities Grok Bot.
Yeah. Grok Bot, can I get a water?
Wow. Grok Bot in the real world.
It's moved to the physical world.
This is like part of your whole thing though, right?
Like this middle custom newspaper, which maybe we'll talk about in a little bit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Very cool, very cool.
But yeah, thanks so much for being here.
Obviously, thanks so much for using Grok Bot.
The first thing I like to ask anyone when I kind of, you know,
talk to them about Grok Bot, is like, what does your team look like?
Do you have a chief of staff bot?
Do you have a bunch of bots working on different projects?
Tell us a little bit about how you set up Grok Bot for you
and how you're using it and maybe any fun bot names you've come up with?
Yeah, I have very uncreative bot names.
So I just have a bot for each task.
And so I do have the chief of staff, but I have a package tracker.
I have like a reality TV shows tracker.
Oh, I love that. Okay.
I have like 30 morning newspaper bots
because I was testing creating a template, which we can get into.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And I used cursor a lot for projects
and then now I find myself switching over to Grok Bot
because actually I'm not super technical.
And whenever I vibe code it, I would actually oftentimes feel a little dumb
because I see all this code be like,
yeah, do what you want to do, but I don't actually know what's going on.
And I love how the Grok Bot UI kind of just makes decisions for me
and almost hides what I don't need to see.
And so I can just focus on this is what I want to do.
That's awesome. And so it sounds like you're doing a lot of coding work,
but also maybe some operational stuff for your life
and maybe your business as well. Is that the right way to break out?
I would say it's stuff I'm doing personally.
And then also like weird things I'm inventing slash making.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ideas that I've been building.
And what I love is that Grok Bot connects the cursor on the back end
so it can actually code and make things.
That's awesome. And so you're spinning up cursor agents
then within Grok Bot and kind of pairing those things together
to build all your stuff. Okay.
Well, obviously you've built some incredibly cool things.
I'd love to hear a little bit about some of them.
We'll leave it to you to pick which one you'd like to talk about first.
But I know you've done a really cool project with Vesta boards
that we showed a second ago.
You have a really cool custom newspaper.
Right. Any one of those that you'd want to kind of share?
I'll start with a newspaper.
I just posted about it on Twitter last week, actually.
And so the idea is, I don't know if you want to fill up the slide.
Yeah, let's see if we can get the slide back on.
So the idea is if you look at that middle video there,
it's a newspaper that's personalized to you
that prints overnight while you sleep.
Why do this is because you can now start your day
without touching your phone. So you can grab this in the morning.
It pulls from your calendar and your email.
And then it creates this newspaper meetings,
packages arriving, weather to do.
And it turns your subscriptions and sub stacks
into a reading section.
And then it creates a comic based on your day
and a crossword with hints from your life.
I really like that.
I actually brought the one that it printed for me this morning.
Yes.
So I can show you.
Let's get a camera close up on this
so we can show everyone on the stream.
Yeah.
So this is actually a bot template
that I made that you can try.
If you go to newspaper.caronex.com,
I'll say that again, newspaper.caronex.com,
it's a bot that you can just add to your blockbot.
And then it will say your name.
It won't say my name when it prints.
What if I want to copy the Caron Times?
You can have one.
You can have only your time.
Fair, fair, fair.
But it will basically pull a summary of your day.
It'll draw an image and then summarize your day
with your meetings.
And also, I have a section for packages arriving,
which is pretty useful.
And then it has today's weather.
And then the bot will actually ask you which of your emails.
It'll actually go through email and look
at your email subscriptions and ask
you to pick which of your email subscriptions
do you want to include so you can pick your favorites.
And then it will actually show your subscriptions.
And then I did actually a bunch of testing
with laying out this newspaper.
So what it does is it says verbatim what
the person you subscribe to is.
And then it has an editor summary towards the end.
Because that way, your paper isn't like 20 pages long.
So this is the reading section.
And then my favorite part is that it draws a little comic
about you and about your day.
And you probably can't see this, but this is actually,
it turned out to be about the event,
which I didn't plan it if I just saw it this morning.
And so this is me getting the Uber code to get here,
which thanks for the voucher.
And then this is me at the cursor at the Groff bot event.
And then this is me leaving.
And then it also creates a crossword with hints
based on your life.
And so I actually, if you go through
and try the newspaper bot,
so it's at newspaper.caronext.com,
or you can find me on socials and the link is there.
It will actually draw an avatar of you.
So it will look like you.
So it has you pick your avatar
and then you can just type in an ad,
do I want glasses?
Do I want to wear a certain type of outfit
and it'll make it look like you.
That's awesome.
And so the bot prompts you when you set it up
to do all these things.
It sounds like it connects to a bunch of services.
Is that right?
Yes.
So basically, it introduces itself.
And then I actually programmed a,
so basically the way I set up this template
was I wrote like a 30 page long prompt
about how this thing should be set up.
And the first is the set of instructions,
which is the questions that it's gonna ask you.
And then the second part is all these rules
about like how to design and lay out this paper.
And the set up flow, it will ask you your name,
where you live.
And so that way it'll pull the weather
and the like events around you,
like things around town to help you get you
out of the house, hopefully.
And then it pulls from your calendar to email
to get all this stuff about your day.
And then it asks you to pick an avatar.
And then it asks you what time you wake up
in the morning.
So that way it starts working on it
like an hour beforehand.
Sort of like a newspaper alarm clock.
I sleep next to my printer now
and I kind of wake me up in the morning.
I said that from social media.
I saw that, I saw that, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So, and then I was testing it with friends
and before I released it, and my friend was testing it.
And then he was like, oh my God, it just started printing.
Because what it will do actually once you reach the end,
it sets up your, it makes your newspaper,
is it will just automatically scan
your like network for printers.
Oh wow, okay.
And then it will just print.
Very agentic.
Also there's privacy settings in it.
So by default it will keep financial figures
and like stock medical details and stuff off the page.
That's good.
But just to warn you, it will find a printer and print it.
So if you're at work, like just be aware.
Be careful, yeah.
Maybe there's like a printer setting, then the budget.
But I love how it will just find the printer
and just print it.
That is so cool.
That's right.
Printer setup is like the most notoriously hard problem
in home tech.
I mean you guys did it, you guys figured it out.
That was honestly the part I was most excited about.
Wasn't it printed?
Wasn't it just Grokbot figuring it out by itself?
You just told Grokbot, hey find a printer
and print things and it just does it?
Yes.
Wow.
Well I set up the template, which I just said like,
can you print it?
And it didn't ask me like settings.
It didn't ask me to connect anything.
It didn't ask me anything.
It just in the background saw that there was a printer
on my wifi and then it just started going.
And I was like, this is the true magic.
Right here.
A true agent in the physical world.
Maybe next we could build a water robot
that brings you water.
Yeah, so we can really tell that story too.
Wait, so this is incredible.
So it sounds like you also mentioned
prototyped a bunch of different bots
as you kind of iterated towards
what the final version of this was.
Could you walk through kind of what that prototyping
experience was?
How did that go?
Like what was great about it?
Maybe like what was so great about it?
So this newspaper is formatted really to look
like a newspaper, but I will say the first versions
of my newspaper formatting was really ugly.
I don't have like pictures of it,
but just take my word for it did not look good.
And so I would just constantly give Grokbot feedback.
And then it figured out that it needed to use
some sort of like Wheezy print skill and CSS.
And then it also picked out like all these fonts and stuff.
It just made all these great design decisions.
And then I iterated with it to get the design
the way I wanted.
And then I had it create like a template PDF
and a template CSS file.
And then basically I uploaded everything to Cloudflare.
So when your newspaper bot loads,
it pulls all the files, all the fonts,
everything from Cloudflare,
and then sets everything up for you.
That's really cool.
So your bot template, you've kind of iterated on it.
The template now comes with some connectors
that it should have that you should set up with it.
And then kind of once you install those.
But you don't have to worry about any of that.
You just literally click import bot
and then in the background it pulls all that stuff.
You don't even know that that's happening.
Awesome.
So you've kind of set it up where you're hosting
a bunch of that stuff too.
And so it's kind of helped.
Yeah, makes sense, makes sense.
Very cool.
I guess I'm curious kind of having gone through
this process with Grokbot,
obviously you've built a lot of other really cool stuff too.
How do you think about what Grokbot does
for creators, inventors like yourself?
And it sounds like a lot of this is just like
it lets you test a bunch of ideas.
Maybe it kind of brings the code a little bit closer
to the creative process.
And I personally really love that too.
It's like you can go from idea to execution much faster.
But curious, are those the things
that you're seeing the most?
What have you done for you?
It's speeding up so many ideas.
And I'm just able to build things much faster now.
And I'm able to build things that I couldn't before
just because it's crazy just how much of a difference
the UI being simple accelerates my ideas
in just the sort of like subconscious way.
And I can share an example of,
let's go back to the slide.
And if you look, the first project that I did
on the very left side is a project that I did with Cursor.
And I did this before Groffbot existed.
And so this is basically what I call
the world's dumbest smartphone.
But basically you pick up a rotary phone,
you ask a question, you hang up.
And then I have it connected to a split flap display
that will answer the question.
And again, the idea is that you can spend less time
on your phone.
As you can see, I really have a problem
with my phone addiction.
But what you'll be able to do is you ask any question
and it can look up the weather.
It can look up like my exercise classes.
It's also pulling from that.
And this took me quite some time to code in Cursor
to figure out how to connect to the APIs.
And there was just quite a lot of development involved.
And I felt like a lot of imposter syndrome
actually when I was building it.
Cause I'm not a coder, I'm not a developer
and I can use Cursor and I can ask you to do things.
But half the time it's asking me to commit to GitHub
and repose and I'm like, I don't know, can you help me?
And it will help me, it will do it.
But I am in there and I feel like an imposter.
I actually recently tried doing something,
like reproducing that thing on the left side,
that video on the left side inside Grokbot.
And I was like, hey, can you just,
I set up a package alerts tracker.
So inside Grokbot, I recommend you do this
because I'm not always good at like
knowing what packages are arriving
cause I have my packages separate
on a separate email account.
So I don't know like what's arriving.
And then I maybe miss it.
And then I'm home, but the UPS driver
doesn't ring the doorbell
and then it's on my doorstep and it gets stolen.
So I wanted a package tracker that tells me like,
this is what's arriving today.
This is what's arriving this week.
And so it will check my email like twice a day
and for like what's out for delivery.
And then it will scan and then if it's out for delivery
it starts checking more often.
And then it even logs into my Amazon account.
And once it's out for delivery,
it will send me a screenshot of the number of stops
away my Amazon driver is.
So you're truly getting like down to the minute
notifications for your package.
Yeah, but I want it flipping.
And then also it checks like for door dash.
It'll tell me like when my door dash is on the way.
So I've made this package tracker
and I've had it connected like all these different packages.
All kinds of packages like food packages
and also like mail packages and everything in between.
And then I connected it to my split flap display
which is the best for which is the thing that flips
and it's in my room.
And so whenever a package comes, it's like,
bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam,
your package is here.
Like I can't miss it.
So you never have to look at your phone.
Like everything just gets notified to you on.
For packages.
I still have to look for my phone for other things.
Fair, fair, fair.
But that was so easy to set up because in Cursor
I had to build a whole like web interface,
connect to APIs, like upload,
create a web, it was just many steps
and a lot of troubleshooting.
And then inside Grafva, I was just like,
wait, can you just connect to my best of board?
And I was like, sure, give the API key.
And I'm like, okay, so I pull up the app
which comes with the split flap display,
grab the API key, paste it in.
And then like two minutes later,
my display starts flapping and I was like,
and it didn't ask me to build anything,
commit anything, upload anything.
And so just the frictionless nature,
I'm coming up with so many more ideas now
because of that, because it's just so easy to build things.
And I feel like I don't have to code anymore.
Like the coding is invisible.
Like it's no longer vibe coding, it's just vibing.
It's vibe creating.
Maybe, maybe.
Yeah, vibe creating.
Yeah, I don't know, I'm not good at coining your terms.
I'm not pointing back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Please don't, like, yeah, please don't feature me.
One of the things that I'm finding that is really resonant
about the work that you've done
is that it has really shortened the creative process
but it feels like you also like have dug pretty deep
like in your phone project,
you're kind of like working with microcontrollers
and like doing a lot of work with hardware.
And so I'm kind of curious, like, you know,
have you used Grokbot to help with sort of learning
how to do those things?
Are you kind of like using Grokbot as an educational tool?
And then also just like,
where do you get some of that inspiration from?
Because I think there's a lot of people out there
who are like, I don't know where to get started,
or I don't know what to work on.
I'm just curious kind of how you like think of those ideas.
Right, yeah, I'm starting to use Grokbot to connect,
especially with tools that have APIs.
It's been really helpful.
Actually, the next step of my newspaper bot
is I'm going to actually take this a step further
and I actually got a robot pen that like actually plots
and draws it so it can draw like a full-sized newspaper
and that can connect with an API.
So I'm working on connecting Grokbot to like this robot pen
and so that'll be my next video.
I'm still figuring that one out.
So that's been really fun.
And yeah, I just feel like it has just been able to,
I've been honestly been really manic the last few weeks.
I haven't been sleeping as well
because I've just been, I have had all these ideas.
But in terms of where I get the ideas,
actually this came from solving problems that I had.
So last year, I had a challenge for myself
where I would not look at screens on Saturdays.
I didn't do it every Saturday,
but I would do it at least like once or twice a month.
It was very hard, but basically the ideas from like
from Friday night until Sunday morning, no phones,
no laptops, like I would watch a little bit of TV.
But no like, no devices, no devices that are connected
to the internet that could send me notifications.
And I did it because I was so burnt out
on like my phone and phone addiction
and I was feeling just really not good.
Physically not good, mentally not good.
I felt like my brain was a sponge
that held the maximum amount of water
that it could possibly hold.
And there was just no room in my brain for anything else.
So I did this thing where I would not look at my phone
for like a day a month or two days a month.
It was shockingly hard
because there's so much on your phone now.
Like everything that you need is now on your phone.
So it's much harder now to not to forego your phone
than it was 10 or 15 years ago.
It feels like you're like giving up an appendage
or like you're just losing context in the world
or something like that.
I can't like order food.
I can walk to a grocery store and cook,
which was, you know, that was a good thing for me
to learn to do.
Maybe that's also a good outcome.
Yeah, yeah.
And then I also can't just look up something.
Like sometimes I'm just curious.
I wanna know like,
well, what time does the hardware store close?
I can't look that up.
What time is the exercise class today?
I gave up so much in not using my phone.
So I had all these like problems.
And so I think you identify a problem
or a pain point that you have in your life
and then just solve it.
And so I came up with these kinds of ridiculous solutions,
which was creating, you know,
this phone that would answer questions for me
on a giant split flap display.
And the thing that would print my newspaper.
But the problem with this solved actually was I know
I'm not supposed to look at my phone
first thing in the morning.
I know that that's,
I noticed when I look at my phone on Thursday in the morning,
I'm scrolling with like one eye open.
Yeah.
I like both of my eyes haven't even opened yet.
Blue light in your eyes.
Yeah.
Like not the healthiest thing.
I'm like scrolling Instagram.
I know this is not good for me.
I'm scrolling TikTok.
This is not good for me.
And then I wake up and I start my day
and it kind of throws my whole day.
Yeah.
And then I would have days where I was like,
okay, I'm not gonna look at my phone.
I'm gonna go out in the park first thing.
And those days will always be much better.
But that would take so much discipline
because in the morning I'm like,
well, what's new?
Who needs me?
Was there an urgent email overnight?
Was there a calendar event that was moved?
Was there something I need to know?
And so I would just could not resist checking my phone
in order to get that information.
And then, but then I would see all my social media apps
and I would see all the other stuff I don't need.
So I was like, okay,
what if it could just print just the information I needed
which was how this idea for this morning
was gonna come about.
This is amazing.
Well, I'm sort of taking away from this.
For those of you who are watching
and maybe you want some ideas
of what to do with GrokBot,
I think so much of what you can do is like,
install GrokBot, give it a problem that you are facing,
whether it's wanting to curb your phone addiction
or maybe getting outside more often
or anything like that, right?
Like helping manage a crazy schedule,
helping track your packages.
I think there's so many of these sort of like daily
problems that people face.
And daily things that,
if you haven't used an AI agent tool in a little while,
you don't even know it's possible
that you could like ask an agent
to help with some of that work.
And it sounds like you really sort of like,
productize that in some ways by saying like,
hey, I'm gonna like go and figure out
all these little things where I can go
and get GrokBot to help me out.
I think that's just super awesome.
I can share a few other, I don't know how we are on time.
Yeah, I think we're gonna be more minutes.
Yeah, I can share a few other of my bots
that have been really helpful.
So one is like when my favorite t-shirt,
there's a shirt that I wanted that was out of stock
and the color that I wanted.
And I just have like a back in stock tracker
for items that are out of stock.
And so once a day, it'll go to the website
and it'll check for like the size and the color
that I want and see if it's in stock.
And then sure enough, like one day it had the alert
and it was like, it's in stock.
There's only one, I think probably
because someone returned it.
And I went and got it immediately.
You could also set it up to buy automatically.
I was going on vacation.
So I was like, don't bite on that.
I will do it.
Your package tracker.
You need to track the package.
And then my package arrives.
Yeah.
I have a shows tracker.
So I just put in like, I just tell it,
here are my favorite shows.
And it'll tell me when something is renewed for season two,
when it's going to come out that day.
Because I'm sitting down at night,
and I'm like, what am I going to watch?
And then this thing will tell me,
hey, your favorite show premieres tonight,
or it just got renewed.
And that's something that I look forward to.
Because I think you've also done a lot of proactivity.
So things that you'd otherwise have
to go seek out information for.
You kind of now have Grok Bot pushing that to you.
So you kind of just have one place.
It's kind of like a feed of all the stuff you care about,
all these things that are arriving on your doorstep,
maybe some notifications that would be over there
that you can have centralized.
So I really love that idea of kind
of putting everything in one place.
And then the thing that I really like doing
is Grok Bot can control your iMessage.
And I know you can.
OK, so this takes, I think, a little bit of settings
to set up.
You have to change some settings in order for this to happen.
But Grok Bot controls your iMessage.
So then to be able to put if-then logic on your iMessage
has been so cool.
So for example, I was ordering an item to a friend's house
that they needed.
And so I Instacarted it to their house.
And so I needed to tell them,
this is when your item's arriving.
But I wanted to go take a shower.
I didn't want to go sit and update this to my friend.
So I was like, OK, Grok Bot, I want you to check
where my Instacart driver is.
And then once it gets close, like within 10 minutes,
I want you to take a screenshot and then send that screenshot
via iMessage to my friend every two minutes.
And then my friend actually would know
where the driver was.
Because Instacart doesn't have actually the ability
to share where the driver is to someone else.
With Grok Bot, you can make it multiplayer, it sounds like.
Yeah, very cool.
So these are all really amazing.
I know we're coming a little bit up on time.
One thing, kind of just working on the Grok Bot team
that's really helpful for us to hear,
and kind of putting my product hat on,
is what feature request do you have?
What would you love to see in Grok Bot Next?
Maybe where are some areas where you might want
things to be a bit better, or some areas
where we could add new stuff?
I would love for it to be able to,
I would love for it to be able to manage logins better.
So the login stuff is super useful.
I use it, for example, to check.
I have a subscriptions canceler.
And so it checks how much money I'm spending
on my various subscriptions.
But the problem is things are always getting logged out
on the virtual machine.
But sometimes I'm logged in on my local computer.
So it would be good.
Just managing that whole life cycle better.
Yeah.
Yeah, makes sense.
That would probably be one pain point that I would love.
And it sounds like you're logging into a bunch of services.
So you're probably hitting that pretty frequently.
Yeah, yeah.
Awesome.
Well, thank you.
It's like really helpful for us to hear,
especially from a power user such as yourself.
And so maybe just to wrap us up,
first of all, thank you so much for being here.
This is incredible.
I just find it is incredible to see the creativity
of what you've built with Grok Bot.
I'm excited to see all the future projects you build.
I'm not gonna ask for too many spoilers,
but the plotter sounds amazing.
That's coming.
I might need to buy a plotter
and go make myself a full page newspaper.
So like, you know, we'll chat afterwards.
Just to wrap things up, where can people find you?
Where can people find your bots?
Yes.
And any parting thoughts you leave for the folks watching?
Okay, you can find me on social media.
It's KarenXCheng, C-H-E-N-G.
And then if you want the newspaper bot,
it's newspaper.karenx.com.
Wonderful.
Just search in Google, like Morning Bot,
Morning Newspaper Bot.
Yeah, and we should get that in the marketplace too.
I think that could be a cool one.
It is in the marketplace.
You can go to the marketplace,
and in the personal category,
you can go to the Morning Newspaper.
X.ai slash bot slash marketplace,
and there we go.
All right.
Well, thank you so much for being here.
We're gonna cut to a short break,
and then we will come back to building our three-day business
and keep the process going.
Thank you all for being here.
Okay, thank you.
Yep, we're back on.
And so that was a conversation with Karen and Sharon.
And, yeah, and honestly,
one of my favorite demos for RockBot
is Karen's internet-connected printer.
So if you haven't seen that one on X yet,
highly recommend I really want to build something
similar to myself.
And so in the meantime, during our break,
I was sharing with Lauren.
Lauren did a bunch of whiteboarding,
started to think through some ideas
and directions for the game.
Yeah, so we'll take a look at my screen real quick.
So I have TLDrawOpen,
and I was, basically, this is more for me.
I could have prompted a bot to come up with this,
but I just wanted to visualize it in my head
how it would work.
But this is kind of a rough,
like I guess a rough set of moths where...
This is cool. Yeah.
Yeah, you have like a game screen.
Yeah, the name of the game is obviously...
Cupcake.
Well, working title.
Working title.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cupcake.
And then you got like a new match screen.
And then...
This part, I'm not...
You gave a captain, yeah.
Yeah, so I was thinking like,
so you would pick a bot as your captain,
and maybe that has some implication later.
Yeah, right.
We could build on top of that.
For now, I don't know if there's any implication.
But you choose your captain,
and so that's the bot that you get to pick.
And then random one and then the two are the ones
that are up and true.
To assemble your team and kind of put the team together.
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
And then...
You can see the stats, maybe.
Yeah, so once you click and choose captain,
then you get like...
So this is like your list of bots
that you've already hired.
And you can pick which one.
And then I guess there could be like another,
like an input here that says...
Create a new one.
Or you can do it here.
But then you can also go to this team page
and then you can manage the bots you have.
And maybe for now, we'll just...
This is a very simple list of bots
you've employed before.
Yeah, I like that.
Well, they're kind of associated with your account, right?
So when you've logged in,
you kind of have a team that's...
It could be interesting to track
who minted the bot.
The original creator.
I don't know what that means.
Yeah.
It's just because it's just the person who uploaded it.
That could be a fun like easter egg to add,
maybe as a bonus feature.
Do you like the whiteboard in the browser inside Cursor?
And what is that unlock for you?
Like, can you do anything special with those?
Yeah, so the really nice thing about drawing...
So yeah, I have TLDrawOpen in Cursor's browser.
And my agent can just see it.
So you can see, I just told the agent,
hey, can you look at my browser?
I drew some mocks and it took a screenshot
and now it has context.
Oh, that's actually sick.
Very useful context to actually go off and build it.
So I have it actually,
because our original version of our prototype is kind of...
I still love this, by the way.
Like, I think this looks pretty great, but we can open it.
I mean, it doesn't look like a game.
It looks like some kind of...
Trading cards.
Maybe they look like trading cards.
But yes, I wanted to make it look more game-like.
So that was the inspiration for,
okay, how do I actually want this to look?
Because this is not the game I want to play, personally.
So, you know, very big and minimalist and fun.
I like the big sort of like, take over the screen,
really focus on the bots.
We can maybe bring some of the card CSS
that you were calling out to bear here
and have this really be simple, right?
So you see your team and then,
did you have a chance to prototype out
how you'd actually go and then...
Yeah, so once you pick your captain,
then like, let's say I picked Dr. Eggbot as my captain,
then you get to decide the order of the,
and you just drag and drop.
Cool, yeah.
Then you confirm, and then you put,
you get a matching, you get a finding match screen.
It'd be ideal if the matchmaking was so fast
that you'd never saw the screen,
but maybe it takes more than like a few seconds
to show you the screen.
Cool loading animation, maybe, for me, too.
Okay, so let's say I got matched with Maddie P,
who has Mattbot, and round one.
So unlike the prototype we saw before,
which is very text-worthy,
you just see like, you know, one bot at a time,
and it's like round one.
And I'm still kind of thinking about how this would look,
but maybe I'll get the bot to kind of,
now that I have a one basic mock,
just get the agent to actually riff on these.
And so I was just thinking like,
okay, random two-use Riz, and Mattbot used implode.
And I was toying up this idea of like,
not making it too stat-focused, if that makes sense?
Because it's like, it's not very fun to me.
Like, random two-use Riz, and that was 37 cards,
like, who cares?
So I was thinking like, maybe there's like a way
to visually show like, well,
this has two arrows of power, you know?
And so you can, it's more like, conceptual,
and implode only has like,
maybe this is just based on the stat.
Yeah, I think that could actually be fun.
It's like, we just maybe we chunk the stats
into four categories, like zero to 20,
20 to 40, 40 to 80.
Right, so we just show weak strong, whatever.
And the numbers are like behind the scenes.
The numbers are behind the scenes, yeah.
So it's for the people who really want to dig
into the numbers and like, you know, get into it,
they can, but if you're-
I mean, I don't know, I feel like the numbers-
Or maybe the numbers aren't visible.
I feel like the numbers could be hidden
from the numbers, and then you will see how that feels.
That's a good point, we can always add that later.
And maybe, yeah, it's like,
I feel like the numbers are only interesting
if you can somehow have an impact on the number.
Yeah.
So I think that maybe just show the relative strength
for now, feel like that? Yeah, I like that.
We should just take, because I think we go up to what,
150 max, 150 total staff today.
So it's probably way for us.
Yeah, so maybe like, if you're legendary,
it's like four. Yeah, you go four,
and it like, it'd be like a cool animation.
And maybe you don't even know
that your opponent bot is like, legendary.
And it gets revealed that it was-
It just gets shown when the user still has extremely power.
I really like that too,
because it sort of amps up the drama.
And I feel like that's something that keeps you really,
you know, would keep people engaged.
I would love that.
I'm like waiting with anticipation to see what happened
in each one of these, in each one of these turns.
This part definitely needs some design help, I think.
I'm not that good at coming up with designs here,
but just thinking through like,
how do we do these,
how do we make the animations look good?
You know, how do we make the,
how do we just make it not like a tech suit game,
where it's just a tech floating around everywhere?
So some like cool animation,
like a win and lose animation,
it could be interesting.
But yeah, that's what I just sketched out really quickly.
I love that.
And we have our,
oh, there you go.
We have some mocks, I guess.
Nice.
I didn't ask it for mocks,
but oh, maybe I just need to refresh.
Oh, there you go.
Cool. Okay, let's try.
Let's walk through a break.
Hold on, is this a real login?
Okay, no, this is fake.
Thank goodness.
Okay, new map.
That's a fun logo.
Okay, so I'm diamond, cool.
What is diamond?
Oh, so I had this idea.
So since we have new ranking,
yeah, I thought it'd be cool to show,
instead of, again, like,
instead of showing numbers,
it's far more, I think, engaging and interesting
when the player doesn't see the actual,
I don't know, like,
you don't have to like see the guts of how the game works.
You just wanna play the game.
You kind of, like, it's more,
instead of saying, like,
oh, my elo is one, three, seven, two,
I can say I'm diamond.
And that's like way cooler.
Yeah, like, I'm in this cool category.
Diamond, you're like bronze.
I'm totally better than you at this game.
So.
I like that.
Okay, this one doesn't really look like my mock.
Is it still working?
I like the big loss.
Oh, that's kind of,
I like the summary screen here too
that it came up with,
where we'd show all the boss in the summary screen
if you scroll down.
Oh, interesting.
I can show you the summary.
I guess maybe that's interesting
because then you can tweak your strategy.
Yeah, that is one benefit of actually,
of showing the stats
is that you could kind of then show why you lost.
So like in the actual battle,
maybe you don't know the stats,
but afterwards you're gonna get the game summary
and that would actually be really cool
to share on social for people too, I think.
Yeah.
So I wanna actually tell,
give it some feedback here.
Like, can I draw?
Maybe I'll just do the shift click.
Oh, that's not what I wanted.
And so what you're doing now
is using design mode and cursor, right?
To kind of give direct feedback on the actual prototype.
There you go, yeah.
You have shift click here.
I'll just say,
Select the whole screen.
This doesn't match my...
Just giving the agents some feedback
on what to adjust.
Three big cards
where the first card is the captain selector, I guess.
And the other two cards are...
Okay, and then that's actually,
it was just for the sake of the scene,
I'm just gonna go with the link she needs a lot.
And okay, so now we can sort the order.
Help me out.
What do you guys think?
Who should go first?
So for this one, I think let's do our...
Well, I can't see what Kirito gets.
Charisma.
I think we should put our Kirito first.
That feels like it's a guaranteed win, right?
I think it's gonna actually implement the drag.
Oh, okay.
So I think, what does this do?
Oh, that was not...
This thing is blocking my screen.
Oh, I guess...
I think it might a lot.
Did we lose your screen?
And we're back, there you go.
I think I'm gonna give feedback again and say like,
keep pressing this.
Make this draggable.
Draggable through the order.
And you can remove the reorder button at the bottom.
One thing that might be cool too
is if we wanna push some of this up to our repo.
I did push it up so you can start playing with it too.
Awesome.
Yeah, I was working on some landing page stuff
based off the design Lauren has.
So you can get...
I wanna zoom out a little bit.
So I can actually click and stuff.
Just keep it off.
Okay, then I'm gonna confirm.
Okay, finding match, check it out.
Finding a match, looking for another name player.
Okay, okay.
This is just like a demo, I still skip the lead.
Oh, this is kinda cool.
Yeah, but it happened too fast.
I think...
We need to add the animations.
Yeah, but you know what?
Maybe this is fine, we'll ship it.
Yeah.
And then we can iterate.
Exactly.
So, so Ling-Shi's engineer bot used Riz.
I don't wanna show the details here.
So I think we'll give it some feedback as well.
We'll say, don't show this card here.
Just the bot avatar.
And then let's remove the...
Let's say let's remove the...
What do you call this?
The stats, the stats maybe.
The stat line.
Mention, stat line.
Okay, and then let's go next round.
So we definitely gonna need some animations
since it's more interesting.
Yep, I can take a pass at that once we have this pushed up.
And then actually, do we even need to see the result
at this point?
I think it would be...
Well, what are you thinking?
I just think, I'm wondering is this kind of a useless button?
Why not just after this round,
we can just show after a few seconds to show...
So we go like round one.
Round two, round three, and then done.
Yeah, yeah.
And lost.
And then it'd be nice as well if I wanted to do this
where we should automatically find a new match
after five seconds if user doesn't click.
It'd also be kind of cool to see,
do we wanna show you any tier changes in this?
Like you can show diamond plus five.
Yeah, it could show that maybe this could...
For each player, you might wanna see
how they color ranking change.
Small subtitle or caption that shows the change to your elo.
Yeah, change to your elo.
But we don't wanna actually show the number.
We just wanna show your tier plus minus some number.
So we could show like potato minus five.
We could even do it where next to your handle.
Then if we just say diamond minus five,
what is that?
It's kind of hard to understand.
We could come up with an icon for it,
like arrow down and have some more severe arrows
for dropping along.
Okay, now that I'm thinking, I guess team,
some of these competitive teams do show the number.
But then it's like...
So you do know like, okay, like,
I don't know, like bronze is from 800 to 1000.
But you just talk about your scores, your tier is bronze.
Maybe one way we could do this is we could implement
the tiers as a bit of a medal.
So you have like bronze, silver, platinum,
medals that are next to your name.
But then we still show you the number.
So like a tool tip on hover basically.
Oh, I like that.
You hover over the diamond and you get the actual number.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So yeah, my bot's kind of like working through
all these feedback, all the feedback.
Cool.
And let's see, is it working?
Okay, I think I'll just refresh.
Okay, let's get new bot.
See if I can get the latest version of this run.
Are you just pushing to main?
Yeah.
Awesome.
Nice, nice.
No time for full requests.
No time for VRs.
Cool, cool, cool.
Okay, I'll just say like, when you're done,
push commit and push to main.
And I'll kick off an agent to like prototype
maybe some of those animation frameworks.
Cool.
What are you prompting?
Help me do some research on game animation framework.
So I'd be like more curious if there's like a library
or open source solution where like these things exist
and then we can like build them somehow,
maybe even using sliders.
It's like rather than like constructing ourselves.
I'm wondering maybe you think
we could take a different approach to that though.
So for like raw bot animations,
we actually use like code to drive those.
Okay, so we could just use.
So I wonder if we could actually,
I mean, I don't know if we should reuse it,
but maybe we can have code drive the animations
as well if it's like programmatic.
That's kind of what I was thinking.
I was just wondering if there's like.
I don't know if there's a framework.
That's what I'm saying.
If there's like a dev, like a game dev way.
I feel like the agent or bot could just figure it out.
We can just also have the bot like write it.
Just be like, yeah, write us a.
Might be hard though.
It feels like you need design chops.
I'll just like chat with the agent for a little bit
before I have it like build something.
So how do you do, like what is your recommendation
for that with potato mode?
Like do you, and it's like huge potato mode
and then chat with an agent before you,
like I think this is like a very good one.
Yeah, in this case, if I'm not sure if you approach,
I would kind of like keep doing prototypes.
I'll have to build some prototypes.
Tell you to do some research as well.
Look up how to do programmatic animations
with JavaScript and prototype a few examples,
small examples.
It's kind of hard because I think for the Grokbot avatar,
we actually spend a lot of time thinking about the,
like so even though they're like 2D,
but they're actually like,
like they're 3D in a 2D space in that sense,
but you can actually see like when they do like a rotation
or like a cool flip or something,
like you actually see them rotating in the eyes obviously.
Moving around, yeah.
So I think I feel like you need to prompt that somehow.
Okay.
Right, or show your agent an example.
Well do we want to keep them two dimensional
or make them three dimensional?
I don't know.
Maybe we start with 2D?
Yeah, I think two dimensional.
And then I think I'll give all this instruction.
It needs to be interesting.
Literally give it a new dimension.
Because it maybe starts simple
and then we'll try and expand there.
Yeah, I feel like 2D would get us to something faster.
And then we can revamp the graphics later.
Because the graphics are just a layer on top of the logic.
Right, exactly.
I think we should ship something.
Yeah.
Agreed.
That would be an interesting moment as well.
Like when we go from 3D to 3D,
if we go to that point,
like the next milestone.
Yeah, right.
Like having our main process.
But I think, yeah, my hope is that we can get
this prototype launched as soon as possible
and get our audience to actually play.
Chat to play.
And, oh, actually, you know what?
I forgot we need a leaderboard.
That reminds me.
But the idea is that, yeah,
the leaderboard will be like bragging rights.
Like, you know, like who's the best cupcake battler
and you can replay the game.
Oh yeah, like see the replays
and see what happened in that game.
Yeah.
Are you thinking for the leaderboard?
We just rank everyone by ELO and that's the V1?
Yeah, I think V1 would just be like,
who has the highest ELO?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I like that.
And we'll just keep it really stupid and simple.
Sounds good.
Yeah, and then we can go back and put it to tiers
and do medals and stuff later on.
So yeah, OK.
We'll just get it working first.
Cool.
Has your agent pushed up the latest changes?
Let me see.
No, it still works.
It's still doing some changes,
but I'll probably start switching to PR
since the three of us are quartering.
Yeah, let's do it.
I'm excited to start.
But I think for now, I think you can keep working
and then we'll just have your bots resolve.
Resolve all the changes.
It should be fine.
OK.
But let's see.
I need to know.
Let me just wait for it to.
Yeah, I really want to get the base in there
so I can't see it.
Mm hmm.
Now?
Let's see, it's taking screenshots.
Oh yeah, OK.
So it is working.
But I guess it hasn't.
Let me see.
Oh, there you go.
OK, OK.
So now, OK, I can see my E-low score now.
So Diamond, 12, 40.
I can choose my captain.
And oh, there you go.
I have who am I going to pick?
I'm going to pick Dr. Eggbot.
Hell yeah.
And then let's actually go Tinkerbot first.
OK, OK.
Tinkerbot says really good.
Dex. In fact, maybe Dr. Eggbot's stats are pretty bad.
I'm sorry.
So...
We might need to change that on the back end.
Actually, why not? I have a handy dandy beebug running here.
Let's make Dr. Eggbot...
Oh, I can't change the rarity, unfortunately, but can I actually...
Well, since my ability...
Oh, you know what? Let me just make my ability charisma.
There you go.
So now Dr. Eggbot has 43 charisma.
Nice. What is that?
We got a cheat.
Should we add cheats? Should we add cheat codes?
We'll say that one.
We'll have to hide the debug when we actually deploy.
We'll make an admin interface.
One thing that could be fun for the two of you to help me with is the...
Right now, I feel like the bots are kind of boring looking.
It'd be nice to have...
I guess you're working on the animations, like a better and nicer design for them.
And then for the abilities, I feel like it'd be really interesting if we used Grok Imagine
to come up with a cool icon for it.
Just to make it a little bit more visual and more fun.
And instead of just text.
I can start working on that.
Yeah, I feel like the enemy of the game design here is too much text and numbers.
Yeah, for sure.
I want to make it a little bit more visual, more fun.
I actually have a bot that I might be able to use for this.
Actually, we cut over to my screen.
I'll show you what I use.
We could reuse this.
This is before the pivot.
And this is a pattern that I like to use for Imagine.
So what I'll do is I'll chain together a couple different services.
And so here I use Imagine with FAL.
And so there's a really good FAL model by RefNet V2, which is for background removal.
And so then once I get a good style.
So you can see I was kind of prompting and in like an Airbnb like a little house kind
of cute style for like some of our designs on the storefront.
And I can combine Imagine to get the design and then a background removal model to remove
the background.
And so you get really good transparent backgrounds.
And this is something I've been using both for like icon design and every project that I have.
So what we could do is like maybe we could get some of the bots in like a PNG format here.
I guess I'm a little like torn because like how are we going to animate the bots with
a JavaScript based animation framework if they're if they're PNGs.
Right. So like I almost feel like you want them to be expressed as code.
Yeah. So we should start with code.
Maybe there's something about like you know we get we get it to build and then build 3D models.
And then we somehow render that as 2D.
Is that too complicated?
I don't think it's too complicated but then we're not really using Imagine right.
Like Imagine could be just like hero assets maybe or like stuff like that.
Imagine actually make like different states of these I guess.
Like a series of states.
Yeah. So like you know like I kind of like a sprite sheet almost.
Yeah we could probably make a sprite sheet.
That could be that would be a simple way to do like 2D animation.
Like a sprite sheet and then use that to like move over to SVGs or something.
Like I'm because I think like the animation could just be like swapping.
Swapping between the states.
Yeah. Like an angry state.
Battle state.
Yeah. Idol state happy.
Yeah I guess like my inclination is that the more we can keep it in code like the more flexibility we have with the states.
So I don't know. I'm down. I'm done.
Sure whatever.
I think yeah my sense is like let's keep the bots as code for now.
Sure.
And then only use Grog Imagine for the skills.
OK. The ability icons.
OK.
So you could have like really cool icons for like a Riz skill ability.
I like that could be like a I don't know whatever the Grog Imagine comes up with.
And I think that could be pretty interesting.
OK so what I'll do is I'll have like my chief of staff bot and I'll say like have a cupcake and talk to the image and thought and explain the repo we're working in or like our.
Explain the game mechanics and then build some cool like I don't know skills skill icons using imagine and remove the background.
These need to be on brand.
So use the existing design language.
Cool. All right.
We'll see. I'll see what imagine comes up with for that.
By the way so you created Cupcake and Dr. Eggbot.
Yeah I'm curious what what how did Dr. Eggbot make your cupcake.
I think if you click on Cupcake and and then click on the icon at the top.
Yeah. And you can see the description.
OK. The descriptions are actually pretty interesting because I don't know if this is common knowledge but essentially the descriptions almost like the.
Well some people call it like a soul or like a system prompt.
I had no idea.
But yeah it actually affects how the box works.
So a lot of times when you're this is how Dr.
Eggbot designs good boxes like it equips the bot with really good description.
You know like how what voice to use when you're talking to user.
It looks like at a time of content in here.
And I think it was like oh yeah.
Dr. Eggbot also specifies like one job so you don't have a bot that tries to do everything.
It's a specialist.
So that's pretty pretty cool how it sets that up.
I think I feel like this one is too specific.
And this is almost like a meta point here where I sometimes know this has happened with agents in general.
Like when you create a skill or a rule or anything really.
Whenever that rule or skill change comes from a problem or like something that happened in that chat session.
I find that agents tend to like to put all the details in that thing in that rule or skill.
And then it makes the skill less reusable because it's like it's over fitted to that one scenario.
And does that kind of make sense.
It was like a lot as a lot of inspiration for P-stack.
I see it came from that. You know the principal skills.
Came about from that where I saw the agent making a change.
And I was like why are you saying like this thing just was only for this PR.
Yeah. It's not a thing that's going to be.
It's like a locked into this like scale content.
Over time if you don't fix that then you just get this.
Your skill just becomes like a soup of examples that are no longer relevant.
Yeah. Distracting.
OK.
So a lot of how I like to think about these changes are how do we keep it durable.
OK. High level.
Yeah. And how do you do that. Like when you're building these agents.
Just a lot of prompting. OK.
Prompting and observing. OK.
You like you have to like click into things and read them.
That's the hard part. I guess AI produces so much text.
It's hard to read. I mean this is helpful right.
Because now I know where to look like where some of these details are coming from.
Yeah. One question. I would even say like you could tell doctor.
But hey the description you came up with for P-stack Engine is way too specific.
Can you read potato mode again and come up with like principles that Cupcake
and should follow instead of these overly specific issues.
And actually why you do that. Let me get a QR code for people to download Dr.
Eggbot if you don't have it already.
Cool. Dr. Eggbot is on it.
Yes. What is the does the label how does the label affect our bots.
I've always wondered this.
Actually I believe it doesn't right now. It's cosmetic.
But someone else can correct me on that.
Because yeah it's been changed a little bit.
I think we made it more cosmetic because the point of the label is like when you
have a lot of bots that are you know.
Well some people not everybody has like descriptive names like you do.
Like for example my bots are just all like food names.
Tater, Mash and Hashbrown.
And if you forget it's helpful to have. Yeah.
Just remember like oh right.
Tater is the engineer and Steve is the chief of staff.
OK. Yeah. I was I was always wondering that.
So it's good to know. Dr.
Eggbot is rewriting writing that the cupcake and potato.
Potato. Potato principles.
Love that. Cool.
Well I have a prototype running which is great.
Yes. Chat. It's live.
What's your bot doing. My bot.
Your agent. My agent.
So these were like the lander design prototypes.
Looks like we're having some issues.
These are running the cloud with the remote server there.
So I might have to pull them down locally.
And then I was doing some research on the animation frameworks.
So it looks like. Computer use is actually running the game.
So you can kind of see the game and testing out.
It built. I think that the older.
It might be. You might.
You might want to like hey we based on.
We based on mean get the fresh changes.
All right. So we're going to ask you to rebase on main.
Good. Good deal. Yeah.
I love that one.
So for those of you who know what what the hell is this kind of
to go. Common sickle is a agent in PSAC
whose job is to kill comments.
There's actually a story behind us.
So like it's called the kinds of code because it's like inspired
by sickle mode or sick.
You know you know the meme of the person like hearing
through the sickles. I see.
So my idea was like inspired by a fellow colleague Paul
who had created a sickle mode skill.
I made a comment sickle who gets fairly excited about the comments
and you might be wondering like who cares about comments.
And I've actually noticed that.
Lots will often or agents in general will often use comments
as like a crutch for explaining some kind of work around.
Instead of actually fixing the root cause.
And I've noticed this on like our base where.
Over time you just get like a ton of comments
and like a ton of work arounds and you know your app
just becomes very unmaintainable.
So that's the inspiration for the comments.
It goes.
Always loves when when when when it gets fun
because if you if you ever click on it you'll see it
last like yes ha ha ha yes going to delete comments.
Nice. OK so Cupcake Eng is now just this already
looks a lot cleaner number one.
So high level context on our game studio one job
owned engineering outcomes by orchestrating work
through piece stack potato mode and cloud agents
and supervising and verifying.
This is a little bit I slop so we could probably clean
clean some of these up.
Match your playbook and follow it.
This looks more aligned with some of the cupcake stuff
maybe a little bit more high level.
What do you think Lauren.
I think it looks good.
I mean it's kind of receding a bit of the potato mode stuff.
Yeah. So you're probably it's fine.
I mean this is better than what it was before.
So we can iterate.
Cool. You got the lander running locally.
I do. And I'm actually doing a quick a few quick layout
tweaks here.
Maybe cut to a Russian screen.
Yeah let's see.
Or should be what are you thinking as you make this.
Yeah. So basically what I was doing is I'm trying to go
through the prototype end to end here and get it sort
of feeling really like we could take this in like with a few
clicks or if you could think changes ship it.
And so a couple of things that are going through my head.
So I'm starting off with just kind of like running the app
locally kind of using design mode as well.
By the way team can we get Russian screen.
Yeah we could get my screen on that.
There we go. That would be great.
Cool. I want to zoom in though. Yeah.
So so time. There we go.
So yeah we have we have this working kind of like what
you're seeing on Lauren's screen earlier.
If you think I'm noticing is you know kind of going
through my like how do we start to make this a little
more polished right.
So I started out I can refresh this here.
So here we have like this sort of header looks like it
should be actually pinned to the top of the of the
menu. So I have that getting pinned to the top with an
agent working on it.
This debug menu is obviously just for us right now.
But we'll probably put it behind a feature flag at some
point or something.
And so I feel like we need to delete it.
Yeah. So I have it as a floating code for now.
So if it's a feature flag then it's like a it's like a
runtime check which means the code has to live in the
code so we'll get shipped even if it and so like a
hacker in the console could be like I'm going to
tweak the values.
That's fair.
And actually that's a good point as well for a
competitive game.
We actually want to make sure some a lot of the
game matchmaking logic and battling I guess are
it's maybe server driven.
We don't have to do that now but it's something to
think about for competitive games so that you don't
you don't have people just in the console.
Let me make my step one million.
Yeah.
And defeat your your character.
Yeah. I think it's a really good point.
I'm also adding a feature here where I want to be
able to mint a new bot which is something we
talked about.
Yeah.
And then this copy is a little bit.
Come on design mode.
Oh yeah.
We could just we just delete that.
Yeah.
Actually let's just delete this.
I agree.
Delete this.
Cool.
And then I think for these guys I like the drag.
I like the highlight but there's some like
interesting like see how the CSS kind of just
looks like that.
So I'm going to see if I can try and fix that a
little bit.
That would be hard to.
Oh I guess you could draw on it.
I could try to draw on it and say something like
when the card rotates this number stays in front
of it.
It should be maybe.
Oh I see what you mean.
It should be like attach more like attach the
card and rotate with the card.
Right.
Attached to the card rotating with it.
And then these are running as sort of multiple
multiple agents all at once which is great so I
can kind of see all these changes hopefully as
they get deployed.
And then I also think we need to improve a little
bit of how we're showing the the abilities down
here.
Like to me it's not really clear from the
screen like you see a bunch of stats and then
you see this like hustle decks and I'm not
quite sure what that means.
So maybe I mentioned multitask actually.
Yeah.
I want to like go back to that real quick.
Totally.
What is that.
Yeah.
So in cursor we have this multitask mode which is
really cool.
It basically means that we can ask the agent to
do multiple things all at once and particularly
when making design changes like I do this all
the time when I'm editing something you know
within our product where you can tag a bunch of
things that you want the agent to work on and
then actually click start multitasking which I
did a few seconds ago and we'll spin up a
separate subagent that works on each one of
these capabilities.
So what this really does is just help me
parallelize a bunch of work all at once.
And I love it for design polish things.
Yes it's like I'm in my head being like fix this
change this do that do that.
And I can just kind of get the agent to start
thinking about all at once.
So yeah I totally agree.
Actually that's something I completely forgot to
do when I was doing my changes earlier.
So I was just blocked by my one bot and doing
doing it you know.
So well this is this is now fixed but that this
is now needs to be fuller height.
I think why not.
Let's just tell the bot to kind of delete this
container.
That makes sense.
So that the everything else just overlaid like
this doesn't need a container.
Yeah I agree.
And then what's up with the cupcake logo and
what is going on there.
It almost looks like a bot that's where's our
design.
We have a design for a lot of them to I'll check
in on my and see what we may need to start
thinking of a name at some point.
Maybe it's not that important now.
It's just a code we're getting close to it.
We got some got some images are generating
according to according to my bot here.
Yeah I do have a little lander potentially if we
want to show that.
OK yeah we got a map.
There we go.
So this is so we got the cards with the shimmer
and what I've been doing here is I've just been I
went Grok 4 6 low effort fast and that's like my
favorite combination for using design mode because
then I can just like yeah kind of rip on some
of these things that I don't like.
So you know the header was like a little too
bold and close together.
We made it a little bit more sparse.
I still don't like some of this language right.
Some of this is just kind of like I'm picking
things that don't make sense to me.
I get it used prototyping language in the lander
which obviously we don't want.
But then even things like hey you know like
these were it gave me like fictional bots but I
was like oh just actually look at the bot
marketplace and then find me some better
bots that are actually on the marketplace.
So we got Dr.
Eggbot Tradbot from I believe Clairvaux
overheard a few others.
And then one thing I noticed AI does a ton is it
like take something super specific about like
what you're building and be like I'm going to
just like show this to everybody.
Like bro what is this.
Like I don't I don't want to see it on my
landing page.
So I need to think through at a higher level like
what is this game like what it why is it fun.
Why should you play it.
And I don't think that that's like some crazy
like a step.
I have a bit of a contrarian take this which is
like doing need a lander page in that.
I mean it's cool that you have one but we
already have the sign in screen.
I think I think but what you're highlighting
though is like the how it works part and like
maybe like you know I mean like there's the
screen that I had in my mock up was like you
would just you just come to the page and the
first thing you see is sign in with X.
And now that I'm thinking about it like why.
Why would you sign.
So maybe there's something about like a guide or
even a mini tutorial.
Sure.
Yeah maybe interactive tutorial.
I kind of like the lander though.
I like that there's sort of a home like you
know if we're if we're building this as like an
app there's sort of a you land somewhere and
then you kind of click in and you get into the
actual game experience.
But maybe there's other fun stuff we could add to
this over time too like you know maybe I'm
thinking just one day in terms of reducing
friction.
Yeah I want you know the play just drop into the
game.
It also makes it simpler which is better.
So yeah I just love how this looks.
It's like so I do like the cards.
It takes inspiration from this.
I think we should definitely keep this like a
little card collection here.
I mean if there's nothing else that comes away
from this.
Honestly most of the rest of this isn't.
Yeah just right now.
Like all this.
But I think the top part is like its own little
image could be cool.
We just show a cupcake all the way up to the
yellow bar.
We just keep that.
That can be a really cool.
What is that how it works.
But in our link to.
Nice.
Oh it does.
It just goes down.
Yeah.
Yeah no honestly this is my favorite part and I
love like these little but I actually quite
like the design language here.
Like I don't know what where like these look kind
of good to me.
Honestly all things considered we could tweak the
eyes a little bit.
But yeah I like this this card stack I guess.
Cool.
OK so maybe I just like keep this part and we
yeah I think we should keep the hero part of
the lander and then just like a big play
button that's just like play anything that's
where you get into the log in with X flow.
That way we at least have like a nice place
where they're not the first thing you're
seeing is just to log in.
Also it feels like you could create some
friction and that might be a good in between.
So cool.
I'm curious to watch you prompt this and kind
of learn from higher prompting.
So if you want to just quickly jump to my
screen for like a few seconds while Matt's
getting that ready.
I mentioned a QR code for Dr.
Eggbot so you can get your phones out and put
this drop out link in.
And if you have the drop out app installed it
should prompt you to open the app and let
you install Dr. Eggbot.
But yeah you can download Dr.
Eggbot and add them to your roster and get
them to take a look at your bots and improve
their prompts.
And it also does like a health check.
So nice to have.
Awesome.
And yeah you can know there are a ton of
bots out there too.
So Dr.
Eggbot is one of our fan favorites here that
we've been using this entire time.
But like a ton of really cool bots out there
too depending on your role you work on.
And yeah hopefully we need more to come there.
So positive progress on the.
I'm pushing my changes into main I'm just
checkpointing as I go.
So that way if you guys are also editing we
can we can play this but I got some of the
alignment issues fixed which I'm pretty
excited about.
We still need a logo so I'm looking to.
That design partner over here.
We're checking on and OK we got these are not
good.
So I'm asking Matt to multitask.
We're going to have to like task mode for
Matt.
Should we like take a quick second to talk
about our like how we want to split up the
work. And also I think we have maybe under
10 minutes left.
So maybe we'll think about like how we split
the rest of the work and then during the
break we can go off and work on this a little
bit more.
Yeah I think that's a good idea.
What I really want to spend some time on is
just getting like the core prototype built
end to end because what I really like to get
to is a point where we have a prototype in
Maine that we all feel kind of good about.
And then we have the scaffolding where all of
us could just go independently build
features and then just get our bots to help
reconcile the differences on them.
Yeah.
And so what I'd like to get to I think we need
to implement the auth system too.
And so I'm happy to work on that.
Or did you already.
Yeah I think what I was thinking like maybe I
could work on the auth.
OK.
And then because like I agree with you I
think it'd be really good to like maybe
just the three of us for now.
Yeah.
We'll find in and actually just fight each
other.
Yeah we should play.
And then we can actually play.
Yeah.
Because I think like play testing is a
good important part.
So I can work on the auth.
And Matt what would you like to work on?
So we got to get I think assets.
We need some assets so we can generate some
of those.
Some other fun stuff I think we would work
on there.
But maybe some design like what the actual
you're talking about like a mini tutorial.
I think that sounds fun.
So a mini tutorial and I think like the
abilities should have some cooler
icons so they're not just text.
Because right now we just have like
Riz ability.
Yeah.
That's not the most exciting thing.
Riz ability.
Yeah the ability.
Yeah kind of cleaning up that core loop.
I think that will be really cool.
Maybe we spend some time kind of like
designing that out together.
So we're really really aligned.
I also think the part where we have round
one round two round three now like if you
see on my what I'm drawing on my screen
we have this sort of we haven't fully
implemented this like the main game loop.
And so I think it'd be great if we also
spend some time on that and I can I
can take that as well.
But basically right now we just show round
one and then we kind of make you click
through the whole experience which is not
not super great.
So but it's funny every time I play
this I lose and my ELO score goes down.
So we have that part working.
Let's see.
Let's see what it is after this one.
OK.
I'm at 1258.
That's pretty good.
Oh you won.
I won this one.
As soon as you started watching I won.
I mean like the core.
This feels pretty good if I just
click click click.
You can see that the ELO is
persistent.
That's nice.
I like this.
Yeah I think the part that we'll need
to really get right is the
player feel.
Yeah.
So I think like nailing the
animations are going to be really
important because you know at the end
of the day like right now our
mechanics are not very complicated.
It's just like rock more or less
rock paper scissors with some
numbers.
I think we can add more systems
later.
Yeah.
Once we get the core within.
But it would be nice for it to
have you more visually engaging.
You know like some somehow just
show like what's happening.
Like right.
You mean in this part right where
we're seeing.
Yeah.
Because right now we're just
showing round one.
You need at least see like who
like what happened.
Yes.
Yeah.
And so I think this is where we
I really like your mock ups and
I think if we can come up with
like that that animation of how
they how they behave.
Cool.
OK.
So yeah I think we have a bunch
of things to work on.
Right.
Yeah.
I'm thinking what about some.
So we've been talking a lot about
the game.
Yeah.
What about all the other parts
of running the business.
All the other parts.
Should we also kick off some
bots before the break.
Yeah we could.
To work on like you know like
GTM things.
Yes business things.
So the only thing we were
talking about were ads.
Yeah.
We're not a type of thing about
running some ads.
I know.
So I know me.
So things like maybe because
right now like the bots are just
battling in like an outer space.
But it'd be interesting if
there was like a stadium.
Yeah selling ads right.
Yeah.
And then you have like little
banners or something.
Yeah.
So maybe I'm intrusive not not
not obnoxious.
I'm sort of like ad marketplace
maybe.
So like where people can bid
perhaps and then we like figure
out a way to mock like have us
moderate the companies that are
like applying to have a
like that.
How are we going to get the
companies.
I mean we got a stream right.
Hopefully we have some
we have some friends
for to give us some ad ad money.
OK cool.
Yeah no I can take that.
We can start thinking about like
the stadium and how we're going
to get ads there.
I also want to start thinking
about the game server.
Like what I was mentioning you
know not allowing people to cheat.
I don't know if we need to
bullet right now but I'm
starting to think about it.
And then doing handling off.
Like I can take those pieces.
Nice.
Cool.
So we got a lot of stuff going
on.
Yeah I'm just doing a little bit
of cleanup of our navbar a
little bit.
So yeah this logout button
which I think is good.
It looks like my agent is
taking over.
This is really cool too where I
can tell the agent to make some
changes and then in cursor it
sort of takes control.
You can see that it's asking
me if I want to take control
here.
But the way the agent verifies
this output is it just runs
itself through the entire
loop.
And so you know if you're
building or prototyping things
this is really powerful like
agents do a lot better when
they can verify their output.
And then earlier we showed you
right.
I talked about multitasking.
Now I can show it to you so
you can see that I have a cued
prompt here to add a badge to
our tier system so that
platinum diamond et cetera come
with a little bit of color.
And so I can just hit this
button to say start
multitasking.
And then you know the
cursor agents will
automatically jump in and
we'll start kind of building
multiple tasks in parallel.
I could also just send the
prompt now if I wanted to
interrupt the agent and kind
of steer it.
And so those are both options
kind of pick whatever one makes
sense.
Cool cool cool.
So it looks like we're working
there.
I still think this captain flow
is not perfect.
Yeah.
Well why the number
got fixed.
Oh yeah that's like that.
Yeah.
We need to fix this one too.
I'm also wondering about like I
guess maybe we can start
iterating a bit on the
mechanics.
Do you think like the random
bot thing makes sense.
Yeah our initial idea was
because I assemble a team right.
No because it just occurred to
me like we have a reroll team
button.
Yeah.
Like why wouldn't I just spam
that button until I got three
legendary.
I think I think we should get
rid of that feature.
Like no rerolls.
I think once you assemble your
team it's your team and you
kind of write.
What if like in this screen we
just didn't show which which
bots you got.
Oh so it's blind.
It's almost like you pick your
captain and you do blind bots.
OK that could work.
Yeah.
And then you can reroll I
suppose.
Yeah.
And drag and drop.
Yeah I'm going to just also do
some visual tweaks there.
And what were we saying.
So for reroll maybe we.
I think we should just get rid
of the.
Oh no maybe.
Yeah I think we can keep the
reroll button but make the
make these bots the non
players like the bots hidden
first.
And I think we only have about
two minutes left.
So let's quickly wrap up and
talk about what we'll do next.
Cool.
We fire off this last prompt
happening multitasking is
happening.
We have we're pushing directly
to Maine for those who are just
joining where a game studio
building a game along a three
day journey of which I think
we're halfway through it's a
bit scary to get something
into production.
We have a bunch of design and
asset work going.
We have a core game loop
that we're pretty excited
about.
A fun way to bring in some
rock bots and we're hanging
out in San Francisco for
three days.
There you go.
Rock bot galaxy right next to
Dreamforce as well.
And so a lot of really fun
conversations coming up
including one just in a few
minutes on rock bot for
sales.
But I think a couple of things
we're going to work on off
stream.
We're going to keep cooking
on some design work in the
lander that we really liked.
We're going to improve the
core game loop.
We're going to add
authentication to our service
so we can put out into the
wild and we'll do a bunch
of play testing and we'll be
back in 45 minutes to an
hour or so and hopefully show
you guys a bunch of
progress.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
All right.
With that, let's take over to
the main stage for rock
bot for sales.
Hi everyone, thanks so much for joining today's workshop on Grok Bot for Sales.
My name's Christa Lutz. I'm on the Go to Market team here at SpaceX AI.
And I'm Mark Wright on the same Go to Market team at SpaceX AI.
And excited to share with you Grok Bot for Sales, something near and dear to all of our hearts here.
Getting into it, we'll talk about the agenda.
We're going to be introducing Grok Bot or reintroducing to some of you here today why Grok Bot specifically for Sales and in the marketplace.
Some sales use cases and Christa will take us through how she's using it and demo it.
And then what we learned, we'll have time for Q&A and then hands on session together as well.
All right. A little bit about the AI maturity curve and where Grok Bot fits in today.
I think as you all know, it's evolving very rapidly.
Just a couple of years ago, we were simply using chat to ask and get feedback, you know, ask a question, get a response,
and then quickly evolve into a task based where I'd say maybe clean up my my files on my computer and then come back and ask for the next direction.
But now we're really doing bots and agents delegating full tasks or work streams.
And so now you can simply say things like build me pipeline, get me a meeting with X company, and it'll simply go do that.
And we really believe the future of where Grok Bot and this is going is having more of a staff function.
So having a team of bots that focus on a specific set of opportunities and tasks and then having them work together to essentially solve what you're looking for.
So if you win the sales function as well, incomes Grok Bot. Hopefully it's not the first time you've seen this, but excited to share it with you.
One thing you'll notice rather quickly looks very simple.
Looks like I message easy to message and chat with and and figure out what to do.
You can create bots for different jobs.
That's highly recommended.
Whatever their specialty is, you should create them.
And the memory aspect of these bots are really incredible.
So things you were told to it at the very beginning.
One recommendation is always to tell a lot about yourself, your functionality, log in the same way you would in different applications so that I can then start to take over a lot of the work, the mundane work that you have been doing repetitively for days on end.
And get it to go out and start to accomplish some of those.
One thing we'll get into as well as setting up automations and routines and skills, ensuring that they can simply take this work when you're not there and effectively work on your behalf as well.
And then lastly, you can easily share bots and templates across to each other.
It's actually something that we saw internally at SpaceX AI.
Krista has been a power user for some time, and she's actually shared out templates the rest of the team so we can effectively get moving on Grokbot much faster as well.
Why Grokbot? As we know, there's a lot of different things in the marketplace, but Grokbot is really taking the world by storm at the moment.
And here's a few things why that's the case.
I mentioned we're meeting people where they are.
Everyone knows how to type an iMessage, and so we make Grokbot feel much the same functionality as such as well.
So you can simply just type away and go from there.
No longer do you need to keep your laptop just a little bit open and keep it on for the bots to work.
It has its own computer, its own VM working 24-7 when you're not able to work.
It uses the tools just like you do.
So it has access to what you as a user would have access to and be able to go do that work.
And as mentioned at the beginning, no longer do you have to really handhold it.
The future is now sharing an objective, something that needs to be accomplished.
Whether it's generate the pipeline and or going through and getting a meeting with a company, it's going to go out and figure out the best way to do that.
And then you can obviously share the work to move more quickly.
All right, the exciting part.
What are some real life example use cases that we're seeing today in
We'll talk through a little bit how we're using Grokbot to do so rather than spending all your time looking through identifying the right contacts and sending out.
We as sales folks get a lot of questions that are really engineering specific and sometimes we can't always answer those.
And the key here is not to always have to bug your sales engineer or engineering partner.
Now Grokbot can actually have that knowledge so that you can just simply bug your Grokbot in this instance.
Echo is one really exciting one.
I think Chris will take us through and it's how to really live understand the call and be able to offer in some of those insights within it.
Chief of Staff is one you guys probably all seen kind of having a starting point and working through your bots from there.
And then lastly, like forecasting.
We all have to do it.
It's all used to be a manual process.
And now with Grokbot in your systems, you can simply one click or have it automated as a routine to move forward from there.
So with that, Chris, I'll turn it over to you to introduce us to your team.
Yeah. So before a demo, I wanted to introduce you to my team of bots.
So first I have Olive.
I like that you can customize this agent.
So Olive is my dog.
She kind of handles my day to day.
P.G. is outbound prospecting, as you mentioned.
Pipeline is key.
Echo is one I created that was really popular where I want to ensure that I leave a discovery call with something like around next steps,
you know, discuss the actual use cases the customer discussed with me.
So you can easily update a deck just by stopping a granola recording and we'll update those slides based on what the customer said during the meeting.
And then just like a customer expert, I work with a few strategic customers.
So it helps me stay on top of usage before renewals, any product signals if they're trying a new product within SpaceX.
I can track slack threads.
I'm sure everyone's slacks are very noisy lately.
So it can track any key items related to the customer.
Something I really love is like I have a lot of feature requests that customers raise.
So when we ship our change log, it can actually pull up a feature request that the customer asked for maybe a month ago that I would have forgotten about and be like, hey, we just shipped this change log.
Reach out to this customer who asked for this feature kind of feels like we built a feature request for them.
And then the engineers you mentioned, I like to think my bots like how I would work with colleagues.
So if I would slack an engineer or maybe slack a BDR for something now, you can have bots that go and handle this work on their own.
So I can share a quick demo.
Let me share my screen.
As I mentioned, I have my team of bots here.
All of is my chief of staff.
So she can prep me for my meetings in the morning.
So if you're on the bus, the office, I feel like for me, that's like my most anxiety prone time is like when I'm not at my laptop.
But I still need to get work done.
I have like slack and email is flowing in.
So I can prep me for my day, prep me for my 9 a.m. meetings and then also like reply to emails for me.
So you can see that just has this email card.
Maybe I got a note from a customer who was asking for a one pager.
It will go ahead and draft that for me.
I can make any changes here and then just send the email or discard or change it.
So that's my chief of staff.
They also have routines.
So you can run like a morning inbox scan.
You can run this like a couple of times a day.
I think a tip for usage as well to ensure you're using using your tokens in a responsible manner is I actually run less routines.
I usually like run a routine once or twice a day.
Otherwise, I find it really noisy.
But I'll set up routines for my chief of staff to let me know anything coming through my inbox.
I had echo that we talked about earlier.
So you can see I had a couple of calls today.
These are demo notes, but it can it can actually update these slides based on what calls I had.
I can even ask it like, hey, can you translate this slide to Japanese?
I work with a lot of international customers, so it's nice to be able to translate slides on the fly.
So it'll go off and work on this next.
I have P.G., which I think is top of mind for anyone in sales.
So you can have your P.G. agent.
What I have do is it will based on my P.G. skill, which is available in the marketplace.
You can run a agent to go and pick five accounts in your book.
It will pull that from Salesforce.
It might look at intent data, like what are the best fits, or you can actually give it
those accounts to run.
So you can do five accounts, you can do 100 accounts.
I do five, and then I have it pick five contacts.
And instead of just like basic company data, like, hey, your company raised funding,
they're probably getting the same outreach from 1,000 companies right now.
I like that it will pull personal hooks.
So say the CTO posted on X about building a software factory with his team, or the CEO
posted about a new product they're launching.
You can have it actually pull those personal hooks and then shape messaging not only the
company but the person.
What I found with other AI tools is it would pull out of data or just things that weren't
personally appealing.
Everyone has AI now, everyone can see basic company events but pulling actual social data
I think is really important.
So I would highly recommend connecting with the X API.
I always talk about this, but I think X is where a lot of leaders and companies post.
You probably saw the Apple CEO just joined X.
So it's a great way to stay on top of recent company news and just connect with all of
your executives at the account.
So it will create the sheet filled with personal hooks, intent data like company growth, maybe
job openings, anything that you would like it to pull essentially.
It can rank contacts by who they recommend that you reach out to.
It pulled some podcasts and webinars.
And your agent can actually watch these podcasts and webinars.
So I think before I had graph bot, I would try to listen to a few webinars or podcasts
on my way to the office.
But it wasn't scalable to listen to a 45 minute webinar and try to find a hook or blurb where
the CTO or CEO, whoever you are working with, mentioned something that would be relevant
for what you are trying to partner with them on.
So it can watch these webinars and pull out actual quotes or things that relate to how
your business would help them and then put together messaging.
And then you can draft it in your Gmail.
You can have it create a card like this and edit them.
And something I do before I send all of this is I have graph bot scan your Gmail, your
Slack or even your X.
Give it writing that you are proud of and it will know your writing style and know your
voice.
I am very picky that things sound like me when I write.
I don't like the generic LLM type style writing.
So I think to like de-slop that a little bit is to make sure that it understands your writing
style.
So that's my PG bot.
I booked a lot more meetings with executive buyers just because I really understand the
things that are important to them based on what they posted about.
I don't know, does anyone enjoy updating Salesforce next steps or pipeline?
Probably not.
Oh, you do.
Okay.
I have one person who enjoys updating Salesforce.
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, perfect.
So this is like one of my favorite things because it will actually listen to my granola
in Gong calls and it will pull out relevant context to update next steps.
I even gave it like the format I wanted like my initials, the date, customer outcomes,
what are next steps and you can give it the format and then it will pull those details
from your emails, from your Slack, from your granola, from your Gong and update those
for you and then you can like review it and then push the Salesforce, which is really
powerful.
I talked about this a little bit earlier, but I have a few strategic customers.
So my job is to really know these customers in and out.
A lot of times I work across different departments.
I have multiple Slack channels, maybe internal channels, external channels, maybe they're
emailing me or other members of my team.
So I work with Notion as my database for my customer expert.
So after every call, it will update Notion on the account plan, any signals, maybe I
have a renewal coming up, who are the stakeholders I need to reach out to, what were the calls
we've had, what projects are we working on.
So it'll automatically update this account plan in Notion.
It will kind of detail the next steps.
I can pull any usage data here.
For this example, I asked for like what the top 20 power users are.
So my team and I can reach out, get their feedback prior to the renewal, or maybe we're
shipping like a new feature that they'd like to try out.
You can see that there was like a customer question and a Slack channel.
So it'll kind of ping me when things are top of mind or I need action on things.
So I found that really valuable, just spending more time with customers, not spending time
like searching through Notion, asking an engineer a question.
And on that note, I have an engineer, it's connected to the code base.
So when I'm live on a call, instead of needing to get back to somebody, I can just ask a
question live on a call.
One example is we work with customers to set up cloud agents a lot.
So I could ask like, hey, can you send me a customer facing answer on how to set up
cloud agents?
So send me a few outcomes that amplitude and fare achieved.
So like maybe for this question, I would have had to like talk to an engineer or bring an
engineer on the call to help walk the customer through setting up cloud agents.
And then maybe I would have had to like talk to the amplitude and fare account managers and
understand like how they're leveraging cloud agents or talk to those customers myself.
But it'll pull that customer or that response from a code base.
A lot of times I paste this in Slack, so it kind of already knows how I work and
like shares with me like a paste ready version I can share.
But it gives me all the steps to set up cloud agents.
And then it also shows customer outcomes, like how have we worked with other
customers to set up cloud agents and what are the outcomes achieved?
So I use this a lot.
And then just like pulling content.
I think like the most powerful thing for me is just like actually watching content
and doing things.
I like to think of Grokbot like not just like as a good thinking partner or
like a research partner, actually a doing partner.
So I could have it, you know, watch a customer webinar with a CEO.
Be like, okay, based on this webinar, draft me an outreach messaging or
put together messaging for my CEO to reach out to the CEO instead of a meeting to
talk about their three key objectives and how it relates to what we can do for
their business.
So when I first started working with Grokbot, I think I mistakenly started using
it as I would like a chat interface.
So I was like, hey, go and do this research.
And then it actually gave me the links to go and watch these webinars myself.
But I kind of pushed back, I was like, hey, no, go watch those webinars for
me and draft an email for me.
So I think you have to change your mindset with how you work with these.
Like, think of them like colleagues who have their own computers,
they can work overnight and they can do these things for you.
So a lot of times when I'm prospecting, I will just have my prospecting bot
work overnight on like a very long list.
And then just have all the emails ready to go for me in the morning.
And then I think every day I like to add like, you know, 20% more.
But like, okay, well, you drafted these email responses, that's great.
We'll go in and draft like LinkedIn responses or
go find 10 other people to reach out to.
So you're gonna build upon your bots as you continue to use them.
I also use GrackBot a lot for travel and expense.
I'm sure we all do.
Also expenses are not fun, so you can find like Starlink flights,
which is helpful.
And then I use XBot a ton, so this is connected to the XAPI.
As I mentioned, like I found just like LinkedIn is a pretty out of date with
company information, and you can kind of dig and find like who you can reach out to.
And then I also just like learn it, like use GrackBot for learning.
So if you're like researching like a new topic, like one I like to like think about
is like SpaceX, or maybe it's like learning about or like a topic like I want to
research new restaurants or something.
But you can just like pull up a new chat and research restaurants to reach out to.
But yeah, these are all my favorite things.
You can ask it to be like, hey, can you watch the most recent webinar with Roman around
GrackBot on Lenny's podcast?
Yeah, I think we have a lot of GrackBots actually watching this as well.
Yes, yeah, there's probably GrackBots live.
So it'll go off and watch any live GrackBot webinars.
Yeah, and Krista, I want to hit on one thing on the engineer piece, the engineer one.
This has been impactful for me as well in terms of like speeding up my deals.
How many times have we all been there where it's like, oh yeah, let me find the answer and get back to you.
But now with the engineer bot, we've been able to like quickly get those answers,
answer them on the call and really speed up the next steps in an opportunity.
And that one I highly recommend is really impactful for us and the organization as well.
Perfect. I think that's all I had planned for today.
Happy to go through any questions, happy to go through any demo items, but would love to chat more.
We'll kind of finish up with what we've learned today and then we'll open up for questions at the end.
Sure. You want to switch back there?
Great. So a few tips and tricks, kind of what we learned today, looking at that as well as overall.
The biggest thing we talk about with our customers is really connect your stack,
like look at what you use in your day to day operations and get those connected directly in GrackBot.
That's really going to help you speed up the time to value here.
And it's really impactful in terms of getting those aha moments early and starting to really work within GrackBot.
One thing we've talked about, too, whether you use like a chief of staff to delegate down or by GrackBot,
you know, have one bot with one job like this is your focus.
And Chris showed a great example like we have engineer, we have pipeline generation,
travel expense, have them be an expert in that field.
These are your team members that you're onboarding.
Have them be an expert and give them all the relevant information materials to be great at that at that job.
And then another one is work on the routine.
Some people use them more regularly and people don't.
I frankly like the automations and routines.
Can I run for pay like set it and forget it, have it do the work and come back to me with anything necessary.
And that's a good way to make sure that it's always working and doing the tasks needed.
So three tips to take you forward on your GrackBot journey after this.
But it would be great to open up the for any questions you may have for Chris and myself. Sure.
I think it depends how you're using it.
Like there's ways to reduce your amount of usage, which is like running less routines a day.
I think we had one example where someone actually put routine for every 15 minutes.
So those are like ways to reduce your usage.
I personally don't use routines a lot because I find them too noisy.
So I just run them once or twice a day.
And I think another way to save on token consumption is I personally like work with my specialized bots.
And I feel like if I use my chief of staff, we I didn't show this today, but your chief of staff can orchestrate other bots.
So I've been working on a deck.
It'll call like the deck designer or maybe working with a customer.
It'll call that like customer bot and pull the account data.
I personally like to work with my specialized bots.
And I found that reduces tokens as well.
But it's highly personalized to what use cases you're leveraging.
Another tip is I use computer use if like there's not a good MCP available.
I think like most of us work in sales.
And I've just found like a lot of the sales tools we have don't have great MCPs.
But I would save the computer use for if there isn't an MCP available already.
Thankfully, we shipped a lot of MCPs out of the box.
Like I think we shipped a gong, granola, sales force and more.
So use the MCPs when you can and save computer use for when you need it.
Great point just to add, like I'm probably the opposite where I'm like you have staff routines.
So perhaps my my my spend is it's certainly higher.
But one thing I make sure to do is like ask rock for optimization tips.
Right. It's a great way to go there and say, like, look, like figure out a way to go to optimize some of our workflows here.
And what's the best way to save money?
The fact that we leverage first party models and a lot of these things really helps reduce that cost anyway.
Thanks. You hear me. Yeah.
What do you think is a good hack in order to maintain a really good knowledge space like connected to notion granola?
Ask to the load of CDN and manage of CDN account.
Or I mean, what it will be a good hack if you get bigger and bigger knowledge space.
Yeah, I could start that. I mean, I think I think if I understand correctly, like we meet where you are.
Right. Like what are you using internally within your company and where is that knowledge sits?
That's typically the best way to be able to quickly get access and start to work through these things quickly for us.
I feel like everything lives in notion and slack.
And so connecting those two has been really the the unlock for our company in order to like hack, if you will, way to move quickly.
Obviously, we use Salesforce. So Salesforce has been like a like a source of truth.
But I think I see Grokbat as like an orchestration layer of all those tools.
So whenever I need data, like I can pull it from Grokbat.
So whether it needs to go to Databricks or Salesforce or notion or slack, I don't think anyone,
any company is good at maintaining data and having it in one place.
Usually, at least before I had Grokbat, it was like, oh, great, you want this data?
Like go to Databricks. Oh, you want this data?
Go to Salesforce or this is a notion or no, someone just posted in Slack the other day.
So it's so it's like really impossible, I think, especially for a very slack heavy companies to stay on top of where data lives or when something changed.
So I think Grokbat is like a really great outer layer of pulling that information wherever it lives,
whether it's notion or Salesforce, Slack or anything.
Delegate task to cursor or get to tell it to, hey, this is what I want and then go build with cursor.
Yeah, you can tell Grokbat to spin off cloud agents.
So you would just have your cursor account connected.
But if you're like, hey, go spin off cloud agents and cursor, you would just tell the bot to do it in natural language.
Great, thank you. We got one question from X.
There's some confusion on when to use a specialist bot.
So the question is, would you set up a bot for a major client or would you create an expert that handles all of your client?
I think this is preference. I think I even asked my Grokbat the other day.
I was about to spin up a new bot and I was like, hey, like should I keep these bots separate or should I move it all to one space?
So I personally have bots for each of my strategic customers, but I only work across a couple where I know other AEs, other companies or even at SpaceX AI work across hundreds of customers.
So I think it's preference. But what would you recommend?
Yeah, absolutely preference there. And the way I do it is somewhat similar, but different,
where I've got bots that are delegated to these customers, which is looking at their intent,
kind of taking the notes from our previous calls and able to kind of feed into there.
And then I've got my chief staff that kind of directs them on what to do.
And then I've got the intent one that's actually just looking at all things Grokbat and building demos for me in my behalf on the Grokbat.
So that any call I get into, I can quickly spin up a demo and go from there.
One of those things where it's like once you get started with Grokbat, you can kind of figure out the best way to do so.
And I think X is the best way to find those quick wins as well.
There seem to be some pre-packaged skills already, right?
So if we download these, can you customize them for your use case and edit those as well?
Yeah, one, we already have some sales use cases on our Grokbat like template marketplace, but you can also create your own.
So if you want to share your own templates with your team or you've done on X,
like I think everyone in this room probably has a good template you can steal or share.
But there's some on the back of the cards if you're in the room with us.
And we also have a marketplace online.
I also have an X account, so I like to share mine.
But yeah, you can steal others templates.
And I think that's what makes Grokbat like so fun and easy to get started is you can steal what somebody has already built and customize it for your own use cases.
And the product team from the sales organization, is it via Slack or there is a better way to do that from Grokbat?
Like how do I communicate with other departments?
To other organizations, sales is talking to marketing all the time, products all the time or like, you know, so what is the best way?
Right now we do it, of course, through Slack, but is there a better way to do that communication?
Yeah, right now I do that via Slack, but you can also use Grokbat to track channels.
So if you're in a marketing channel, maybe about this event and you want to track what's going on, you can keep track of that or that event like within Grokbat.
So we've been talking a lot about personalized setups, your preferences versus yours.
How would we set this up for or do you work on setting it up for a team where you kind of had somebody else in sales?
Here's your kind of standardized setup and then personalized from there.
Is there a good way to do that for a company?
There's some best practices out there.
Certainly like today we are working with customers on like how they want to set this up.
The starting point has really been everyone get Grokbat and start to build it for yourself.
So very, very good point there.
What we are seeing in terms of a change is like now when you get into Grokbat, it's going to ask you about your role and maybe pre-give you a change.
I'll give you some of these templates that make the most sense for you.
Some of the more advanced companies though are like leveraging a power user that's done really well like Kristin, this is that has templates and then kind of sharing those out for as a sales rep at your company.
I'm going to get these five bots populated into my instance and then be able to.
Run from there, and if I'm in marketing, perhaps I get another five.
So, possibly it's really endless there, and that's been a big shift we've seen more
recently of having this pre-enabled based on your role or persona in the company.
So is that set up through your cursor account,
where you start setting that up on the enterprise level, or?
Yeah, directly through Grok Bot, you can kind of build these up and
then share them to new users, right?
So, a little bit like, let's build them out, and
then a new user will just share them over so they have them day one.
Are you able to demo the echo bot on how, during call, right?
Somehow you have some streaming capability to stream the transcript to the bot
itself so that you can understand context to update the slides or something.
This is not the echo bot that you have.
So how do you, how do I stream?
The echo bot.
Echo bot, okay, yeah.
So I use granola, so I'll do discovery,
usually like most of the call, and I just like stop the echo bot, or stop granola.
And I run echo, and it'll just pull the granola or
transcript automatically and just like start working on the slides.
So granola is like very quick.
I also use gong too, so if you use gong, I would say use gong because it takes
a couple minutes for it to load after the call finishes.
So that's probably more for like the next call or to send out after the call.
But you can run granola during the call, stop it, and
then just run the echo bot, and it'll live update during the call.
It, I think it takes me two minutes, so maybe give yourself two minutes, and
then it'll update.
Got it, thank you.
Yep, perfect.
I think we're gonna wrap up here, but lastly, thanks for all the questions.
Before we jump into building, I wanted to announce that we just launched
an exclusive challenge on X.
So you can share a Grokbot, we talked about templates a lot.
You can share one of your Grokbots that you can't live without and
how you use Grokbot for work.
And you and a plus one could head to Starbase and
actually get the chance to watch a Starship launch in person.
I'm very jealous, I would love to watch a Starship launch.
So to enter, you can follow at Grok and at bot on X.
And then quote our challenge post on X with a description of your Grokbot and
a link to your shared bot template.
And you can scan the QR card here and save the X post.
You'll need to quote to enter the challenge.
So best of luck.
Great.
Perfect, thank you all.
We're back and while Lauren and
Roshan are off getting some work done, I am joined by another Matt.
One of my favorite Matt's, Matthew Berman, who can maybe tell us a little bit
about himself and we're gonna go into how he's Grokbot,
some of what he's seeing in AI.
But first I'll let him introduce himself.
Sure, everybody, I'm Matt Berman.
I make content for a living now, which is still wild to say out loud.
Yeah, all about artificial intelligence.
I do everything from model reviews, breakdown news,
sometimes geopolitics, research papers, sometimes tutorials.
But everything is generally artificial intelligence and
been doing it for about three years.
Before that, I've been in technology for about 20.
Nice, amazing.
And while you're, number one, a friend of the Grokbot team,
we've hosted pop ups with you, we've done a lot of collaborations.
Also just a really great content creator and
I take some inspiration from your work.
We've been friends for a while.
I remember you're talking about moving up to the Bay Area,
now you're in the Bay Area.
I see you around all the time, it's great.
Yeah.
How are, I guess we could start with,
how are some of the ways you're creating content changing with AI?
And then we can tie that into some other things.
But I think it's a good place to start, yeah.
This was kind of an interesting learning over the past especially year.
I tell a lot of people, don't use AI for the actual creative process.
When you're coming up with the ideas and deciding what to make, and
you really actually have to invest the time and be creative.
But especially in the last few weeks,
we have figured out how to increase our productivity substantially,
simply by doing things like, I mean, my team has been incredible, Brian and
Alex with editing videos using AI.
And prior to three weeks ago, it wasn't even possible, it seems.
But then all of a sudden they're dictating and
they can do multiple edits in parallel.
And it's really great.
Obviously, we're doing a lot of behind the scenes automation with AI.
So everything from like sponsor management to taking notes for
us during meetings, follow ups, proposals, everything, kind of the back office stuff.
That is easy to automate, you should automate it.
The new stuff that we're getting into with video editing is what's most exciting to
me right now.
Cool, and yeah, it sounds like you're kind of trying to automate backhouse stuff,
trying to eliminate the managerial, more just like tedium from your day.
And then using that to spend more time focusing on the creative side, right?
Yeah, I think that's where humans are gonna be.
More and more in value is going to go to that kind of, how creative can you be?
How well can you craft an interesting story, a compelling story for
other people?
That skill set is going to increase in value over time.
So I'm super excited about that.
I mean, I'm excited about it too, because yeah, I just love creating things.
And so it's exciting to think, okay, well,
I'm gonna be able to spend more time doing what I love.
And so seeing that in your creative team and your creative process,
how are you using like RockBot and some of these things?
Or maybe for your personal life,
I'd just love to hear how you've used tools like RockBot,
and we're done.
Yeah, so Matt and I were talking right before this.
I actually wanna pull up some of the RockBots I'm using,
cuz I wanted to talk to you about it.
Okay, so the one I've been using probably the most is the FamilyBot.
And so I set up this bot, and it reads all of the emails.
And I have two kids, they go to different schools right now.
They have multiple sports, multiple after school activities.
And I get, I don't know why every single teacher,
every single coach decides to send a three-page email every other day.
So I'm getting these things so often.
And of course, I have a million other emails to get there.
So I have my RockBot reading every single email,
making sure, hey, it's family-related, one of the kids.
It'll summarize it for me in one to two sentences.
It'll actually recommend when I have to take action, rather than just like,
hey, here's something you have to know.
It's like, hey, you need to tell the coach if you can show up to this event or not.
That's been incredibly helpful.
Then I have it connected to my calendar with my wife.
We have a special family calendar.
It automatically puts the events on our calendar.
It will notify us if there are any conflicts.
It'll help us solve it.
I know it's very specific to being a parent, but
I can't tell you how much time this single bot alone has saved me.
Well, if you take a step back, these are the problems everybody faces,
which is you have two calendars and you need to manage multiple information sources.
And the glue that holds all of those things together traditionally has been a human.
I would be trying to do that.
You make mistakes and it's really painful, because you have to read a three-page email.
And I think before RockBot, what that looked like is, all right, a script and
have AI parse the things, and then you're creating service accounts and
doing all this weird stuff.
So what did it allow for me, and it sounds like for you as well, is like,
oh, I can just stick all these things together really quickly and
then drop an agent on top of it.
And it turns out there's a really powerful interface.
Yeah, I think there's actually also a meta aspect to it, which is,
once you connect one of these things, whether it's your calendar or your email,
you don't necessarily have to do it again.
RockBot kind of already knows where to look.
Yeah.
And I think that's really the power of it,
where it would just make assumptions about the way that I want things done.
Just so, it saw an email and it knew I had this other event at the same time,
and it knew I had a preference for not taking meetings in the morning.
And it just kind of learns these things over time.
And I'm not having to re-explain myself over and over again,
which is super helpful.
So it sounds like maybe some skills or memories or something that's like
remembering your preferences essentially.
Yeah, I mean, all of this stuff kind of was inspired by,
I think, originally OpenCloud.
When we first saw OpenCloud, it was incredible.
But I think what really stood out for RockBot in particular
is all of the difficulties of having to manage and fix and maintain
a lot of the kind of initial AI assistance software that was out there.
It's all gone.
It just works.
And I think that's been a really nice thing.
I give my wife access.
We have a shared telegram.
So now she has access to certain bots of mine.
And she doesn't have to think about, OK, what's a bot?
What memory does it have?
She just interacts with it as if it were an AI assistant.
That's super cool to hear.
It's cool to hear that your family is using these tools as well,
because I think we're still a ways away from mainstream adoption.
Yeah, I agree.
And many people watching this might not even know what RockBot is.
And so to kind of ground it, you reference another AI agent tool.
And it was like these personal assistants that got everybody really excited
this year.
I think it's because of the idea and the promise of like, oh, hey,
you can just connect everything to this agent.
And then the agent reads messages, drafts emails,
takes care of the things you don't want to take care of.
So the core idea is like, oh, there's an agent.
And maybe you run it on your laptop.
But that's not really secure.
So it needs to run the cloud.
But then that hosts, that brings all these other problems together.
OK, how do you run an AI system securely in the cloud?
And I think the original AI assistants, that was the hard part.
Everybody's talking about buying Mac Minis, getting VPSs,
doing all this crazy stuff.
But now it's like, OK, RockBot exists.
And it's just an agent that accesses all this stuff
and just runs in the cloud.
There's no setup.
Most people don't want to think about it.
Exactly.
They don't want to think.
I mean, let alone like getting everything installed and then making
sure it has access to the right A computer, the internet, browser control.
People don't want to think about this.
The broad audience does not want to think about that stuff.
I generally don't want it.
If I'm on the run, if I'm taking a walk or I'm doing something else
and I need to shoot off a quick email or a task,
I don't want to have to think about how it's all working behind the scenes.
That's not where I want to spend my time.
And I think the new generation of AI assistants, like RockBot,
are incredibly good at abstracting all of that complexity away.
Super interesting.
And so you talked about how you're using RockBot with your family ops.
Do you have any other cool use cases for it?
Yeah.
OK, so I think I mentioned this before we started streaming.
But one of the coolest ones is I went around my house,
gathered everything that I wanted to sell.
Like stuff that I've not used in a while.
I had a PlayStation I didn't use for a while, a mountain bike.
You're getting rid of the PlayStation, dude.
Come on.
I got rid of it.
I know.
And especially with GTA 6 coming up soon.
I kind of regretted it in that moment.
But I haven't turned it on in a year and a half.
So OK, anyway, so I took pictures of everything.
I sent all the pictures to RockBot and just said, list them.
And so the only things that I had to do after that
were log in to Facebook.
So it listed it on Facebook Marketplace and log into eBay.
Some of them it listed on eBay.
Interesting.
And so like the mountain bike, I
want to meet somebody in person because I
don't want to ship a mountain bike.
You can't really ship a 70 pound mountain bike.
But for like everything else, I shipped it.
And yeah, it just, OK, so posted everything,
did the research on what the items were.
That's a big part of shipping or, sorry,
selling, making sure the listing is really complete.
Did all the research, put the listing together,
posted it, and then watched it.
And then when we got questions from potential buyers,
it would automatically try to answer them.
And if it couldn't, it would ask me for like, hey,
how would you answer this?
Or hey, do you want to entertain
this kind of lower price?
And it just followed up indefinitely.
And I've already sold.
Yeah, I sold the PlayStation.
I sold the MacBook.
And I'm still working on getting that mountain bike sold.
But it is just, man, I was just showing you.
I just got a message.
Somebody offered me a price.
So I'm going to go negotiate, or I'll
let my graphite negotiate it.
You could sell it live on this.
That's funny.
And I actually use mine for similar,
actually buying things sometimes on Facebook Marketplace,
definitely like negotiating.
A lot of like purchasing and understanding these items
is like you have to immerse yourself in the domain.
Software is very similar.
You have to understand, oh, what is a mountain bike?
How much is it worth?
How much is my mountain bike worth?
What are the variables?
Nobody has time to do that to then list this thing.
And so you can just ask an agent that
can do web search to understand relative prices.
It got comps.
It actually got the comparables for mountain
bikes that had sold in the last six months.
And yeah, it listed at a great price.
And yeah, it's impressive.
I think one of the things that might go understated
is that we talk about these personal use cases.
And then people go, OK, but you're
trying to use Grokbot in our jobs or whatever.
And I think the important thing is
personal problems map almost directly to business problems.
You're trying to sell something.
OK, well, you could use Grokbot to haggle with a vendor
the exact same way that we're describing using it
in Facebook Marketplace.
OK, go out, help me understand the raw materials,
help me understand the data, help me understand deals
that my teammates are doing, and synthesize all of that.
And then in this communication that I'm having,
I don't have to go ask somebody.
That saves eternal time.
Yeah, we do something very similar.
I mean, for my business, Forward Future, we work with sponsors.
I make videos.
They want to tell my audience about their products.
OK, so we take on sponsors.
Grokbot now knows about all of our different ad units.
It knows about the pricing.
It knows about our inventory.
It knows about the context of the relationship.
Have we worked with this company before?
Have we not?
And it helps me.
It joins all the meetings via Fathom,
which is like an AI recording for meetings,
gets the transcript, understands.
It basically puts it all together.
And at the very end, it's just like, OK, here's your proposal.
And I didn't have to do anything.
And sometimes I'll say, OK, actually, that's
like a little bit off.
We have a little bit of other context here.
But it's right, and it's saving me so much time.
It's really nice.
And that's kind of the back office stuff
I had mentioned earlier.
OK, interesting.
Yeah, and I mean, same for me.
I joined Cursor and then eventually SpaceX
right around the time of this acquisition.
And so there's a lot of context going on.
And luckily, Grokbot was in development at the time.
So I had access to it throughout my entire tenure here.
I just use it for onboarding.
Lee hired me, shout out Lee, amazing guy, Lee Robinson,
at LeeRob on Twitter, this little plug.
And I feel bad being somewhere, and I
have to ask people things.
I feel useless.
But even then, normally at a company, you start your job.
And you're like, OK, I guess I got to open the company wiki
and read all this stuff.
And then I don't know where this stuff is.
I got to ask somebody.
I got to putz around and search, look in Slack, find messages.
It's like the information retrieval,
very similar to how you're retrieving information
across your email and your calendar with your wife,
all this stuff.
It's like now you actually have the shared context
that you could just say, who owns this thing?
Look in Slack, look in Notion.
How do I get XYZ done?
Oh, actually, I'm blocked on perms.
Have other people been blocked on similar permissions
in the past?
Who did they talk to to get this stuff done?
Totally.
And what I've found is the number of messages
I've had to send to a manager or to my teammates
to ask them random questions is nearly zero.
And that compounds over an entire organization.
If you have everybody that has the agency
to be able to just answer questions, it's outstanding.
OK, Matt, let me extend on that point.
Because you're right.
You kind of made me realize how valuable that
is in the moment.
With AI, if I have 150 emails coming in every day,
and I'm trying to remember in a moment,
what did this person say about a sponsor?
What was the last context I had with them?
And I'm working with a bunch of sponsors.
I don't necessarily have to go search through my email,
dig through it, look through the thread,
look through all of the replies.
I simply ask the bot, and it'll go and find it.
And so I think that reduces the amount of context switching,
but also context searching, which is what you just mentioned.
And that also is a huge, huge value.
And OK, now multiply that across multiple email addresses,
Notion, and Slack, and Drive, and all these other things.
Now you have documents and contexts
in so many different places.
And you don't have to remember where each one is now.
And I'm realizing I've been doing that,
but maybe I didn't put it verbally how important
and how valuable that kind of piece of it is.
Yeah, and I mean, to me, these are universal problems.
And it's almost like I can't really remember
what it was like when I was like, oh man,
I need to go look through Slack.
I'm like, I'm never going to do that again,
because it's really hard to find stuff.
And searching across multiple calendars.
I remember just a couple weeks ago,
I got invited to something.
I think it was a company event.
And I was like, wait, did someone post that that
was happening in Slack, or send me an email,
or just put it on my calendar?
And if they did put it on my calendar, when was it?
And you talk about, hey, we just want AI to be easy,
as humans.
This is Friday, after my brain was cooked.
I'm like, I don't even know where I am right now.
But this is like being an employee and doing a job.
There are times when you're overloaded
with all this information.
And to just ask AI, could you remind me
when this thing is and where it was?
Might seem like a simple thing,
but that could be the difference between you missing
an important meeting or being there.
Do you remember Microsoft Recall?
Do you remember?
It was like maybe a year and a half, two years ago,
where Microsoft was, they announced this product, Recall,
which would watch everything you do on the computer.
And it was kind of this super powered search.
And so it would effectively take screenshots
of everything you were doing on the computer,
and then you would be able to ask AI,
like, hey, I remember this email.
They, leading up to the launch,
got so much flack about the privacy and the security.
And it's just, it's like,
it's very different from how Grokbot works.
But I think back to that,
and I at the time was so excited,
just not having to remember where all the things are
in the 17 different places that I store documents.
And so...
Now everybody's kind of opting in.
I'm like, no, I want to share all this stuff.
I would have been OK.
But yeah, at the time, they got a lot of crap for it.
It is interesting.
It is interesting how everyone has leaned into some
of these agentic.
You just trust the model.
It's going to work out.
You trust the guardrails.
Also, security has evolved substantially since then.
It's not just taking screenshots anymore.
No, we actually have a secure connection
to the system of record.
Even some of these personal assistants
you're mentioning earlier this year,
I remember because I do technology demos, someone was like,
hey, I want you to demo this thing on our service.
And I look at it, and I'm like, I can't show people this.
It's just dumping passwords in plain text.
Now, compared to that, it's like Grok Bot,
where it's like you have secure entry.
It goes into a vault.
The agent can't even see the password.
So that is much more secure.
And you have a much smaller blast radius
if any of the systems get compromised.
Shifting gears a little bit.
One other use case you told me about,
which I think is interesting.
You told me Grok Bot helped you with your electricity bill.
Is that correct?
Yeah.
I'd love to hear about this, because I
pay a lot for electricity.
So I kept getting these emails from PG&E saying, hey,
you could save on your electricity bill.
You have an electric car, so you
should think about one of these other plans.
I looked at the email, first of all, as three pages,
like a ton of text.
And maybe I have no attention span.
Maybe that's it.
But I'm looking at this email, and I'm like, OK,
I would like to save money, and I would like to change plan.
And then I would just like, oh, then I have to compare.
What plan should I be on?
They don't tell you.
So I gave Grok Bot.
I took a screenshot of the email, gave it to Grok Bot,
and I said, figure out if I should switch plans
and which one.
Look at my previous 12 months of electricity usage.
Look at the bills and tell me.
And so all it asked me to do was log into PG&E,
and that was it.
And so it did all this review, looked
at the 12 months of my bills, and said, oh, yeah,
you could save $1,000 by switching to this other plant.
That is especially tailored for having an electric car
and doing off-peak usage, charging off-peak usage
power.
And I was like, wow, that was really easy.
I had it double-checked the math twice, just in case.
Yeah, I switched plans this morning.
There you go.
$1,000.
$1,000 a year.
I mean, it's incredible.
Maybe all in all took about 60 seconds
of my actual mental attention.
I love classifying problems like these, because it's like,
again, you're talking about a very specific personal problem,
and there might be people out there like, oh, I
don't actually pay that much for electricity.
This doesn't apply to me.
But it's like, there are all these things in our life
that we have to pay attention to.
And part of being an adult is that you can't.
It's just so hard to give your attention to all these things,
whether it's your kid's emails or stuff at your job.
Maybe you're so overloaded that you pick a more expensive
supplier at your work just because it's easier for you to do that.
You just don't want to think about it more.
Exactly.
Yeah, totally.
And now it's like, OK, well, if I can at least map the problem
space and then put an agent on figuring that thing out,
you don't have to worry about that.
And you can optimize these things.
Yeah.
It's so interesting you say that.
I've talked about this a lot on my channel.
The ROI on tasks that had kind of a lower value
is now substantially greater.
The ROI on, let's say you have two things to choose from,
one which would have been $10,000 of value
and one which would have been $1,000 of value.
Obviously, you're going to focus your human mental attention
on the $10,000 one, maybe forgetting or just dismissing
the $1,000 one because it just didn't make sense.
Now you can do both.
And both of them take substantially less attention.
And thus, the ROI on investing in that getting whatever,
the $1,000 value thing, like simply changing plans
on my electricity, or whatever else it is,
it makes a lot of sense now.
It just becomes much easier.
And I think an extension of it is just
have it go through your email and look
at all your subscriptions.
Even if it's $9.99 a month and you haven't used it in six
months, go ahead and cancel it.
And you can have GrokBuy.
You can have your AI assistant do that for you now.
And previously, you would have maybe said,
OK, that's $9.99 a month.
Maybe I'll use it next month.
I don't really want to click through and have
to answer 17 questions about why I'm canceling.
It's like, no, no, GrokBuy, go ahead, cancel.
Yeah.
And that's it.
It's done.
Yeah, totally agree.
I mean, it just incentivizes the agency.
If you're the type of person that you like to get stuff
done, or you just feel like you don't have enough time,
you're limited by time or resources to get things done.
But you have the energy and willingness
to dig into problems.
It's like, hey, look.
Any time you've ever gone to the doctor's office,
this has happened to me.
I use GrokBuy and Grok for these sorts of things.
You get a bill.
And the bill makes no sense.
And you're like, dude, where did this number come from?
Nobody can explain it to you.
You can just use AI and not have to spend your Saturday
morning trying to understand a bill.
And like you said, one of those things where it's like,
oh, maybe I just don't want to deal with this.
So I'll give them a couple hundred bucks.
Totally.
Now I can have something that helps me figure that thing out.
I want to bring up something.
Maybe you struggle with this now.
I am getting more work done than ever.
And I know you've probably heard this.
I'm also busier than ever.
I'm actually struggling on the attention,
not the attention, the context switching
between all of these things.
I'm kicking off so many different agents.
And they're coming back.
And there is still this cognitive load
of switching between different threads,
switching between different pieces of context.
How do you solve for that?
What does your workflow look like?
That's interesting.
So it's funny.
We actually talked about this in a session on the stream
just earlier today.
And Lauren, who's probably sitting over there somewhere,
hacking on our software, our game design, shout out potato.
Potato gets all the shout outs on Twitter.
If you go on Twitter, it's just potatoes.
Yeah, I've been seeing her name everywhere.
It's just people saying potato.
It's insane.
So one workflow she mentioned, which is like she's
is a chief of staff.
She just calls her Steve, which I like better
than chief of staff.
Chief of staff is like overplayed in my book.
Like we're on the stream.
If the chat in the stream, no more chief of staff.
Can I show you?
I have chief of staff.
Of course you have chief.
I'm switching it right after this now.
I have been shamed into switching it.
I just feel like we have to be more creative.
We have to be more human with our agents.
So anyway, just basically like the same model
as a coding agent, which is that you have like an orchestrator.
And then you can like fan that out into subagents.
And rather than interacting with the subagents,
you interact with the orchestrator.
So you could be like chief of staff bot.
So OK, so this doesn't work without one other piece,
which I'll describe, which is Lauren
has like a bot factory bot, which is
she thinks about how she likes to create bots.
And then she put that into a bot.
So chief of staff bot, talk to, she calls it Dr. Eggbot.
This is all very playful.
Steve, talk to Dr. Eggbot and create a bot to do this thing.
So now you're really only interacting
with chief of staff bot.
So you say, chief of staff bot, I
want to understand my power, my energy bill,
create a new bot that is focused on auditing that
and report back.
And so now at least you're looking in this one thread.
And you can kind of kick off these agents that then report
back.
And you're maybe in one piece of context.
So that's one way to approach the problem.
I like that.
I've done some of that.
But I find myself going into each individual thread.
I'm a huge fan of having things separated by topic.
And so I do find myself, the chief of staff
is where I go in the morning.
That's where I go to really think about things
and kick off the day's tasks.
But as each of the individual bots are working,
I do find myself going into each one.
And it's kind of interesting.
I do think eventually I'll kind of more and more
try to push things to just being summarized really concisely
in the, I'm just going to call it chief of staff for now.
I'm sorry.
But I'll probably try to push more and more things,
my attention specifically, into the chief of staff
rather than trying to go into each and every single bot
that I have.
I mean, the other thing that I'll say
is because I feel like everybody in AI
feels like they have to have some sort of like swab
answer to questions like these.
It's just overload sometimes.
As an engineer, if I'm writing code,
I have 10 cloud agents running at the same time
working on 10 things.
Writing code used to be like, oh, I'm
going to put on low five beats or whatever
and just chill out and think about one thing.
And now you're just like an overloaded manager at all times.
So I think as an industry, we just
need to evolve to understand the way to handle
some of these problems.
And I think at least the people I've talked to,
everybody's a little stressed out and trying to do more.
And that's normal.
It's so nice to hear that, Matt.
No, it's nice.
It's nice because I'm not alone on this.
It's just true.
Myself and my entire team, we're getting more done than ever.
We're busier than ever.
But there is this cognitive overheating at times
where I'm just like, I need to step away.
And I think a lot of these are probably design problems
that'll get polished over time.
But it's really nice to hear people suffer with it too.
And I think it actually, in some ways,
like being busy all the time, it
makes you think like, what are actually
the right things to focus on?
So it's like, OK, do I need to do this all the time?
So yeah, I think this was a great conversation.
We have a customer video that we're
going to kick to in a second here, Nokia.
And they're analyzing 50 million lines of code
in two weeks with Cursor.
So we're going to kick it over to one of our customers.
We'll learn a little bit more about that.
Cool?
It.
That's cool, but I can just be going with you.
Oh, whoops.
Now we're back.
Are we back?
The SVP of product and engineering
for one of our product development divisions
at Nokia.
We are trying to leverage Cursor as an agentic platform
to introduce specialized agents that are persona specific
for every aspect of work that we do that can partner
with the human in seat that does that work today.
Those things become much more possible
if we are able to iterate in much, much faster loops.
That directly impacts customer economics,
lowers unit cost, improves customer satisfaction.
And then finally, there's an entire class of things
that I think we're now going to be able to do faster
that are to do with increasing resilience, reliability,
and security in the network.
Cursor and Cursor's agents that increasingly,
many of them are out of the box,
is a massive step up in accelerating analysis,
getting insights that otherwise would not be possible.
So we're at the beginning of a very critical journey.
We've burnt the boats.
Our plans, our goals for this year,
not next year, for this year, hinge on this working.
We have a product line,
easily 50 plus million lines of code.
We are, I would say, in an intermediate stage
of decomposing what is fundamentally
a monolith-oriented architecture.
It would be a very daunting task for us
to attempt a manual inspection of that code base.
We have undertaken that with Cursor.
Our early results of that analysis
have been remarkable.
We have been able to do precisely what I just described,
which would have required bespoke tooling,
would have taken far longer,
probably several months of effort
across probably a dozen or more expert people.
We performed the initial analysis as one example
within a matter of, I think,
a couple of weeks by two people.
We've seen evidence of Cursor being deployed
very successfully in situations that involve
a need to move very quickly
where we have run into a customer-impacting defect
that might be having a subscriber impact,
and now we're able to do that
against an extremely large corpus of service requests
and radically accelerate something
like a root cause analysis.
These examples have not been one or two.
There have been quite a few and growing in number.
That's where we're seeing, I'd say, the early success.
And where we would love to take it next
is leveraging Cursor as a platform
for multi-agent deployment and orchestration,
where really the role of the engineer,
the architect, becomes the supervision of agents
that are calling out the tools,
that are performing work at scale,
collaborating with one another.
We are literally redesigning
our entire software development lifecycle
from inception through product delivery
and everything that comes in between.
And we are back.
So Matt has left the studio.
Now only one Matt remains, and we have another guest.
Got to keep the great guest coming.
Yeah, welcome back.
For those of you who are just tuning in,
we are in the middle of a three-day livestream
here at Rockbot Galaxy in San Francisco,
part of Dreamforce right next door
to all the festivities happening right outside.
We are building together, over the course of three days,
a business entirely implemented
by Rockbot and coding agents.
And so we spent our first day
working through some ideas.
Today, we're really deep in coding.
We were earlier today showing you
how we're using bots to drive a lot of the core workflows
that we use to power our software engineering stack.
Lauren is currently off stream
working on re-implementing some of our prototypes
into a scalable game system.
And so we're really excited to show you that
when we come back on in just a few minutes here
with the full team.
In the meantime, we're really excited
to bring on our first intern.
So I really guess we actually just hired an intern.
I mean, I feel like any other team needs an intern, right?
Like, you've got someone who can help out.
Yeah.
But you're more than just an intern.
You're also currently a student at Stanford, right?
You wanted to introduce yourself
and say a little bit about who you are?
Yeah.
So everyone, I am the first forward deployed intern.
So on my full-time job,
I am bringing them coffee on a day-to-day basis.
Currently, actually, before this live stream started,
I was handling all the coffee logistics.
Really, really great.
But in my free time, I guess, whenever I get that,
I'm a full-time student at Stanford University.
I'm a rising junior and I need a job.
Hopefully we can help with that.
And hopefully this job is some good
on-the-ground experience.
And what are you majoring in at Stanford?
I'm majoring in computer science right now.
Cool.
And you are a huge Grokbot user.
Is that right?
Yes.
I personally get through all of my usage
in half the time limit.
Wow.
Okay.
We should really maybe take that feedback
back to our usage team to figure out
how we can make that a little bit better.
Or just give me more usage.
That would also work, yeah.
Maybe it's an intern benefit that we can stick in.
Some intern credits.
Okay, very cool, very cool.
Well, thanks so much for hanging out with us.
I think one of the things that we've been doing
throughout the stream here is,
in addition to benefiting from all the work
you've been doing behind the scenes,
also just trying to learn how different people
use Grokbot in their day-to-day.
Obviously you have a really unique use case
that we were talking about off-camera
where you are applying to jobs.
You said you need a job.
And it seems like you've put together
a pretty cool team of Grokbots
who are helping you do all that work.
And so, would love for you to kind of
just talk us through how are you using Grokbot?
How has it been helpful for you in the job search?
And for those of us, or for those of us watching maybe,
who aren't as familiar with how a job search goes these days,
kind of like how that process works nowadays,
I feel like it's a really competitive market,
particularly for software engineering.
So maybe let's start off with that.
How does the job market work these days?
What are the things you're having to manage
as you're kind of going through the job search process?
And let's start with that.
Yeah, of course.
So keep in mind that I started my job search,
my internship search around two or three months ago.
Now, there's usually like three to four pathways
that I like to think of when it comes to the job search.
First is obviously the normal method, which is cold applying.
You see that job for SpaceX AI, sweet internship,
and then you see that and then you're like,
all right, I got to apply within three hours.
At the end of the day,
any big company is gonna get over 200, 500 applications.
So it becomes very competitive, very fast.
The second approach is focusing on the startup community.
All startups need good engineers at the end of the day,
and they need people who can ship fast, deliver fast,
and then also bring in new unique ideas
that can improve either their business or their workflow
or anything else.
The third approach is a little bit unique in that sense,
which is going outside of the cold approach strategy
and then just directly communicating with the recruiter,
seeing if you can email them or having a coffee chat
with some employee within a particular organization
you wanna work for and then have them connect
with the recruiter and then get you fast-tracked
into the process.
And then the fourth strategy is just on-air begging,
for example, on here as a forward deployed intern,
so let's hope that stays.
That's what that could burst.
That's what that could burst, yeah.
Well, it's funny because when you're mentioning that,
there's so much that this ties to
when it comes to sales, right?
There's this sort of like,
you're doing some outbound prospecting
where you're going out and finding leads for your job,
and then there's sort of the open contact forms
where you're filling in just like, contact us,
but you kinda wanna make sure that goes somewhere.
And so it feels like,
I can't help but draw that analogy.
It feels like you're almost selling yourself, right,
versus selling a product.
Does that sound right?
Way, exactly.
That's a perfect analogy.
Like, you have to sell yourself when it comes to the job.
Whether it's cold applying,
you need to be the perfect match
for whatever scanner they use.
When it comes to a startup,
if you're DMing them,
you have to be the perfect candidate
at the end of the day.
You have to craft like the perfect DM
that catches everyone's attention.
Okay, well, I know you're using Grokbot
to power a ton of these workflows,
and so it'd be really great
if we can just get your screen up on the camera.
I think this laptop is plugged in here.
We can get that on the stream soon.
But yeah, take us through how you are using Grokbot.
And I'm curious just to maybe like walk us through your team,
kinda who's in your team,
how you set up these bots.
There we go.
And if you don't mind, just like command plus a little bit,
we can zoom all in a little.
There we go.
Oh yeah, walk us through your team.
Actually, maybe even a little bit more,
if you don't mind, just really big.
Oh yeah, of course.
Yeah, we're good.
We're good, much better.
Yeah, of course.
So I guess I can start off with the most recent one
I talked about other than Begging,
which is the Recruiter Finder.
Right now I have a Grokbot that essentially controls my web
on their VM.
It will find all different recruiters via search,
searches them up on LinkedIn,
uses the Apollo extension, a browser extension
to see if their email address is like within their database,
copies that into a CSV,
and then now I just have access to that.
And then it goes through all the different big tech
companies or any tech companies that are hiring
for software engineering roles.
So for instance, you can see all the different rounds
and all the different emails.
I really hope this doesn't go against any law about doxing,
but also who cares.
But as you can see, there's like a bunch of emails.
There's also this, let me see if I can pull up.
Some email validation scripts you've written.
Yes.
Some cool notes there.
Yep, yep, yep.
Cool, and you have like cover letters
that you're writing.
Okay, we've got to talk a little bit about that.
That's gonna be fun.
Oh, that is gonna be very fun.
And that is actually something I was working on,
but really quick, these are all the recruiting emails
that I have.
Love it, love it, love it.
Okay, let's go back to your Grok bots.
So you have a bot here who's helping you find recruiters
to contact, that's awesome.
Walk us through some of the other ones you have here.
I see an alumni database email finder.
Yes, okay.
I really hope Stanford University is not watching this.
Really hope that.
It might be.
If there's any sensitive data,
we don't have to show that for me.
It's not sensitive data, at least not shown here.
What this does is we have,
every university has like alumni database
at the end of the day, or a majority of them do.
And they all have information about
which alumni are working where.
And for example, I'm interested
in like software engineering positions.
So I'm looking into the alumni database
and see who's working at Google, Microsoft,
SpaceX AI, et cetera, et cetera.
Then I searched them up.
So this bot, what it does is it searches up
a bunch of people, runs it through the alumni database.
That alumni database hands me back the email
and then it copies that, puts into a CSV as per usual.
And then eventually what I'm gonna do with both
the combination about the recruiter finder
and also the alumni database email finder
is use that and then connect it with the Outlook MCP
to just start sending out emails to these recruiters
and alumni asking for coffee chats
or asking for a way to understand the recruiting process,
getting any information or any tips.
All of those things are gonna be very important
during the job search.
And that is something I'm planning on doing.
I'm curious, so you mentioned that there's
like a database backing this.
How did you connect GrokBot to that source of data?
Is this like a connector you built yourself?
Did you feed us some CSVs?
What does the process look like
to kind of bring some of that context into the bot?
Yeah, so I think the biggest thing is that
there's actually no connectors.
It's actually really non-technical in that sense.
I can honestly show you the screen if that's okay.
Yeah, let's not show any sensitive information.
Oh, there's no sensitive information on the blog.
But this is the alumni directory.
All it does is it just controls this web
and it just searches up every different name,
every different profession, whatever, whatever, companies,
and then it finds all that information.
There's no connectors.
Honestly, all you need to do with your GrokBot
is just give it access to whatever directory you want,
and then also eventually give it access to your email
that connects your GrokBot to your student email,
and then just start sending out emails.
It's actually very straightforward.
There's not many connectors involved with this.
I really like that.
It's a great example, I think,
of how GrokBot has its own computer
to go get work done for you.
And it sounds like in this case,
you're just driving GrokBot through computer use
and having it navigate these various services for you.
Obviously something that we've seen
a ton of great use cases around over the last day or two.
Yeah, I'm curious.
We earlier saw a little flash
in your Finder window of cover letters.
So maybe tell us a little bit
about your cover letter writer.
Because we talked a lot about
how this is a marketing and sales game.
So how are you marketing yourself
and how you write these cover letters?
Yeah, so that's actually a great question.
This is actually something I was working on
five minutes ago, actually.
Well, it was lacking off while entering for us.
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It was my downtime.
It was my off-air career.
You're a cover writer.
Okay, so the way that this works is
I have two bots that actually work with cover letters.
One thing I've noticed with all the jobs
that I've been applying for is you need two things.
You need a resume, obviously a tailored resume
with the key words or whatever stacks
and you need to implement
based on the job description or the JD.
I will say JD a lot,
so that just means job description.
Second thing will be the cover letter,
which I think is the harder way
to actually autonomize in that sense.
Because cover letters are really personal.
It describes not only the job and what you've done,
but also needs to connect what you've done to the job,
include your personal experience,
include your voice at the end of the day.
And I think that is something that
you just need to work on a lot
in order to make that possible.
So what I have here is a set of two bots.
First is the cover letter writer.
This is actually a new bot that I created
less than like 10 minutes ago.
What this does is it takes my resume,
it takes in all of the different stories
that I've written within this bot saying,
oh, I work this internship at Stanford Medicine.
Here are all the stories
that relate to what I actually worked on.
Here's what I worked on for my project.
This is what I worked on for my game.
And these are all the stories.
And then it has all of that information.
And then it also has my resume, obviously.
Then what it does is there's another bot
that's like the sweet job appire,
which focuses on finding all of the jobs out there,
GitHub repositories, greenhouse,
I forgot what it's called, Ashby.
Yeah, Ashby, exactly.
Goes through all of that,
finds as many jobs as possible,
scans through the JD,
sends it to the cover letter writer.
Then it will take that information,
do a little bit of deep research if it needs to
about company values or whatnot.
Then it sends it through a pipeline,
which is just a cover letter creator repo
that I personally made.
As you mentioned before, like off air,
you saw cloud agents running.
So this is all the different cloud agents
that were running before.
If I scroll up right over here.
What does that repo do?
We can get your screen back on there in a second.
Yeah, but what does that repo do?
So you wrote some code with the cloud agent.
Is this sort of generating a PDF with the cover letters?
Yeah, that's exactly it.
That's cool.
It generates the entire cover letter
and it sends it back to the suite job applier.
The other thing that I wanted to work on
because at the end of the day cover letters,
as I mentioned before, are really nuanced
and they need to be perfectly crafted.
I created an actual guardrail in that sense,
like a cover letter critic,
which looks at the cover letters and is like,
hmm, this doesn't sound like you.
Yeah.
I don't like how it's saying,
and this is what I wanna work on,
which sounds so inspirationally useless.
So that is something that I have right now,
which is essentially like a guardrail at the end of the day,
whether it's in cover letter generation
or in like actual like code bases,
you need to have something that's writing the code,
something that's actually thoroughly testing
and sending it.
So those are the two bots I have
for the cover letter generation.
This repo also creates the resume.
However, I don't worry too much about the resume
just because, and this is also a tip
that I would give to everyone who's applying to jobs,
do not fake your resume.
You will have experiences,
you have stuff that you can work on
or you've already worked on.
Don't fake experience
because when you get that first interview,
which I have multiple times,
if you fake anything, you are not gonna get through.
Yeah, not lying I think is a good idea.
Yeah, just to get it.
Honestly, honesty is good.
Honestly.
Yeah.
So it sounds like you have this cover letter,
I love the bot interaction you just described.
So you have a cover letter generator
and then how did you train that cover letter critic?
So it like knows stuff about you clearly,
there's also a resume that hangs out in the generator.
So did you prompt this critic in a way
where it kind of learns more about how you're,
the actual things you've worked on?
Like what does the review process look like
when one of these bots talks to the other
and it's like, hey, critique my work.
Yeah, well, that's awesome.
So the way that it works
and the way that it was actually trained is
I personally like was just sitting there,
it generated a cover letter.
I would look at the different feedback
and like the different use cases that are the patterns
that I just knew that were embedded within this repo
that wasn't resonating with the way I actually write.
An example that I was actually fixing just now
is that it would write very short, very useless sentences.
An example would be like-
AI slop.
Yeah, AI slop, but like the most motivational AI slop.
Interesting.
Right, it would be like, and I want to do this.
I want to work on agents.
And then I, myself, I was thinking,
yeah, what agents, why?
What are you working on?
The complexity, specificity.
Yeah, specificity.
You want to be able to tune it to be a little more real.
Exactly.
So I noticed that my writing style
and I also looked through all my different papers
that I've written, I also gave it all the papers
that I've written in pre-2022,
like before AI slop became a thing.
So what happened was it noticed the pattern of like,
I like to use compound complex sentences,
maybe a little bit of gerund usage as well.
So it includes that into the cover letter.
I also, I personally like to write very enthusiastically
in all of my messages,
whether it's in DMs, cover letters,
or just professional messages I sent on Slack.
So it also mentioned that.
So in total, my cover letter critic
looks at the four different paragraphs.
First is the beginning paragraph.
It checks whether you mentioned the role,
you mentioned why you want to work on the role
and how your experience,
how, what you want to take away from this role.
Like what do you actually want to work on and why?
Second cover letter, one experience focusing on what you did,
does it actually use the experience,
from my experiences.md,
does it use all that information
and does it connect back to the job?
Second or the third paragraph, same thing,
another experience and explaining why,
how does it connect back to the job
and whether it's impactful.
And then third, fourth paragraph, sorry.
Fourth paragraph focuses on going back,
summing up the work that I did for these two,
like the last two paragraphs very briefly,
and then describing,
this is the impact I want to make on this company.
I want to build X, Y, and Z.
An example would be like,
I want to build agent evaluations
to ensure that research production is done properly
or something like that.
But obviously with a lot more specification
based on the job description.
Like tailoring it to the actual goal and all that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is really cool.
And I feel like it does link,
going back to what you were saying earlier too,
how you just do prospecting if you're in sales
and thinking about like,
making a compelling pitch for your product,
in this case yourself.
What I particularly like about this
is something we were talking about earlier,
is like you can really train these bots
and they sort of grow in their memory over time, right?
And I think we've seen a couple of examples of that.
Lauren just has really driven this home to me,
just like over,
every time I talk to her I'm reminded,
it's like as long as actually really
all you need to prompt well
is attention to detail
and just being extremely conscientious.
And so as soon as you see an agent
do something that you don't like,
you just say, why did it do that thing?
Help me understand at the root cause
of what that thing is,
and then I'm gonna make a one line sentence
in the skill that the agent loads
to make sure it doesn't do that thing.
And it's like, if you do that over and over and over,
you actually get agents that like compound
and get better over time,
versus like, oh, like I didn't really like that,
I'll just fix it and I'm not gonna tell
the agent what to do better.
And then you kind of lose,
you lose that, you know,
you have to save these things off.
Yeah, you lose the feedback loop.
Exactly. Yeah.
And then one other thing I was gonna say is just,
aside from sales, right,
there are other connections,
which I liked how you, you know,
you described how you're using these agents
to tell your...
I think having a job, one of the hardest things for me is to remember, this is going to sound silly, but when you're doing a lot of things, what you actually did in a given day.
And so for me it's so easy, I have an agent that every day and every week looks at Slack notion.
Actually you can cover pretty much all the services you work in as a knowledge worker, GitHub, right?
Just look at my PRs, look at what I sent in Slack, look at what I posted on Twitter because I make content, and then summarize that and then write it into bullet points from each day.
That rolls up over weeks and all of a sudden you just have a log of everything that you've done and you can more clearly speak to, oh hey I'm going to stand up, here's what I'm working on.
My brain is more focused.
Yeah, I use that kind of thing all the time too where it's like, help me maintain this sort of self-evolving knowledge base of the stuff that I'm doing.
And so I feel like when we're writing a lot of code, we do this in the code base, and Lauren actually talked a little bit yesterday on the stream about how code bases are the best example of memory because they sort of have this history over in the course of Git commits and all this.
That kind of persists memory for how code evolves over time.
And I think there's actually an equivalent for this for knowledge work that we're kind of talking about where you can train a bot on sort of things that you've been doing and kind of build it over time so that it has its own sense of memory.
Of course, bots have their own memory but kind of helping steer it based on the inputs that you're creating, the outputs you're creating each day, making that part of your process I think.
Sounds like you've implemented a lot of those, a lot of those things.
Yeah, very cool.
Go ahead.
I was just going to say, maybe we could do some work with our intern here rather than talking about him applying to other jobs.
Let's do it.
No, I'm just kidding.
Yeah, so maybe we could start talking through like one thing we haven't really covered in our sort of game studio is like the go-to-market motion.
So I think we need to think through like ops, sales, like basically like everything from marketing to like getting the message out there if we wanted to run some like creative ads.
We have all the codes and maybe there's some ways we could like create ads that are like on brand or something.
But I don't know, maybe maybe you can bring some fresh perspective to the situation.
Yeah.
What do you think makes a game viral?
I was.
Are you a big game or do you play games or are you a big?
I play a lot of games, whether it's like sandbox games like Minecraft.
Yeah.
Minecraft daily, daily puzzle games like Wordle or my own.
So a lot of those are pretty viral.
Like the puzzle games are all over the place.
Yeah.
I think the two biggest things for a virality is word of mouth, which obviously it's very obvious because once you have enough people playing it, right, your friends tell you and then you eventually tell your other friends and then that becomes a big thing.
I think the second thing is just continuously and constantly posting about it.
I think eventually when you just see enough content about like this somewhat interesting game, right, people try it out.
Right.
Maybe the conversion rate is hopefully 10 percent.
Yeah.
It will probably be much less.
But if you get one viral post, a lot of people play it.
Right.
Then you start to develop that like community and foundation, which then starts to expand kind of like a ripple effect.
And that at least to me seems like the way that games are usually made viral.
But there's also like other perspectives just as like paying for ads or like commercials or something like that.
I guess like for the for the friends of yours that you're playing games with and kind of when you think about what catches your eye these days, like, is this Instagram ads?
Is it, you know, like great post on X?
Is it TikTok?
Is it something else?
Like, let's say we were to go and build out some ads.
Like, what should we where should we think about that?
How should we think about that?
I.
Where do you where do you find and how do you discover new products?
I think I would discover new products.
I wouldn't recommend Instagram.
I just think Instagram has a different niche for game development.
Like instead of like games, it's just mostly like random reels or other random stuff.
Yeah.
I think the best places would probably be X.
I know there's a lot of like engineers are just like I forgot the exact term, but it's like early adopters who are going to be like trying out the game and seeing what's going on.
I think a second thing and this is something I was also looking into is posting on like random Reddit channels like maybe not the huge ones.
Yeah.
For example, I was looking into daily puzzle games, maybe not that one, but like just like the niche channels that don't get a lot of love, a lot of attention.
But there's a lot of people there.
I tell them to try out your game.
You're not necessarily publicizing it.
You're trying to get feedback, which then inevitably gets you more people to actually play the game.
Yeah.
I think the first thing would probably be I mentioned X posts, probably like LinkedIn posts or even TikTok.
I would just make sure that for TikTok, it's just like really engaging.
Like the first two to three seconds are key for any virality.
At least that's what I've heard of.
Yeah.
So for you, if we're taking a step back, it sounds like you're talking about like motion or other assets that could engage the user.
That could be fun.
Maybe a trial like in our own in our own repo.
So something that I like to do.
I make a lot of videos for those that don't know.
And almost all my videos are like me doing demos, like talking to the user.
So there isn't a ton of like generative content.
But what I think might go misunderstood sometimes is that you don't necessarily need to generate like videos using like an image generation model or a video generation model rather though XAI.
You know, you can do some of these things.
Yeah.
What I like to do is especially as if you have code, you can use code as a source of truth.
So a lot of times you can add in nice elements if you say use a library like remotion.
So what I'm thinking is what if we send through some prompts to try and generate remotion assets that we can then run as ads for our game.
I really like that.
We have a good design system kind of locked too.
So maybe we could just build on some of those.
Yeah.
We can get my screen up and I can walk you through what I'm thinking here.
Let's do it.
Coming up momentarily.
So generally when I'm doing this, what I'm going for is like, okay, what you want in a platform is you want like aspect ratios that work for the platform.
So it's going to run like Twitter.
I've done some funny stuff on Twitter.
You can actually like I mean, maybe this is something we do at another point, but you can do like clever aspect ratios and like basically stretch things out on screen.
Yeah.
But a good starting place is like one to one aspect ratio.
For those of us who are not running ads or messing around with aspect ratios, that's just the square.
So you can run basically square portrait or landscape aspect ratio advertisements and different ads work for different platforms.
We're getting there's a fly fly in here.
There's a fly on set and it doesn't want me making ads.
So basically what I said is, hey, use remotion for X ads with one to one aspect ratios and the current like scratch assets.
Those are just kind of like where the assets are located.
We could even use some like light motion across for all platforms, prioritizing the hero on the land.
This is kind of like a rush prompt.
But our chief of staff bought is using Dr. Eggbot to then onboarding a remotion ads bot for a cupcake.
And so we should see that created and then spun up as a cursor cloud agent just based on how how we like to do things.
So that's like the typical flow with our chief of staff bought into even though I just talked to Matt Berman about how I don't like to call my bots chief of staff.
We actually have to we're going to we should rename him.
Yeah, Steve.
True.
I don't know if you've seen Dr. Eggbot, but we've been using Dr. Eggbot.
But that helps you stand up and has a lot of great context on how to make great bots and rockbox.
So kind of a meta bot, but it's been really fun to play with this.
Use P stock, right?
Yes.
Use the P stock.
Yeah.
There you go.
Lauren is actually like like I just keep saying that.
Like I was talking to Matthew Berman.
He's like, is that is that Lauren?
Like who just walked by there?
I was like, yeah.
He's like, dude, I see her all over Twitter.
That's amazing.
So what I'm noticing here is my Steve noticed that there was a remotion plug in.
Oh, nice.
Which was cool because it installed remotion skills and that should ideally guarantee better outputs.
And some of these are the things like I just forget sometimes, like on a new project, add the skills.
It really helps the agent behavior at times, right?
It's like someone else has done the work to kind of make it make agents really good at working with a particular tool.
It's like, yeah, just install the plug and install the skills and they can really, you know, work a lot better.
Sweet.
Yeah. So we got the remotion plug in installed and then I'd imagine it's just going to spin up an agent.
We'll start working on some remotion assets because because remotion leverages code, it's actually perfect.
If you look at like cursor like our, you know, if we look at like the files that we're actually working with here and this.
Sort of scratch repository or in a repository that has scratch files, it's in the scratch directory, the game loop.
Just it's just the HTML file, which is fine because, you know, you can do a lot of stuff with HTML and most of this is like there's some CSS in here.
Premotion uses, I believe, just typescript or React rather.
I might be wrong about that.
Don't quote me, but we should be able to translate like this.
This CSS pretty well to get like on brand assets.
So it'll be interesting to see what we get.
Maybe this will run for a couple of minutes and we'll have something to show.
Yeah.
Tim, maybe we should come up with a couple of ads, a couple of cool ad stacks.
It looks like we got the plug in going there.
You know, off screen while that's working, we're also talking about, you know, just how the job search is going and any questions you might have for us as well.
We're all hanging out together and so curious like, yeah, what's up for you?
Yeah, I think I got like the first part of the interview rounds got in that sense, like submitting the actual job application.
And then I think my question, and this is like very pertinent for me, is there's the final round interviews for a lot of big companies, right?
You obviously go through like a technical screen or technical screening with the recruiter, technical screening itself with like a senior engineer and then going through a problem, AI or the code or whatever.
Then finally, you have like the final day, which is like three back to back interviews.
Yeah.
Right.
And then I'm curious like, hey, how do you keep up the stamina to make sure that you like answer all those questions properly?
And second, like, what would you recommend as like general advice?
Obviously, off there, I will ask him how to get an internship at SpaceX AI as like other than picking up coffee.
But in general, you have any advice?
Yeah, I mean, I'm curious to get Matt's take on this too.
I think it comes down to a few things.
I think a lot of it is what you mentioned, like you have to demonstrate technical aptitude.
And so they're sort of like, you can't get around that.
You have to be sort of qualified for the role you're applying for, whether this is software engineering role, as you call it, a product role, developer engineering or any other role.
I go to market and all these.
There's like a technical aptitude that sort of needed to kind of prove that you can do the work.
And I think ultimately, one thing that I think some people sometimes forget when applying to jobs is that for employers who are hiring, job searching is a long process.
Like it takes investment.
It takes investment from like the best people on your team to spend time interviewing.
And so one of the things that I've always told myself, and maybe this is just because I'm an optimist and I like to think of the world as half the boss is half full.
But most of the time when people are bringing you in for an interview, they want you to succeed.
And so really, I think just shifting your mindset to say, hey, if you can truly, if it all works out, you're helping this team bring in someone who they really need to get something done.
So I'd say, like to me, that a large part of it is the mindset shift.
A large part of it is obviously the technical aptitude.
And then to your point on the stamina and just keeping up with it, I think it's really figuring out what systems work for you, like the way that you get energized about something, the way you can bring that energy into the people you work with.
I think a lot of work is also person to person interaction, like as much as we're hanging out with our bots and like, you know, bringing bots in to help us with our work and chatting with our bots all the time.
A large part of what makes a great team is the people that form it up.
And so just like, you know, making yourself kind of show showing to that team that you're interviewing with it, like you can be a really exciting part of that team.
And I think those three things really make a big difference. I don't know, Matt, what would you say?
I mean, I guess the thing about it a little bit differently, which is that I mean, it's tough for a first job because it's kind of like, well, you might not know anybody.
You might be in a new city where you don't have any, you know, any connections or whatever.
And even if it's like if we take a step back and you're talking about like your first internship, that's really hard. Right.
But once you start to establish like a professional network and, you know, it's actually it's shocking to me.
You don't today you don't even need to do that. You can just make cool stuff and put it on the Internet.
Yeah. Huge advocate of making stuff and putting on the Internet, much like the stream.
And it's actually a free way to make friends who are also passionate about the things that you're passionate about.
And I really think about, you know, a career as finding something that you love to do and you love to work with people who also love to do the same thing.
And so if you think about it less like a job and more like how do I just have a good time and create stuff that people want?
Right. Then it becomes less like, oh, I'm going to like by the way, what are you doing? Is it wrong? Obviously, like resumes and cover letters.
This is a very valid approach to getting a job. This is how I got most of the jobs in my career.
But there's this alternate way that I think is like very much embodied in like the open source ethos,
which is just like I'm going to spend my time doing my free time doing things I like for free.
And if you do things you like for free, whether that's making videos or tutorials, writing code, creating stuff, making art, just talking to people, you just bump in.
You just end up in the right sphere. So this is like a very like sort of one.
People might even call it like backwards or like unintuitive way of getting a job.
But through that, you usually find people who are passionate.
And if you're passionate, which I can tell by talking to you are, then it's like, OK, I want this person.
Like, I want this guy working for me because he's like I see you with using Grok, but I'm like,
there are not that many people that know how to do this. Like, let's use Grokbot.
Right. Yeah, I think that's totally right. And I think what just made me think of is that it's sort of like passion, but also like demonstrating the things that you're creative and passionate about and like opening up to a pretty broad audience.
And like for some people, that's not like engineering. For some people, that's like creative physical projects.
Like we had some guests on earlier today kind of walking through how they are like, you know, have a real passion for a particular problem that they're solving in some way.
And just being able to talk about that, I think you're actually right that, you know, sort of always been the case, like building a public profile and kind of putting yourself out there really helps.
But even now, more than ever, sort of like the distance between an idea and then seeing that idea come to life has gotten a lot smaller.
And so being able to take advantage of that in the current marketplace and throw tokens at problems and see what you can come up with.
I think that probably makes a lot of sense. Yeah.
I definitely resonate with both of you as a device. I think for your point, I always think of it as like, it's like a very antagonistic, like the whoever is interviewing me is like my antagonist.
I'm approaching like a problem by like your approach. It's like you've already in that sense, like you've already gotten the job.
Now you just got proved that you got the job right and that you're like good enough, right?
Like you're starting from 100 and then now you can like slowly go down rather as you're starting from zero and then you got proved by going all the way up the mountain.
And I think that's like a good way to look at it. And then also with your point, I love that.
I think personally, like I don't post a lot on like X or LinkedIn.
And part of the reason is because I'm like a little bit scared.
Like what do people think about what I'm working on or do they think they're dumb?
But I like I started like building more stuff over the summer. I started like talking to my friends and like realizing there's such a supportive community out there, whether it's like with your friends or like strangers on the Internet regardless.
And I think even if there's like one percent of population who might be like saying, oh, what are you doing, guy? Like, what are you doing?
Like there's going to be 90 percent who are just to be very clear for the first. I mean, people still think that of the concept that I create.
It was especially true when I first started creating content.
And I think anybody that has ever made anything and put it on the Internet would say exactly the same thing. So definitely.
I mean, you have to do that. Yeah. That's like putting yourself out there part.
It is the hard part. Be willing to suffer the criticism, but also be willing to establish yourself.
And yeah, I think it is a lot easier said than done.
But once you can get past those hurdles, I'm notoriously manifest.
Matt inspires me every day when I see the cool stuff he cooks up and I'm like, whoa, like, where does Edia come from?
How do you package it up? And so, yeah, I think it's also cool. Like, follow those inspirations.
I think that's also a really great way to like learn how to do this work is finding people who you think are doing the best versions of this and whatever niche you work in.
Like, maybe that's software engineering. Maybe that's like craft making, whatever it is.
And kind of just like seeing how some of the best in the game do their work and seeing what you can learn from that.
And I think even nowadays, like, yeah, put all that stuff in a rock pot that teaches you how to do this work.
I think that is a lot like tools now that make that even easier. So I know we've been yapping a little bit.
But Matt, I see some cool stuff on your screen. Yeah. So I wanted to just show you an existing project just so that you could understand this workflow maybe a little bit better.
So one thing that I did, one of the first things I did when I started working on Crockbot, like we have an awesome design team and they have really great assets.
So I was like, well, what if I could take like our motion assets and translate those into remotion?
So like I have basically remotion assets that looks like we might be getting that express basically like Crockbot as code here.
And so we can then generate videos from those assets. So like a spawn animation.
And then I can use those as overlays in the videos that I create. So this is like generally the workflow.
If you have the code, if you have a very on top of it design team like the SpaceX AI design team, shout out all the amazing designers.
Specifically, you know, Shadow Canny, Shadow Justin, the man helped out with this entire production. Yeah.
You can do really cool stuff. And so like what I'm trying to replicate is this exact workflow. Right.
Like, okay, take a look at main, right. Essentially what I want is it to use the remotion skills. I want it to like fetch the card stack.
And it's like working through you can see some of the logic here and it wrote six thousand lines of remotion.
Which doesn't be clear like animations like this are very are very code heavy.
So like this is kind of to be expected.
But we can kind of see what's going on here. Where did it write?
Where did it write this stuff? We can actually probably just look at the changes.
Well, files changed. Oh, my God. Apps ads. All right. Cool. So we're going to the.
So for those watching along, what Matt's doing here is he has a remote agent agent.
He's kind of interacting with the agent via the agent's command line where the terminal that he pulled up and also looking at the files the agent generated.
So that's kind of what we just saw happen in real time here.
We're making sure that things are installed and the sort of harness that's running that remotion app is running correctly.
OK, this is this is this is stale. So I'm going to have to clear the cache because I just had that pretty sure it's because I had.
It's conflicting with the local host from the other from the other app. So I'm going to come over here.
Like we give me one second. This is the fun of the fun of demoing. Yeah. Yeah.
I guess while Matt's looking to pull it up, I guess you're like what else?
What else is top of mind for you? And you've been kind of seeing the stream hopefully a little bit the past few days, like seeing our game idea.
I'm just curious based on what you've seen so far. Like what do you think?
I think first of all, there's like like you mentioned before, this idea of like from idea to actual execution is like so it's become so much smaller now because of like the use of agents and especially with Grokbot and then also with cursor and any like a gentle coding tool.
I also when I was watching the stream, like I saw like Dr. Eggbot and then I remember it again. I remember actually.
So I visited the SpaceX office a few weeks ago and then Matt was actually I asked Matt, like what are some of the stacks you guys use or like what are some of the skills.
So he mentioned P-Stack and I like I downloaded my like completely forgot.
And then after watching the stream and I saw Dr. Edbot, I went back into it and now whenever I'm coding with cursor, I always use slash bro for pretty much everything.
It's amazing. And then I guess the other thing I'm learning is like software development has gone a lot more quick in that sense, but also means you have to pivot fast.
Like it goes back to that like sales aspect where if an idea is just like maybe an idea is like not working or maybe it's like too difficult, you should be able to pivot very quickly.
And I think when it comes to like your guys's live stream or like the SpaceX AI and team in general or like any other like promising like startup like startup slash company that's working on agents or AI and production, all of that.
Right. If you can't pivot, then you will like fall behind in that sense.
So it's like really cool how we're seeing that pivot and like all of those changes working really in the live stream. Right.
Which is just awesome to see. That's really optimistic way of explaining our last 48 hours here and kind of going through the first day and then going to the pivot.
So I appreciate that take. I also think to your point, like there's some really cool things you can do with P-Stack and then, you know, tools like this where you can actually now just like swarm agents on helping you generate and test multiple ideas in parallel.
So actually, for those who weren't watching earlier, one of the ways that we kicked off our prototyping this morning was we spun up a swarm of agents using P-Stack using different models and some different models.
Obviously, they have different tastes kind of seeing how those tastes would come together and then kind of going through a couple of those options live.
So if you want to go back and see how we did some of that, you can rewind back to the stream and catch some of the earlier content.
But we kind of went through that process a little bit iteratively.
Again, to your point, you can just spin up sub-agents, have them go, have them go figure things out and then kind of quickly see all those prototypes really quickly.
Do we ever get remotion back up?
Yeah, there was just some like basically I was using an agent to debug this. It removed like a file and then broke the wiring.
So I was just using basically for me, it's usually easier to have cursor sort of debug the situation.
The nice thing about using the browser here is that I get access to the console.
So, you know, the agent is able to kind of see the errors and the connections and start to debug these things.
But we should have something working and working shortly.
I think we might have, I don't know, do we have anything else to talk about? Where are we at?
Well, so maybe to bring it back to the game, we're just talking about that a little bit.
So right before we started this segment, I worked on finishing up our prototype and started getting the prototype wired.
We started with some basic HTML. So just like Matt was talking about, we have a lot of like a couple thousand lines of HTML and CSS embedded.
That kind of was our initial prototype. It's really snappy. It turns out modern browsers are pretty good.
But one of the things that Laura and I were talking about right off camera was let's go ahead and start converting this into a React app.
So actually this entire time that we've been working, I've had an agent working on converting our prototype into a React app that we can then wire into the back end implementation that Lauren's been working on.
So I'm pretty excited about that. It's like starting from a really strong prototype, kind of turning it into a proper front end client app, separating the client code from the server code so we can evolve the client separately and kind of be able to integrate on it.
It looks like maybe we'll have some cool graphics to go with it.
Yeah, so we got this kind of lined up a little bit more. And you can kind of see here on the right, the cool thing, several cool things, as a matter of fact.
So nice thing about remotion is that again, it's all just code. So what we did was we kind of pulled in that hero asset that we were working with a little bit earlier.
And I like this idea of like code as the source of truth, especially in content and in the creative assets, because if Lauren is back there, like, I don't know, she probably like rebuilt the entire app by now.
And the assets look different. I can just pull those assets through very quickly to this, this basically piece of content, and I'm not losing anything.
Now, don't get me wrong, there's a lot of stuff that's wrong here. But because remotion is just like react and stuff, you can see it's restarting my server.
I can even just use the design mode and just be like, get this out of there. Right. So like we can start to like clean some of this stuff up.
Like I don't want shadows or highlights on these. Like generally, I just want them to be simpler. I feel like it started adding details.
And I'd like more holistically make the card stack tighter.
So again, we talked about design mode and cursor a little bit. I love the like how tight the loop can be. And I can just kind of spam specifically models like four, six, high.
I mean, it could be low, honestly, if we're just trying to move fast. But I can spam fast mode and it'll just kind of like iterate on those things in real time.
And I get this asset where essentially this is a video. And once I get this square video that looks the way I like it, I can then just generate like portrait assets.
I can generate really whatever I want. And while a bit, you know, are you going to run an ad on this? Like, probably not.
We shouldn't be running ads on this. But if you're someone who has access to these assets and this took us five minutes, it's not like hard to see how we could then.
You know, build out this flow where in Grokbot, we're just generating different kinds of remotion ads. Right. Yeah.
I think it's also hints at like a really cool way to use agents. I think remotion is just magic. It's like such a magical tool.
But I think the reason it's so magical with agents is that it speaks code. Right. So it takes this like what you know, what is still really a laborious process to animate.
Like, you know, go into after effects. And there are people who are like really, really good at this work.
But it provides a coding interface on top of it. And I every time I see someone use remotion, I'm always a little bit blown away with an agent.
And it always sort of reminds me like you sort of got to play to the agent strength sometimes too. Right.
Like you earlier were talking about PDF formatting and text formatting. Like obviously agents are really good at text.
So you can kind of lean into that to get some leverage out of them. I think similarly, like agents are really good at code.
Like we've been talking this entire time about how, you know, like coding is cheap and it's really easy to produce code.
If you can take the act of creating graphics and motion graphics and make that like put a code, put a code interface in front of that, you're sort of like speaking the agent's language in some ways.
And so, you know, one sort of pro tip for folks who are watching and following along is, you know, think of the tools that you're using and how you could try to, you know, make code, make them code more code enabled or build sort of harnesses that involve programming on top of them.
And I think that actually helps your agents go a lot further, both in terms of what they can do, but also just in terms of like, you know, the tokens they burn and the efficiency and all that kind of stuff too.
Yeah, 100%. Yeah. And I mean, I have this like grand vision where everything is code. Like in docs, you don't have screenshots. You just have code.
The XAI and the cursor teams are already pretty good about this, but you could imagine we change the component in the product and it just flows through to our documentation or content.
Yeah, that would be happy. Oh, man. Okay, cool. So we have some ads cooking.
I love it. Thanks for joining us. This has been awesome. Really appreciate you kind of hanging out with us. Are you on X if people want to find you afterwards?
Yeah, I'm on X at shardle Marate. I think all lowercase. Nice. All right. All right. We're doing it. We're doing it actually before you get out of here.
Oh, sorry. I'm a S H A R D L. Right. Yeah. M A R A T H E A T H E. All right. This is this is for anyone who's a recruiter who's watching.
The follow up by the way. And then we're going to do it quick. We're going to do a quick profile break down because I think you know, it was actually I'm surprised we made it this far on the screen without breaking down X profile. Notice how locked in shardle is here. Like I just want you all to see my man is like we're gonna I'm gonna we're gonna clean shot. And then we're headed this gaze gaze is directly at the computer like we get arrow eyes. Oh, yeah.
There is nothing there's none of this is not looking this way. My man both laser vision on the machine. So that's that's one we get a we're not gonna save this image. Maybe for later. We'll keep it on my desktop. So first one locked in check. That's that's a plus. Second, this is a great headshot. I feel like people is just a good look guy. A lot of people that you know, they do like the A non PFP situation. I like that you're out here. You're really good.
I love that you're out here. You're repping the name. You're being just very out there with it. A plus there. We got the portfolio site. We're gonna do a portfolio. I love my I love you. I will start doing so sorry we brought you on here and then I just started going through your stuff. I'm proud of my website. I'm proud of my website. I will say that it's a trap car. There's some good stuff there though. He's like leveraging that hero photo from before. Yeah, some clear speaking engagement.
Even some more headshots actually glow Lauren. We should be so many so many stars. Okay. A plus portfolio. You should click on the projects. See what animation. Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't know if you have enough time to go into all this guys. It's telling us that I'm doing too much. It was great to have you on. Thank you so much. Thank you. We're gonna run a quick promo for those who haven't followed along yet. We are giving away a chance to win a visit to starbase.com.
Okay. I'm gonna go ahead and send it to starbase Texas so if we can cut to my screen for a minute, we'll show that very briefly on stream and then we will switch over to our next talk downstairs in the main theater. So if we can get my screen up please. Alright. So star base just share your best rockpot templates with us. This QR code, we can move our camera off of the screen for a second. We able to see the QR code hiding underneath. There you go. If you want to win a trip to star base Texas to see a launch of starship for you and a
plus one, you can scan this QR code to learn how to enter.
You've got to share your favorite Grokbot templates
with us.
And then we will have several runners up
who will win a trip to see where some of this stuff
is built that powers some of these incredible, incredible
vehicles.
So be sure to enter this.
If you missed the QR code, when we flip it off here,
you could just follow at Grok on x.
And we have some instructions on some of the latest posts
on that account, too.
Share by September 29, and we'd love
to see some really great templates.
With that, I think we're going to cut downstairs
to the main stage for our next talk.
I'm Simon.
I'm here on SpaceX AI's Go-To-Market team,
specifically in SDR.
And excited to talk about Grokbot.
So, I'm going to talk about Grok Bot specifically for this team. So, at a high level, we'll be going over what actually is Grok Bot, why we use it internally, and then dive into some of the actual SDR use cases we use.
And then I'll demo what my environment looks like, and then we can discuss that and go into the Q&A from there.
So, first at a high level, I wanted to kind of discuss the actual AI maturity curve and what this looks like for SDRs. So, starting out, when I was using AI, I was just prompting back and forth with a chatbot.
I do typical things, like I'd ask, can you help me actually draft this email, or kind of perfect this copy, or do this account research for this specific account I'm looking at.
And what we've seen kind of progress over the last year is first the idea of co-pilots. And so, co-pilots are AI that can actually go out and carry out a true task.
So, instead of talking back and forth, getting email copied, and then copying that into your Gmail, it's something now that we see, like, actually having the AI go and basically hook up to a Gmail MCP or an API and be able to actually send that email off for you.
And really with Bot, what we believe is kind of the next frontier, is actually automating entire jobs in full. And so, going beyond just a task and actually doing an end-to-end workflow.
And really with the staff function of actually combining a team of bots, you can see how kind of automating a job, but also combining that with different features of business, like talking to RevOps or talking to your AE and getting context on an account,
and how bots can actually pull in that context for you and really help you do that full process.
And so, just diving into what RockBot actually looks like, if you haven't seen it before. So, you have all your bots kind of here on the left-hand side. And they're doing different things, like we have a sales outbound bot here, we have our chief of staff,
and you can message them just like you message your own teammates. And more interestingly, you can actually see them talk with each other.
And I have my own RockBot instance set up, where really there's only one bot that I'm actually talking to. And so, for the most part, I've kind of offloaded all that context to my chief of staff actually talking with other bots and doing that all for me.
And I think some important things also to emphasize here is that bots keep their own context at a per bot level and memory, so they can really improve as you work more with them, as you go, their memory gets better.
And this is why I really emphasize you actually should be training your bots as well, depending on the task with kind of the relevant info. So, set up your Slack, set up your Gmail connector, and you can actually kind of start to train it on what your voice looks like.
And so, specifically for Gmail, what I do is I've had it go into my Gmail and actually look at how do I actually talk to people? And specifically in my outbound messages, how do I actually talk to people in a way where they actually want to respond and they're interested in kind of seeing a demo for something full of people?
And so, I'll really go into more of what that actually looks like, how I place weights on certain things to actually help Grokbot understand this. But I think a big thing I want to talk about also is the ability to share your bots.
And I'll dive into this more in the next slide. But I think as SDRs, one of the most important things is being able to see what your teammates are actually doing and to kind of easily transfer those skills over to your other SDRs.
And so, you can actually really scale those outputs and do it very quickly. I think the truth, at least in SpaceX, of what we've seen is that what's working for us today was not working three months ago.
And three months before that, it was something entirely different. And so, the ability to really just move quickly and always be iterating is something that the ability to share bots is really going to help you with and help scale the entire SDR team.
So, diving into this more, like why are we using Grokbot? I think to start, it's as easy and as intuitive as just iMessage or another general platform. You can just talk to your bots.
And I think, more importantly, bots are always on. And so, you don't have to walk around with your laptop open anymore. You can actually close it. I can go on coffee walks and continue prompting for my phone.
Or I can set it up on a long-running task and then trust that it will actually complete that task end-to-end and do the thing without me having to kind of object in between and guide it.
It really is the confidence to go carry out and do things. And there's many ways you can actually improve that by recording your own screen and some other stuff that I'll show more in the demo.
But again, it also uses the tools, just like you do. And so, you can think of your basic connectors of MCPs, of APIs, everything that you've already kind of set up.
But beyond that, what's really important is it actually owns its own VM. And so, you can log into the browser. And for the parts of your SDR work that are a little more difficult or there's no real way to automate them, you can actually show bot in the browser.
You can sign in to those tools. And you can actually show bot by recording your screen. Recording you go through it, you can show the exact workflows that you do in there.
The really tedious and specific stuff that's kind of hard to explain or maybe there's no real, like, open API for it.
And so, this is really something that I found immense value in. And what's given me the confidence to be able to say, okay, GrokBot, you can genuinely go end to end with what you're doing here.
And as I talked about before, I think shareable templates are one of the most important things. And I think every single team at a team level should basically all be spending time building their own templates, sharing those with the team, getting understanding of, okay, what are the things that are actually working?
And how can I not only just import that template, but how can I import it and then add my own nuance onto that of whatever, like, my tonality and my messaging is, or actually maybe it's just I like to do my workflow a slightly different way.
But actually kind of taking this as a base template and then working beyond that. And you can also prompt GrokBot directly and ask for direct improvements.
So, you can import templates and be like, hey, look at this template my colleague shared with me. What do you think are things with my own workflow that you think would be a good addition to build on top of this or to kind of get more value out of that?
And so, I really emphasize just actually like talking back and forth with your GrokBots and kind of like starting to really push it to help you. And I think this is why we emphasize so heavily that GrokBot is really just a multiplier for your own work and really a way to scale the outputs you're doing.
And as an SDR, I don't think there's anything more important than actually doing that.
All right, so diving into really what I see as the common SDR use cases are the things that like I'm doing on a day to day basis. I think number one, it's really prospecting.
And so if you're an early stage startup, you can actually even have GrokBot kind of help you understand your ICP.
And so you can look into things like, okay, for the AEs that have closed deals or have deals that have moved to stage one.
What is the common kind of title that we're seeing actually carry those deals through?
Or what's kind of the most responsive title or industry or sub-industry of person to take an original meeting?
How does that actually vary from economic buyer, the person who's actually signing off on this deal?
And so you can really GrokBot kind of from a first beginning actually understand like, what is my ICP? What's the most often way to reach my goal?
And personally as an SDR for me, that's how many S1s can I get?
And so you can kind of reverse engineer from that point and GrokBot can kind of help you actually get to that point.
And so on top of really just understanding that ICP within prospecting, you can do the full flow.
So you can use enrichment tools, set those up within GrokBot.
You can also use web search to kind of find more specific data like job postings or any funding announcements from some of your target companies and really just bring this all in.
And I'll show how I can actually tie that into my next point, which is a sequencer.
And so really what I've done within my own GrokBot instance is I built kind of an ongoing list of all my prospects.
And this lives as a CSV today.
But really what I think is nuanced about this is you can have things like GrokBot routines and automations, which are constantly updating this.
And I think something that's really been a big value add on the sense of sequencing is the fact that when I'm multi-threading an account,
my AD might have a call with them and that might have happened yesterday.
And whatever the context from that call is, is truly golden and it should shape my messaging for today.
And so what GrokBot can do is it can actually take that context in just like a coworker would.
They can go, hey, your AD spoke with this person yesterday.
Here's exactly what they mentioned.
They mentioned a real pain point is they have all these tools to choose from and they kind of just feel stressed out.
There's tool fatigue.
There's AI fatigue.
And really that should shape your messaging for that day going forward for that company.
And GrokBot has that context and it can pull that in and help you actually tailor messages at a company level.
And maybe even in a Gongcall or a recording they mentioned, oh, you know what?
Like this is actually the exact thing that Simon on the AI team is investigating right now or looking into.
You should reach out to him.
But a lot of those things never actually get actioned on.
And so GrokBot has the ability to actually really sequence and kind of do the full process of prospecting them, adding them into the sequence just off of the actual context.
And so GrokBot has that meaning they had with your AI.
And I think that's something really nuanced that I haven't seen before.
And on that same note, you can also do very high level account research.
And so for PLG led companies, you can look at all the internal data of, okay, who are my power users?
Who's actually using this product?
And more than that, you can look at the external signals for all companies in whole.
So, okay, who's fundraising?
Who is job postings?
And how does that kind of tailor the messaging based on our product?
And you can also look at things internally, like, okay, how does this new product that we've launched actually change our outbounding message for a specific person in XYZ industry?
And really have GrokBot kind of tailor those messaging to each and every company specific.
And that's actually diving into my last point as well, which is drafting copy and what that looks like.
And so what I really highly emphasize is you actually sync your email with GrokBot just as kind of a starting point.
And really push GrokBot to understand your tone.
And I think some of the nuances that I've added on this, because it's very easy to just sync your email, but you have to kind of push it further.
And the first thing that I've done on that note is I said, listen, look specifically at my email copy that I've sent out to external or third party companies that also match the Salesforce account where I'm an assigned SDR.
And then from that point, what I actually am pushing it to do, it's also look at, okay, just look at any of the emails from that filtered list that actually got positive responses that didn't get negative responses.
And then I think the most important thing that I've done on top of that note is I've actually put a heavier weight on emails that recently have received positive responses.
And I think for a company like SpaceX, what we're always seeing is the product offerings always changing.
And I think that's what I said, what was working three months ago is completely different now and might not work today.
And so I pushed GrokBot to put a really heavy emphasis on the actual recent messages and to draft my copy more like that, but still kind of pull in inspiration from my older messaging to understand like kind of the human aspect of actually what I'm doing.
And so these are kind of the real SDR use cases that I've seen, but I'll show you more in my demo of kind of how we can expand much beyond this.
On a different level, I just wanted to first show what does my GrokBot team actually look like here?
And so what I've really been emphasizing is you should have a chief of staff.
And I think one of the most exhausting things for me is switching back and forth between my different bots.
I'm always kind of forgetting the context, especially if I'm kind of shuffling many, many things at once.
And so what I actually really recommend is you have a chief of staff and that should be the first spot that you set up.
And what you should actually do from that point is set up all your other bots through your chief of staff.
And the reason being is when you do it this way, your chief of staff just has context on exactly the purpose and the end goal of that bot.
And so as you kind of ask your chief of staff, so Simon bot here for me, to complete tasks, it understands the right bot to actually delegate that to.
And when needed, it's going to understand the context of multiple bots that it needs to delegate to or actually get to talk with each other.
And so I think this is really an important way to actually think from the beginning of how to set this up.
And just for my other bots here, you can see. So I've got Shakespeare here, who is really the one I've like very meticulously trained on my email writing skills.
And then I have Web Search, which obviously is just doing web research.
He actually works in parallel with my Simon soldier. Now I'll show you, I basically have an entire army of Simon soldiers, which I basically consider sub agents or sub bots that when Web Search wants to delegate a task across a 50 or 100 counts.
The scalable way to do that is actually creating sub bots that basically respond directly to Web Search.
Lastly, I have customer bot who does a few things, but really is just taking in all the context on the meetings I'm having understanding for deals that are moving to close one kind of what's the context?
What are the things that customers are really receptive to? And you can also get really nuanced with this.
So I think something you can do is look in Salesforce and say, okay, I have an account that's in the fintech vertical.
Okay, let me understand. Let me talk with my customer bot or ask my chief of staff to actually talk to the customer bot and figure out, okay, what are the similar fintech companies that are closed one in recent deals?
And why were they interested? What were the main pain points they had? What were the main parts of a product that were actually relevant?
And then I'm going to take that context and I'm actually going to have my chief of staff pass that off to Shakespeare to understand my email drafting and to push that in specifically for the fintech companies we serve.
And so this is where I really push that you can have these all as kind of your entire staff working on different parts of your outbound to make it genuinely productive.
All right, so now let's dive into the demo and see actually what my setup looks like here.
So here we've got it at a high level. I'm very serious about my color coding, as you can see here, but I promise I have a reason behind this.
And that's I really like to understand at a high level when my bots are talking to each other, and especially because all my work is delegated from my actual chief of staff.
I need to understand who my chief of staff is talking to at a section level. And so whenever I see the orange here, I know that my chief of staff is working on an actual research mission.
It's doing something around research. When I see that it's message Shakespeare here, I know that it's doing some sort of outbound copy drafting.
And it's kind of starting to understand that. And the same here, I've talked about my army here, but when I see the green messages, I understand, okay, it's delegating account research.
It's splitting these up between sub bots. And you can actually see here, I have an army huddle as well, which basically has my web search bot talking with all of the soldiers here and basically just ordering them around.
And the soldiers are just giving all the context they need. And so you can see I'm researching kind of this demo account fly low here.
But you can see how it's basically broken all this up. And so now, oh, yeah, yeah, for sure. Good. All right.
So now what I really want to show is actually how I'm enriching prospects, how I'm actually going and sequencing these people, and also what my daily routines look like.
Because I think personally as an SDR, one of the most important things for me is waking up every morning and knowing very much what I'm actually going to work on for that day.
I think that's just having assigned tasks that you wake up to is extremely helpful to start with. And so really what I've done here on my routines on the side here.
So the number one most important thing for me is every day I want 50 new prospects. And really, these prospects have their own kind of internal rankings that I've been working on.
And so typically, how I break this up is I have five prospects that I need to action on first thing in the morning. These are going to be the most relevant ones.
So maybe it was someone who contacted sales, but nobody ever reached out to them. Maybe it was someone who just downloaded some of our content that's extremely relevant to what they're doing in conversations we're already having with that account.
And basically, this is my first five people that I genuinely need to action on right away. And what I have is you can actually set up Grokbot to things like your calendar.
So my chief of staff was access to my calendar, and it can basically understand the context of, okay, this is the five things you need action on now.
You have a 15 minute block I can make for you during this time, maybe 9am. So you can actually just knock those out of the way then you don't have any other meetings.
For the 45 others that I know you want to get to today, I'll block off time at 1pm. So you can actually carry those out over another hour.
But really, my chief of staff has kind of started to understand how I actually like to kind of break up my time and what's most important and really how I've seen the most results here.
And so on the same basis, I have an inbox manager who does something very similar. So I get Slack messages that I wake up to every morning.
I'm added to meetings when I wake up every morning, and I have external emails that I wake up to every morning.
And I really just need a simple way to actually understand which of these I should action on right away, which of these are most important.
And so with a similar system, this is actually just going and it's really just ranking these for me on ones to action on and what the order to actually do that is.
So on the same basis as a PLG company, something that's really important to us is actually looking through all of our accounts for some of the signals.
So where are power users living? What are the products they're using? What are the things they're actually using the products for that are most relevant?
And so I also have every single weekday. And you can see all these are 8am.
I have all of my accounts basically getting scanned for any net new signals. So who are the new people who actually signed up for our product?
Who are the new people who have reached out, downloaded content, like everything?
And I really like this because I think speed delete is one of the most important things.
And so even if it's not the strongest signal, being fed that on a daily basis so you can actually just go and action on that while it's as warm as possible has led me to some of the most receptive responses I've gotten.
And so finishing out here, I have my sequencer. And I think just an important nuance on my sequencer is that I also have a routine basically set on a Salesforce trigger.
So any time one of my accounts, the actual account status updates. So maybe it's moving from stage zero to stage one.
This is basically a trigger that works in parallel with the sequence to unsequence people when maybe the deal is moving forward and we don't need to outbound any more people.
So this is really a way you can kind of set up these kind of elaborate systems all just with routines and with Grokbot itself.
But I'm going to dive in now to what my actual sequencer looks like here.
And so here's here's kind of what it looks like. I've spun up this demo one here.
And so you can see it's all saved as a CSV, which I will admit is like a hideous UI.
And it's like very painful to look at as a user.
And I think what my big emphasis here is you actually as a user shouldn't be looking at this much, if at all.
This should kind of just be Grokbot's brain and some systematic way to actually track these.
But you should genuinely trust Grokbot to actually have the context and only look into it when you actually really need to.
And so you can see here, I have all these different sequences, a queue of prospects where I actually need to be at in, my prospect board.
And then the most important stuff for me is the things I need to action on this specific day.
And so you can see this basically gives me all the things.
It's also drafting copy for the emails and everything.
You can see here, it's already got Gmail drafts ID.
So I can basically just go into my Gmail and review these all one by one.
And if I wanted to, I can just talk to my chief of staff and I can be like, can you actually give me a score on how confident are you that this email is accurate, that it's solid,
that they might actually give a response.
And this is kind of what I've delegated it to at this point.
I think I really emphasize that first, and especially as you're kind of training it on your voice to actually like thoroughly look at these and honestly give it feedback.
But it's now at a point where I somewhat just trust it and I can actually push it to give me its own rating scores on how good these are.
But I think on that note, something important to emphasize when you're focusing on your copy.
So this could be Gmail.
This could be for any other platform is what I've found works best is actually just prompting back and forth with Crockbot and asking it for examples.
And so honestly, when I first had it pull in my emails, now you even did all this stuff.
Okay, like let's wait the more recent responses.
I found that it was almost kind of templated and every response looked very similar, but just with swapping of names of company IDs, things like that.
And so what I've really done is just kept going back and forth and asking, can you give me examples of these emails?
And then on each one, basically critiquing it, being like, this is why this email sucks.
And here's how you can make it better.
And really pushing for it to break out of kind of the standardized formatting it has and to actually kind of think and give nuanced responses at each single email.
And I think something I really push is not a single one of your emails should look like a template.
It shouldn't look like the same thing, but just swapping out company or name.
And I think that's something really important to also push here.
So I'm going to dive now into actually like why I structured my setup this way and what this actually looks like.
And so obviously, I'm my chief of staff at the top.
And as I said, this is actually the only bot I talked to and the one that I built the rest of my bots from.
And so obviously, I have all my outbound actually just structured in a single folder.
And the reason I did this is I make one bot basically per platform.
And I think the important reason to do this is because you should be thinking about bots as a way of things that can run in parallel.
And so Shakespeare is doing all my email.
And so I don't need a second email bot, but I might need a second outbound bot for a second platform that I'm reaching out to people on.
Or maybe I need context for some of the calls I'm doing.
And so having different bots for each of those different functions, I think, is the best way to actually handle this and understand the context of how your bots are working with each other.
And then so diving into my research here, so kind of the six key bots that I'm actually using for this.
One, I have my PLG bot, which is tied up to Salesforce.
So I'm actually getting to see, OK, who's who's signing up?
What does our usage look like?
It's also pulling in stuff like, do we have any closed loss?
It's also talking with other bots.
And so Chief of Staff might be able to recognize that, OK, one of our prospect accounts is a closed loss opportunity.
OK, what's the context on why?
Well, let's dig in the voice of the customer bot, understand the reasons why that opportunity closed loss.
OK, maybe we didn't have support for a critical function for the business then.
But actually, as we've been updating, Chief of Staff recognizes that now we actually do support that.
It's seen some of the closed ones come in directly around that.
And so that will actually then take this prospect or take this account and start ranking them higher in my sequencing.
Because it's saying this is more urgent because you need to reengage with them about this direct thing that they truly care about.
And we know that from a call we had with them.
And so being able to take that context and kind of have this full system running together, I think is extremely important.
But as we tie into this more, you can see I also have ample market, which kind of runs all our enrichment.
So once we actually find prospects, this is how we actually hook up our tools to get their emails and to understand, OK, is this actually their email?
Can we test it?
Make sure it won't bounce.
Things like that that won't hurt your email deliverability scores.
And then on top of that, I have a company research bot, which I think is something very important here.
And so I have this hooked up to my symbol instance.
And what some was actually able to do the most important thing that I found is it's able to pull in a company's tech stack.
So for SpaceX's products, it's really important to understand, OK, this company is really operating with a legacy software stack.
And they're looking to kind of move off that.
Like, here's the pain points we see from similar people.
And here's how we can kind of aim the messaging around that.
And on top of that, some people can actually pull in job postings, too.
And so that's actually how it understands tech stack.
But more than that, it can actually try and pull in for you an understanding on their org chart.
So if you're selling, say, for GrokBot into a go-to-market org,
someone can actually help you pull in information on, OK, here's actually the leader for maybe their SDR team.
The person would be interested in this.
And it's pushing all that context back into GrokBot.
And it's pushing it all back into the system and this understanding.
And again, back to the voice of the customer bot.
Maybe they said, oh, yes, Simon on the SDR go-to-market team is looking into these exact things.
And it can talk with other bots like our company research bot here.
Pull that context back in of who exactly that is, where they sit in the org chart,
and help you actually sequence that and rank that based on, here's how high they are up in the company they are.
Like, are they the economic buyer based on stuff like that?
And so really, you can kind of have these all work together.
And again, I think this goes back to the point of the importance of building all your bots from your chief of staff bot
is it understands this context better.
And it understands it just like you would.
And so moving forward here, I've kind of talked a lot about the voice of the customer bot.
But I think a cool one here also that I use is web search bot.
So I'm constantly looking at company fundings or like I said earlier, like job postings
or any kind of public facing information, things in the news.
And what I've really found is a friction point with this is it's hard to scale this.
And you have 100 to 200 accounts.
And every single day, there's updates on some of these.
And so how do we actually like scan for this at scale?
So I've set up my web search bot here, which is hooked up to XA.
And what I actually do have is an army for it that can actually break up and delegate this work.
And so you can see I kind of talked about this earlier, but I have an army huddle, huddle,
which is basically just one bot telling the other bots, OK, we're going to break up these 200 companies to 40 each.
Now run in parallel to actually do web search on all of these.
So we can actually get this information back to Simon in a timely manner.
And this is something I've really seen as like a practical way to scale some of the long running tasks
and some of the ones that really have slowed down some of my workflows in the short term.
And so this has really helped me kind of stay on top of those things.
And so kind of on top of that, also, we're looking at usage for PLG companies.
We're looking into how much are people using this product?
What teams are using this product?
And I think for Grokba, it's something important.
We're trying to understand like how many go to market people are using it and what are kind of the use cases they have.
So being able to pull in data like that too and have my chief of staff actually understand all that context
makes it all the more easy to actually like kind of rank every single prospect, understand priorities
and understand really like who are the best targets to go after.
Because I think it's so easy to be overwhelmed as an SDR with all these different tasks and all these different things you have to do.
And it's really hard to kind of mentally try and try and understand and rank these different prospects.
And so I think having some sort of like systematic ranking here with Grokba as I've kind of built myself is a really good way to do this.
And like I said earlier, I think a really nice part of this is you can actually share these with your team.
And so you can get the learnings and kind of share those learnings.
And I think one last thing I just wanted to show here is I've actually built some skills that kind of go deeper here.
And so I actually have a entire just prospecting skill.
And so our company here is Flylo, but we can just we can just type this in.
And so prospecting understands already all of the different things I want.
And this is more something at this point I just run for one off maybe net new accounts I have or things I want to research like midway through the day.
But most of this runs at routines at this point.
But I think something very interesting that I also want to talk about is the skill I've made around Grokba ICP.
And I think this is something that's really widely applicable here.
And what this is is we're still figuring out all the different use cases for Grokba.
And we're not sure really like who the best ICP and what that looks like.
And it's really something that's kind of an ongoing development.
And so what I wanted to do here is I wanted to turn our own findings on Grokba ICP into a skill.
And I did this because this way I can constantly update this as it kind of gets more and more clear what this actually means.
And so obviously it's something I've talked with Grokba before about.
OK, let's see. What are the deals for Grokba that are actually moving past stage one that are showing interest?
What are the things from voice of the customer bot that are showing interest around this?
And why are they interested in this?
And this has really helped me kind of iterate on the skill more and more.
And I think it's something that really I want to keep building out.
And the reason I've kept it as a skill though is because it could drastically change.
And I want it to be able to be flexible and be something that my systems can basically call upon at any point.
And it's updated. So as we kind of iron out more and more what Grokba's ICP is,
we can really change this on the fly if we save it as a skill here.
And so basically I can run that in the background and you can kind of see some of the high level stuff it's going to do.
But really it's I do all my work and it kind of oriented all around CSPs that look like this that are pulling and everything like titles.
What's their actual...
ICP persona, the owners and everything, what's the context on why?
And then you can see it's talking to other sources, like Ample Market, to actually get
email data, LinkedIn, locations here, and really just a lot of the context on these profiles.
And you can see that it's already basically running and doing something like this.
But really, really at a high level, this is how I actually run all of my sequencing here.
You can see that now it's messaging all of my orange bots.
And I think just for my own sanity, it's very clear now that it's in the research phase.
And I understand that.
I think now, boom, it's doing web search in the background.
And I'm very clear in understanding on exactly what it's doing there.
And that's, I think, why it's important to kind of actually do these somewhat color-coded
fashion, or maybe some themes.
It's easy to remember and to actually kind of at a high level look down and see what's happening.
But all right, that is the demo.
And so now I'm kind of just going to discuss what we actually learn, what I think are genuinely
the takeaways that you guys should have and carry into your own setups for this, this SDRs.
All right, so I think one of the most important things is going end-to-end.
And this is something I hope I showed in my demo, but that I'm really trying to push,
is that it's very simple to just prompt back and forth with Grokbot,
or to have Grokbot do a single task, like sending an email for you.
But I think really you should push it to do the entire workflow.
And it's a lot of pain up front for you to prompt back and forth, to build this system,
to figure out what actually makes this system work.
But if you stick through it and you're persistent and you train it on your style,
you will get so much more benefit when it's able to go end-to-end,
when it's able to pull people in from prospecting, it's able to enrich them,
it's able to understand all the context, and then it's able to push that out
and actually outbound them and do the full process.
And I think that's really what differentiates Grokbot
and what makes it a true force multiplier for SDRs.
So I really emphasize thinking at a high level
and kind of thinking how you can actually build that system.
And I think on that same note, you should be intentional here.
So it's really intuitive to just prompt each bot.
And what I highly recommend is just taking a step back and thinking,
OK, let me build this all through my actual chief of staff.
Bots should be able to talk to each other.
They should have that context.
The point of this is to offload more work from you
and help you actually get higher outputs.
And so you shouldn't actually be focusing even harder
and messaging even more bots.
It's exhausting from just all the prompt and context switching
you're doing there.
And lastly, what I kind of hope I really show in my demo
is how to think systematically about your setup.
I think it is very easy to just always want to make new bots.
It's kind of fun and it's kind of exciting.
But as someone who's built an army of bots,
I promise you I've had way too many at some points.
And it's honestly more chaotic and it does more harm than good.
And so you should really be questioning,
why is it important that a new bot does this?
Why can my existing email bot not just write my emails
and also be able to be my inbox manager?
Why do I need a second bot for that?
And also on that note, when should I just turn things
into routines that that bot runs?
But really, I emphasize kind of thinking
about all these different things as ways for you
to actually just save more tokens in the first place,
but actually just also not confuse yourself
and not kind of just get overloaded with bots
that are just doing kind of similar things.
And again, making these through your chief of staff
makes it all the more easier to actually do that.
All right, so I just wanted to thank you guys
for taking the time.
And I think we're going to just open it up to questions now
here.
Go for it.
Yeah, so you had a daily routine for 50 prospects
and 50 leads, right?
So if you keep running the same workflow every day,
approximately what sort of consumption
from a token perspective do you see for this?
And do you have any numbers that you could share
like per day, per week kind of thing,
like what that translates to into a dollar amount
or anything like that?
So the question is, how many tokens
does it kind of consume to run these on a daily basis?
And I think it very much depends, and it's hard to say.
And I think the best way to actually do it
is you kind of have to see what it looks like
for your own instance, because it depends on kind of the amount
of maybe gone calls you're pulling from,
the amount of context you have in your Databricks instance.
And also on top of that, how many prospects
do you need to freshly enrich versus how many
are kind of old contexts that you're pulling in
from Salesforce that you already have context on?
So I think it very much depends.
It also depends at the scale you're running this on.
But I think the best way to kind of do this
is honestly like prompt back and forth with Grokbot,
get an understanding of where your token usage is at.
And you can also talk back and forth with Grokbot
to find ways to optimize your workflow.
So maybe 50 daily prospects isn't something practical
depending on the scale of outbound you're doing.
Like maybe it makes more sense to actually run
250 on a weekly basis, and that just sends
on a Monday morning, and then you have that
to work through the whole week.
I think mine might be just a little more daily
because I like pulling in all that context
and really like pushing Grokbot as hard as I can.
And I think I'm just using a little more tokens
doing that, but yeah, I highly recommend
just trying it out on that front.
Yeah, go for it.
First of all, thank you so much for a great demo
and the presentation.
It's really fascinating to see the actual,
the use case from your own workflow.
So I think that part of your demo,
I think I saw you kind of have a group chat
among your boards.
So I'm curious, where do you see the benefit
of creating that kind of the group chat
because you already have a chief of staff
already connected all of your boards.
So what is the use case that you found
like it's more beneficial?
And my second question is,
I really like the naming of the Simon Soldier.
But so I think the other, like the orange boards
were pretty intuitive for me
regarding what their like the role each of them is.
But I'm just curious, what is the Soldier Board for you?
And then how do you use it for your workflow?
Yeah, so I built my soldiers really just as like,
okay, like these are my troopers that I'm gonna send out
to go do web research in general.
And I think the reason I put them in a group chat
instead of actually like setting them up
just as messaging my chief of staff directly
is one, I think it's easier to see the outputs come back
to my actual web search bot.
So I can actually go in there and make sure
that outputs at each of the subagents
is somewhat accurate and is flowing correctly.
And I think on top of that, it's much easier
if I wanted to scale that from five people in my army
to 20 or something.
It's much easier to scale that if I have my web search bot
basically handing off the context
and all those subagents really have like low context.
And so it's very easy just in that way
to scale that up or down on a whim.
And so that's kind of like why I thought
of doing it that way.
Sorry, I might've missed it, but like,
I guess like, so if you, let's say you come in, right?
And you create a chief of staff bot,
can you then just task the chief of,
like just show what like your work is
or what you need to be doing?
And then the chief of staff like spins up
the appropriate number of bots automatically.
And where do these subagents kind of come in?
I guess like, because I think when I come in,
sorry, you were saying like,
you should think about work being done in parallel
and show there should be different bots
for things being done in parallel,
but that's difficult for like a user
perhaps to think about.
Unless I guess maybe you just really know that job very well,
but it could be different every time.
But what's like the way to just get going really quickly
where just the time to value is minimized
as if someone just comes in,
just wants to set up for me based on best practices.
Perfect, I'll answer this quickly
and then I think we're gonna go back
to live stream upstairs.
But I think at a high level,
really just talking back and forth with Grokbot
when some of this stuff is extremely overwhelming.
I think Grokbot can actually help you understand
what a practical setup is.
And if you just kind of talk it at a high level
of what your actual workflow looks like and what that is,
it can really help you kind of divide up
when it makes sense to use new bots.
And I think that's kind of the easiest way
to kind of answer that broadly
for all the different use cases.
Just one quick, they hand me the mic.
For Zav, I love the Simon soldiers.
I was telling everyone at dinner last night
about my beautiful, beautiful, sweet Grokbots.
And I call them all soldiers for Christ.
Oh, right on.
Because they march forward on my behalf.
All right, welcome back.
We are back here in our studio,
back on the stream,
back with some updates on what we've been building.
If we can get my screen up on the slides
or on the stream here,
wanted to make sure you all could see that slide
that we flashed up at the end of that talk.
So you could scan that QR code if you haven't already.
While we get my screen up,
if you want to win some free Grokbot, you can.
Follow these steps to get a free month of Grokbot
for $200 in value.
So it's a pretty big free month at our highest tier.
If you duplicate and create a bot with Dr. Eggbot,
so go get the Dr. Eggbot template,
create a bot with Dr. Eggbot,
and go through the experience of installing Dr. Eggbot
into your own Grokbot instance.
If you do that on stream, following this QR code,
the first 1000 users who go through this
will get a free month of Grokbot
to be able to do all the things that we've been doing
and much, much more, $200 in value.
It's a lot of credits, it's a lot of usage,
and we're really excited to give you all a chance
to kind of do a little bit of what we've been doing.
If you haven't had a chance to try Grokbot already,
great way to get your feet wet with a lot of credits.
And it's an exclusive on stream offer,
so now's your chance, grab it before it's gone.
Okay, well, welcome back.
We are working on our business here.
We've been spending the last few days
working on building a gaming business in a game studio.
And for those who haven't been following along
since, I don't know how many hours it's been,
we are some number of hours.
Yeah, it's like almost over two days into this process,
but the plans are starting to come together.
We've had a lot of fun guests on today.
A few of us have been peeling off
to go work on some of the builds in the background too,
and so we've been really excited to make some progress,
show you guys what we've been up to.
I've got a few bots that we're gonna cook up
and kind of walk through some demos on today.
Where do we leave things off?
So I think what I did while during our last break
was I spent some time taking the prototype that we built
and turning it into a Next.js React app
with some placeholders for the server side
that we're gonna build.
So we're gonna kind of split out the client
and the server app into separate apps
so that we can evolve those things independently.
And Lauren, you were sharing a little bit
about how this is gonna make it much easier
for us to rev on the client, right?
Yeah, I mean, I think for the client
and I mean for a competitive game like this,
you do want to have a server that is deciding
the things so like people,
you can just modify the client and cheat.
So I think that will be a good thing.
We'll have off as well set up.
And I'm still not 100% sure on what the client
will look like.
I think like this, what we have with the web version
looks fine so far, but it makes me wonder
if like maybe we should, it'd be interesting
to get a few bots started up maybe with Dr. Eggbot
and then maybe even prototyping
different versions of the client.
Now that we have a backend, like we can have multiple clients.
Well, I don't think we'll have multiple clients
at launch, but for us to iterate.
Because maybe there is an interesting 3D version
or I don't know, a pixel art version.
Get the Blender MCP involved.
Terminal client.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, what's cool about this is yeah,
now that we've kind of separated these things,
we can have the server maintain the state
and then just like follow the server contract
that we've established with that API
and go and let the client prototype a little bit.
We've added a few new features.
We have a global leaderboard here.
It's obviously not fully wired in.
So these are all just fun names for now,
but hopefully be able to get that.
So once you guys are into the game,
we're gonna have a leaderboard.
And then I'm actually excited to get something launched
in the next few hours.
So what I was thinking is maybe to help us
make some progress is let's start kind of tracking
all the things we need to do.
So I have my chief of staff bot here
and I'm gonna ask my chief of staff bot
to get our notion.going that has our to-do list
and then help us keep an eye on it
so we can track all of our ongoing tasks together.
We've all been dumping some stuff into notion.
I think as we go, Lauren, I think you have a great,
you know, a game design bot.
I spun up a game designer bot to do some research on,
well, I think like our game mechanics
are pretty simple right now.
So I got Dr. Eggbot to make me a new bot
to do, I guess, game research.
So it looked at some other battle games
for interesting mechanics and interesting features
for us to be inspired by.
And I got it to write a notion doc
that's not wired up to anything right now.
It's just a standalone doc,
but it'd be interesting to have like a,
you know, as we start to build out
the game studio business,
start just thinking about like operationally,
you know, like how do we actually keep each other
informed of what we're doing?
And like, it could be nice to have a notion doc
that's just tracking all of the work
we're doing on the project.
We don't really, I guess we do have a deadline, right?
We have some milestones we want to hit.
So it'd be good to actually start tracking.
Yeah, let's do it.
I have my chief over here working on that.
And then we have my founding engineer, Bake,
who's been keeping an eye on all the PRs
that have been coming into the repo.
So we have a bunch of PRs that we've been shipping
and I kind of have this,
my bot over here is,
well, let's see if I can pull this up the right way,
is yeah, watching the repo.
So you can see there's some GitHub,
kind of, you know, integrations tied in here
where anytime a new PR is opened or changed,
I'm getting notified about it in my bot.
So that's been really helpful for me to see on top
of all the changes Lauren's been making.
We've been dual merging here.
So I'm kind of making changes to the client,
Lauren's been making changes to the server and backend.
And so you can see I got some updates here,
which is great.
And then my bots are messaging each other
to put together this plan.
So as soon as we have that,
I'll pop up a notion page
and hopefully we can get that going
and look at it together.
Maybe just like pin it to the chat over,
pin it to the stream over here.
So we have our early task list.
Yeah, it'd be good maybe like to even have it on the side.
And then you can have like half of your screen notion,
half of it go off bot.
Yeah, let's do that.
And we can kind of like try to burn down the tasks
as much as possible.
What do you think are the main ones?
We can help steer the agent here a little bit.
We need to...
Well, for sure.
Like I have to get the backend shipped and deployed.
Do you want to do the client thing?
Actually, I don't know if we should.
Maybe we'll just keep it web for now
because web would be the easiest.
Yeah.
I guess we could maybe try like a 3D version.
Oh yeah.
For the animations maybe.
Just to see.
And maybe just not make that a blocking task.
That can be like a little side quest
for one bot to go and just try.
And if we like it, we can take it.
If not, we'll just scrap it.
And then I think it'd be really good
to maybe make some progress
on just thinking through the ad stuff.
I know we kind of briefly talked about it.
I don't really know what our plans are for that yet.
Yeah, we can think about it.
So it'd be good to...
We had a cool remotion prototype.
We have a remotion for actually running some ads.
Yeah, all nice.
Cool, cool.
So we have some assets.
We can think about if we have this stadium theoretically
that the bots are in.
Right, right.
Number one, what does the space look like?
And then two, how do we...
The question would be like,
okay, how do we sell these things?
How do we account for that?
And then which ad should we choose?
Is it like a marketplace for ads?
Are we just selling definitive slots?
How do we price those?
So I think that's like some exploration
to think through the framework,
but then also we can just start to build out that system
since we have server, right?
Yeah. Cool.
Okay, I got those captured as we were talking.
So I'll get those into the Notion dock
and hopefully we should be able to pull that up
on the second here, if I micro window.
Where is my...
Here we go, working to do this.
See if you can...
Maybe ask your bot to share this dock with us.
Oh yeah.
On Slack, ping us on Slack.
And actually something I haven't set up yet
that I usually do is to have a kind of like a Slack manager bot
that kind of like watches for pings
and then it can kind of, I'll just tell it to like,
hey, you know, every time we do a task,
update the Notion.
That's great.
Maybe we can all do that.
Yeah.
Get a...
Oh, you want to try something fun?
Why don't we all turn on voice mode at the same time
and create the same bot?
I think that could be really cool.
Should we try it?
Sure.
Let's all open up our dock here at the bottom.
Wait, who's gonna do the prompt?
Why don't you do it?
Slackbot or your Slack idea.
Okay, okay.
All right, so on three, we hit start on voice mode.
Wait, which bot are you on now?
Are you on Dr. Eggbot?
Eggbot, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
So we'll talk addressing Dr. Eggbot.
Yep.
Ready?
Okay, go.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, hello, Dr. Eggbot.
We are interested in building a Slackbot.
So the job of the Slackbot will be to listen
for at mentions of our username on Slack.
And process them.
So there might be things like,
we might get notified of things like,
here's a task that was completed
and there's gonna be a notion dock
that's tracking all of the progress we're making
on our game.
So maybe let's start with that for now.
And we kind of tweak the instructions as we go.
But yeah, for now, a Slackbot that just responds
to mentions on Slack.
Let's hope that works.
They didn't pick it up.
Hey, it worked for me.
Yeah, no one used, they restate this in your own words.
Oh, I just hit send.
I just hit send.
I mean, I sent it.
Whatever.
Okay, cool.
That was kind of fun.
I don't think I've done a multi-bot creation
for maybe we should publish that one.
Okay, it looks like we have our to-do list
up here in the top right.
So I have, let me zoom in a little bit.
So this is more visible on the stream.
We got some, oh wow, it's given us
a minute by minute plan.
We'll have to see.
We're gonna do some clerk it up UT stuff.
It looks like we have some open PRs here.
Yeah, I have a full autopilot system going.
Okay, and a bunch of to-dos.
It looks like it actually took the liberty
of making new pages for each of our tasks
and putting them in a Notion database,
which is kind of cool.
So, and a bunch of other stuff here.
What do you typically do as a PM tracking task?
This is exactly how I use.
Do you just use a checklist
or do you have a specific view that you like?
I know some people like Kanban or different.
So I actually switched back and forth.
I like Notion for this because Notion
can just make you a database
and then you can flip the views of it
to be whatever you want.
So for certain things I like Kanban boards
and I can just like go from in progress to doing.
And then what I will sometimes do
is just have a bot listening
to that Notion board every little while.
So if I move something to in progress,
the bot just goes in and starts to work on it.
But for other things like for this,
I think the checklist is just easier in my head
because I'm like here are the five things we need to do.
So yeah, I kind of go back and forth.
But for a lot of the work
that we work on Grokbot together on,
I have a Notion board that pretty much
just does the database thing.
So yeah, it's kind of cool, a lot of options.
Okay, so that's our to-do list.
Let's see if I can structure my screen here
or we can see everything.
Cool, cool, cool.
And then we have a,
looks like we made a new Slack bot called Ping.
Oh my God, I had the same name.
How did you know?
Oh my gosh, yeah, I don't know.
I guess Dr. Eggbot is really good at naming.
What is your Slack bot's name?
I'm installing the Slack plugin right now.
Okay, all right.
Okay, yeah, I need to connect Slack,
but I might do that when we're not looking at my screen,
so I'm not showing any secrets.
So can we go to the wide-angle shot for a second
and give me a chance to connect Slack?
Thank you.
In the meantime, I'm kicking off a couple agents.
I got some ads research,
so running like an agent to kind of understand like,
okay, like how do video games sell ads?
Like how do other businesses think about this problem?
And then making a recommendation
for how we'd implement that on the client and our server.
And then also like Lauren mentioned,
checking out some like maybe prototype pixel implementations,
because that could be cool.
So I feel like pixel art, sometimes it's good,
sometimes it's like really bad.
So we'll have to see, maybe play around with that a bit.
Cool, I almost got Slack connected here.
I'm just doing my Glass GitHub setup as well.
In the meantime, if you wanna cut to my screen,
I can show off some of what these,
like the remotion assets ended up looking like
from the last time,
and then we could also walk through some cool
RockBot uses that have queued up.
That'd be cool.
Anything we should be thinking about
for client server implementation
while Matt's playing that up?
Okay, cool, so basically what we talked through before
is like, right, how remotion built these as code.
So the cool thing is that you can just like start
to create different aspect ratios.
Obviously like, you know, is this perfect?
Like do we wanna adjust the crop?
Like probably, but now we have like a 16.9 asset.
So you'd imagine like, or 9.16 rather,
we have 1.1, 9.16, 16.9.
So now we could advertise like,
maybe there's a platform that prefers this,
probably like LinkedIn, Instagram X,
and there's like a way to easily start
like distributing these assets.
This is like perfect fidelity?
No, it doesn't really explain much about the game
or how it works, but like once we have the assets
in the game of, and the game mechanics,
we could then slot those in for the React components
that we have, and sort of like build out
some like dynamic videos, right?
So the whole point here is I could pop this open
and then like render this out as a video
where we'd have like a video asset on my laptop.
So yeah, that was pretty cool.
That was really cool.
Yeah, I love your emotion.
Yeah.
One of my favorite tools.
Yeah, you can just like create these so quickly.
Yeah, it might be cool to even get a bot
to like put some of these in some iPhone frames
and see how they showed up.
I don't know if that's like,
cause the bots are pretty good at generating
just like in like live HTML in the chat.
They are.
You can also, typically what I'll do for iPhone frames
is like if you use Figma, you can find like,
like there's an official, number one,
there are official Apple frames.
Like there's an official Figma pack to do this.
And then like you can like dig through some of these things
and find like good device or assets.
So one thing I think I'd have to set up separately
is like Figma, we'd have to set up like a Figma workspace.
We could pull in some of these phone frame assets.
And then actually this could be a pretty cool workflow
because bot is quite good at using Figma.
So maybe I'll kick it over to that in a bit.
Nice.
But I wanted to share actually,
so we had a guest on earlier, Karen,
some cool, cool girl, I use cases.
She basically had like bot print out
like a morning summary on her printer.
So she has an internet connected printer.
And this is like personally one of my favorite use cases.
So I want to share that.
I think I want to do, cause like I try to journal.
Everybody tries to journal.
Most people try to journal.
Many people fail to journal.
I actually do like try to write first thing in the morning,
whether it's like creative or about like, about my life.
And I feel like it would be really cool
to have like a template with a date
that just gets printed out every morning.
And that would like, to me,
that feels like almost more tactile than opening a journal.
And I feel like it's a better reminder.
So that's something I want to play around with.
And then also I'm thinking about getting like a receipt
printer and then like hooking it up to Twitter
and like printing out tweets or something.
I think that makes sense.
Another one I saw, so this is Lenny,
shout out Lenny Riccinski,
super, super big rock, pop, power user, awesome dude.
He paid a parking citation.
We all get parking citations,
especially in the Bay area, it's like notorious.
So using our like payments link integration,
he paid his parking citations.
I thought this was pretty cool.
That's cool.
We might have some Stripe friends on the show at some point.
That would be fun.
I got a third one here.
The, similar to what Matthew Berman talked about,
this user is, Alexandra here,
using a rock pot to sell items on,
on like online marketplaces, which is pretty sick.
I think the hardest part for like,
I sell a lot of stuff on like Facebook marketplace.
The hardest part about buying and selling stuff is like,
you have to take the photos and then do all the meta-tagging
and like all this stuff, it's so annoying.
So this is a pretty cool, cool use case.
And then the last one I have,
similar printing use case,
there's printing out like, if you,
I mean, when you're a kid,
like everybody has seen sheets like these
and has probably has like PTSD from like doing math.
Oh, homework.
Yeah.
So they just print out like arithmetic worksheets
for the kid, which is pretty cool.
And I like that as well.
So yeah, those are some four things I had queued up
that I'd saw on the timeline that I thought were pretty cool.
Yeah, that's so cool.
I think we have like one really underrated part of
rock pot is are the routines, right?
Like that, like this,
like these daily routines are really nice.
Yeah.
But then there's also routines that subscribe to events.
So like Slack messages is the one
we were just talking about.
But it can also subscribe to things like,
for like, if you're doing coding and doing technical things,
you can subscribe to like Datadog, Sentry, whatever,
and have, you know,
you start to think about like a factory type setup, right?
Yeah.
Where you have a alert,
Oh, our back end is down.
Like then spin off some bots to go investigate triage.
100%.
While you're working on that,
I got our notion dock cleaned up a little bit.
So if we can pull up.
Okay, let's pull up a Roshan screen.
We'll take a look at the notion dock.
So,
I bought starting to merge some of the back and peers.
Awesome. I'm getting all these notifications.
So, Bake, my engineer is getting all these notifications.
I need to remind it to actually check off the notion dock.
Oh yeah.
Well, I was actually about to send a Slack message
to both of you.
And so here we go.
Yeah, my screen's back up.
So I retooled our notion dock to look like a Kanban board.
You inspired me just now.
I have a question.
So here's the cupcake board.
We have like not started up next.
And I just asked my chief of staff here
to send you all a message.
And I actually really love this feature.
It just sort of like gives you a message option
and then you can just send it.
And there you go.
And so that's going to send.
And it lets us preview the draft of the message
and be able to send it.
So we have a message off to Slack for both of you.
And then going back to Bake over here
is our founding engineer, seeing all those PRs come in.
Hopefully your Slack bots get that message
and then can know the canonical source of truth
for our Kanban board.
So.
Sweet.
Cool.
Yeah, I decided I'm going to make a personal PM bot as well.
I like to have like specialists for my bots.
So this bot's only responsibility
will be to update the notion.
Then I have my Slack bot that's only responsibility
is to handle my ad mentions on Slack.
And then it's going to work with the rest of my team to,
I guess I don't know, like when I merge a PR,
update the notion and things like that.
That's awesome.
Cool.
Okay, so we have a task list going.
It looks like a couple of these are in progress.
Hopefully all of our bots are able to pick up tickets.
Almost like we've made our own little ticketing system
in some ways, you know.
Can assign our bots to various tasks.
So I think that seems really good.
I'm seeing a bunch of PRs coming in.
How are we feeling about the actual app?
Do we feel like it's in a good spot to take a look?
I don't think it's finished yet.
Cool.
A lot of rebasing.
Any good software engineering project?
Let's see if there's any of these other things
that can maybe, we've got to wait on the play test,
working on the back end, working on auth.
The 3D client experiment.
Do you think I should send some agents off to work on that?
I think we need the server end for that first, right?
We can still do some prototypes.
Maybe you can just tell your bot, hey.
I'm gonna start a new Docker egg bot.
Or like talk Docker egg bot and make a new bot.
Yeah, you could make a prototype of bot.
I think it'd be interesting.
Maybe the 3D only needs to come in at the battle part,
just to make it more interesting, maybe.
Although I guess then the question is also
how do we translate the bot to 3D?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, let me see what the bot,
what our agents come up with.
Maybe because the bots are all in a standard shape anyway.
I guess the complexity of 3D is like,
we'll have to think about how to.
Visually disambiguate them.
That means it's not a big deal.
It'd be good to just see a throwaway prototype.
Yeah.
Hey, Dr. Eggbot.
We want to try some more front-end client explorations
for the client application that we've
built in the Cupcake repo.
Can you spin up a bot whose job it's
going to be to try and prototype ways
that we can add more 3D animations while keeping
the app super lightweight?
The bot should be able to use cursor cloud agents
to get this work done and interact with the repo
that we just talked about.
And really interested here in being
able to swarm agents using potato mode
on a bunch of different front-end prototyping tasks.
So the core purpose of this bot is
going to be to prototype stuff.
And then as we find stuff that we like,
or find examples of these prototypes that we like,
we'll try and merge those in if they make sense.
So let's go ahead and get that spot.
Cool.
Got a bot going.
I've seen more PRs coming in too, which is great.
What did you think of the game design research
that I sent over?
Oh, I haven't had a chance to look at it, actually.
Maybe we can pull that up.
You had a doc for this, right?
Notion?
Yeah.
What is it called?
I think I messaged you on the slide.
Oh, let me ask Ping.
I'll go back here to my to-do list
so we should have shown on screen.
It's in the RDMs.
OK.
But yeah, I think our game mechanics
are a little bit too plain at the moment.
It doesn't have to block the launch,
but it'd be good to just start thinking about,
I mean, we have some ideas in that doc.
Yeah.
But maybe we can figure out which one's
the best one to fast follow after we get it launched.
I was spinning up a bot for that.
Oh, wow, I just saw some updates filter in on the Notion board.
So our bots are definitely doing something there.
I just asked Dr. Ibot to spin up a game design bot for us
that can handle ingesting that information.
Yeah, it looks like you did DM me.
There's the Notion doc.
Thank you.
Yeah, and here's our new bot, Glow 3D.
I like using these labels, too.
It just helps me keep them all organized.
And I like fun names from my bots,
so it's kind of fun to be able to do that.
So Glow is our 3D prototyping bot.
And it looks like it's asking me what we'd want to try.
Which motion lane should we buy a stuff for system towards?
What do you think?
UI Chrome depth?
Match and fight for us, actually.
That's what we were talking about before, right?
Yeah.
Or I can give it a few more.
This is a multi-pick, so I guess.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, let's do match and fight.
Match and fight could be probably the best place.
Cool.
And I mean, you bought here crit.
That's our game designer.
We got a whole team cooking, watching Slack,
watching GitHub, game designing.
Actually, I don't know that we just told anybody this.
We just launched one password integration.
Oh, cool.
Did we announce that?
Yeah.
I think we did.
I saw it on Twitter.
Oh, no, I meant on stream.
I see it on Twitter.
I have it open on Twitter, or X, rather.
So whoops, a little bit of feedback.
If we could actually cover it up, cover it on my screen
real quick, we'll talk about it.
X.com slash bot.
It was actually just right at the top.
There you go.
Boom.
One password.
So maybe we should start to, I mean,
this would have been super helpful to have when we're
setting all that stuff up with one password.
We spent a day doing that.
But the team shifts fast.
Maybe they knew.
Maybe they saw.
Maybe they saw it struggling.
And they're like, all right.
We got to get that through for you.
OK.
Well, hey, we have a whole other day of stream.
There you go.
All of our secrets management tomorrow will be so easy.
This is really cool.
I want to try this out.
All right, cool.
So where are we?
You're working on some of this design stuff?
Yeah.
I totally lost here.
So I have bots trying to work on the, actually, I don't know.
Could you double check if that Notion page that you shared
is in our Notion space?
Because my bot is having some trouble getting it.
Let us see.
It is.
Do I need to show?
I think it's only private.
Let me change that.
OK, you should have access now.
Cool.
I just asked my bot to try it again.
Yeah, it came up with some good feedback.
This is a crazy doc.
The fleet?
The fleet pulse.
It's a roll up of durable facts from active ship
by Thursday bots.
That's really great.
I guess they just decided they'd want to make this.
Our bots are writing updates from PRs that merge.
One of our bosses, yeah.
Cool.
I have two bots spinning on the 2.5D 3D prototyping.
So hopefully we'll get some cool examples there soon.
Those are cursor cloud agents that are running.
My cursor cloud agents page.
I think our back end is almost done.
So I'm going to start wiring it up to the client.
OK, great.
And so hopefully in a few minutes, maybe after the break,
we'll have it playable.
We'll definitely try to play with it in the background this fall
and continue iterating.
But we're getting really close to being
able to share the game with the chat
and maybe getting some real games and feedback as well.
So one thing I'm actually really interested in
is setting up a lot of saying a feedback factory where
we'll get feedback from people playing the game who are like,
this is boring or whatever.
And we'll get that and start to automatically triage,
put it into our notion, get the whole system going,
and try to move really fast.
So yeah, my bots are wiring up the back end now.
So hopefully we make some progress.
So I was just thinking of this MVP here for an ads, a lobby
sponsored billboard.
And it looks like it's proposing an endpoint
for serving the billboard and describing, hey,
there's no ads route, so we need to add one.
We might need to add a table that allows us to slot those in.
And it's describing a data modeling
for having advertisers, campaigns, and creatives.
Honestly, it seems a little too complex.
I might slim this down a little bit.
But yeah, I mean, I don't think this
seems to be too complicated.
It's interesting to see.
Oh, I'm actually also looking at the chat.
And I guess there are some questions around what
game we're building.
For the people who are joining late, maybe, Roshan,
you want to give a quick update?
Yeah, we'd love to.
Maybe even show what we have so far in the web prototype.
Yeah, let's see if I can find my prototype.
I had it running somewhere.
We'll cut to Roshan's screen here.
Yeah, if we cut to my screen, I
can show you a little bit of what we've
been building in the background.
So cool.
Yeah, so this is what we're building.
So we are building a game studio in our first game.
And that's the business that we've been building on stream
for the last little while.
We have a working name for our game, which is Cupcake.
And the whole premise of the game
is that you'll be able to log in with X
and pit your bots head to head against other bots
in order to win the global leaderboard
and get to the top of the global leaderboard.
How did you get first place, Matt?
Oh, you.
I don't make the rules.
I don't think the rules around here.
What the hell?
It's a placeholder leaderboard.
We'll match up for real.
I'm very competitive.
When there's a leaderboard, I'm like, ooh.
I'm going to optimize.
That's what we're hoping we'll make.
We're hoping everyone's going to be competitive
to drive a bunch of users to the game.
So this is our prototype that we built,
which is just a bunch of HTML.
And we have a client app now that we're
wiring into a proper back end.
But the idea here is that you'd
be able to customize your team with bots
that you're uploading.
So if you create a bot template using GrokBot,
you'll be able to add that bot in.
The bot will be assigned some stats, subject
to some rules that we built.
And if you're curious to learn more about some of that,
you can go and check out some of our sessions
from this morning.
But basically, you have a team of bots here.
And you create a lineup for any match.
So you choose a captain bot, get a few friends
that join your team, and then be
able to have your bots face off against someone else
who's logged in and who's also in the app at the same time
and earn some points and grow your rating
and get onto the leaderboard.
So that's the end-to-end mock-up.
Obviously, we're going to continue adding to this,
but that's kind of where we are.
Yeah, what I like about this is, so right now,
it's obviously very simple.
But I think there's a lot of really interesting mechanics
we can add to the game.
We have a leaderboard.
It's competitive.
We have this notion of a captain bot.
Don't really know what that means yet.
But maybe that kind of some special difference
for the captain.
Yeah, I think there could be a lot of really interesting
ideas.
Maybe there's a chance as well to, if you win,
you get a chance to take the other person's bot or something.
I don't know.
Something like that, where I feel like there's
a lot of interesting ideas there.
Yeah.
That's actually my favorite part about this idea,
is there's so many ways we can go with it.
So it's like, once we get the core out there,
we'll be able to kind of go from there.
Cool, OK.
We also have a task list that we're working towards.
So it looks like auth work is in progress.
Promotion ads are in progress.
Working on the API in the back end here.
Let's see what my, so I have a game critique bot here.
Lauren had a bot that wrote up some thoughts on our game
design pattern here.
So just to kind of recap for folks,
we basically built some game mechanics here for these bots
to go head to head and wanted to kind of validate,
are these best practices for game design?
None of us are pro game designers.
Some of us are pro game players, or not pro,
but enjoy playing games.
What's really nice is we can just go and get some wisdom
from the world here.
So it looks like we have some proposed changes
to the mechanics.
Do you want to zoom in a little bit?
It's hard to see.
Yeah, let me do that.
There we go.
I can actually just make a dropout full screen here
for a second, so we can see that a little bit better.
Type only.
OK, so maybe some suggestions here.
Actually, one thing I'm noticing is,
or a meta thing I'm noticing, is
some of the writing here is kind of,
it kind of looks like AI writing.
So I wonder if you could use the handy dandy unslop skill
or the bro skill in PSAC to, let's get it
like a plain English.
Unslop, bro.
Plain English.
These two are the most, I hear they're the most useful
skills in PSAC, so very, very handy for,
what did my bot just say?
Very, very useful.
Yeah, and if you have not installed PSAC,
go into the marketplace.
You can install PSAC.
You get all of these skills.
There are over 40 of them here that will help you
be a potato engineer.
OK, so it's a clean version here.
Social truth, looks good.
Who will ask?
I'm going to have this crit agent actually talk
to our founding engineer.
Just make sure it follows these rules.
It might be good to have a canonical game design
document as well.
So it's like one thing that's really useful when you're
starting to work in a team with GrofBot
is sharing context with each other.
And yeah, I think it'd just be good to,
I have that one scratch doc for the game design,
but it'd be really nice to have a single document
that we can all reference or the bots can reference.
Great idea.
I'm going to set that up right now.
Send it to Lauren on that, on Slack.
What I like about this is I know you both have bots listening
to Slack, so I can just say send something to Slack.
And it just hopefully will make its way into your bot ecosystem.
I haven't seen anything in Slack.
I'm going to ask my bot as well.
But my bot is definitely listening.
Yeah, let me pull up mine.
So I have a bot here called Ping that is monitoring Slack.
And if I look at Ping's routines, yep,
any time Slack is mentioned, at mention,
it's not even on Slack.
So any time I'm not mentioned, it should be working.
Make sure you watch DMs too, not just at mentions
in random channels.
Yeah, one thing I like to do as well
is when I start to feel like there's almost like a workflow
that I want, that's the point where I start thinking about,
OK, how do I get Dr. Eggbot to actually fix up
not just one agent, but all my agents?
So example, let's just say that we
want it to be very communicative.
And every decision we make should be,
it should go on to Slack.
And we want to always keep each other informed.
That's something Dr. Eggbot can actually help you with.
So you could tell it, like, hey, Dr. Eggbot,
we want to be very fluid with our comms.
And every time we make a decision, post a Slack.
And hopefully, that doesn't overdo it,
and literally, Pinkgood like, spams this.
But the point being, when you're
starting to feel like you are almost
like micromanaging your bots too much with individual commands
and prompts, it's a good time to kind of take a step back
and think, hmm, how do I actually
think about workers trading my team of bots?
And Dr. Eggbot's really good too for that.
Cool.
And it looks like my Slack bot is updated
to be listening to DMs as well.
So yeah.
A lot of curiosity, are our bots updating the notion?
Let's take a look.
So I see a bunch of tasks here.
I did see a few things flip over from up next to in progress.
Like, Clerk was not in progress a few minutes ago.
And so I think we have our bots updating
notion, which is great.
I'm just going to see here, switch back to, OK,
we have a feature here for the replay tape.
I just got murdered.
Yeah, I'm going to tell my Dr. Eggbot
to tell all my team that the notion is going
to be the source of truth.
And every bot should keep it updated.
I'll do the same.
Cool.
It looks like we have my founding end here.
Earlier, I asked, I had my game design bot here
ask my founding engineer to take a look at the client
implementation and make sure we have the latest feedback
from our game design review.
And so looks like we were messaging back and forth
from the bots.
And looks like we maybe need to fix some stuff here.
So I'm going to just go ahead and have our engineer just
start working, doing what I think is best.
What are you all working on?
Updating some of the ad stuff.
So we're working on that, maybe a little bit
of a marketplace.
I also just made sure that my site missions are live and listening.
So we should be good there.
Awesome.
Yeah.
I am continuing to build our back end for simplicity.
Well, actually, I'm reworking it a little bit
because I'm going to use Vercel functions.
Cool.
I'm going to try that out.
Never used Vercel functions before.
But it's going to be an interesting setup
because it's going to be serverless.
So we'll see how well that works.
But yeah.
It's going.
I'm also going to wire our web client so that we can actually
start playing the game.
Nice.
Let's see if we can get some of these videos working.
So while we were talking, I kicked off
a 3D prototyping bot that was going
to take a look at some possible ways we could add some more
3D to this experience and explore some mockups for that.
Let's see.
This video works here.
Maybe it won't.
Let me figure out what's going there.
But what's cool about this is the bot
seems to have generated some videos in the back end
and try to put some mockups together,
which is pretty exciting.
We got some tests failing.
Maybe we can go clean up.
Yeah, tests are interesting because I
feel like agents in general are not
super good at writing tests.
They can be.
So one thing actually we haven't really done yet
is I care a lot about code quality, of course.
But I think at such an early stage of the project,
it's more important to just actually get it out the door.
So we haven't really spent any time on that.
But I think once we have it up and we're starting to iterate,
I will set up the code quality factory,
start thinking about performance, things like that.
So tests are, yeah.
I almost wonder if tests are slowing us down.
Should I delete all the tests?
I really would say the test right now.
Yeah, maybe let me tell my bot.
Yeah, let's do it.
Delete all the tests.
We'll push it to main and deleting all the tests.
True scrappy mode.
We'll write the test later once we know what we want.
Once we know what we're testing.
Cool, looks like our agents are looking here.
OK, and I think we should have a mechanics doc.
Oh, I got to figure that out and clean that up.
Yeah, I think my bots are updating the notion.
And I think if we cut to my screen for a little bit,
I can show off what my project agents are doing.
So if you haven't used cursor projects before,
it's a new feature that we launched.
When did we launch?
I think either a few days ago or last week.
I'm blanking on when exactly we launched it.
But very recently, and projects are
one of the best features in cursor.
The way I think about a project is really,
it's a long running coordinator agent
that does a really good job of keeping track of sub-agents
and smaller agents that it orchestrates to do tasks.
And so it's kind of similar to the multitasking mode
that Roshan shared earlier.
But this one's a little bit, I think
projects are a little bit more powerful because projects
have access to certain things like shared.
So one thing that projects have is
they share this almost memory between the cloud agents
that it spawns with the main project agent
so that they can communicate with each other
and share context.
So you can see that actually I'm not even
piloting this project.
My Grotbot, Tater, I told it to actually work
with my project agent.
So it's going off and doing that.
And you can see here in this working tray
that it's spawned five different sub-agents.
And it's just orchestrating them all and driving them
to completion.
Another really cool thing about this
is we have potato mode in here.
And potato mode has this really cool playbook,
my favorite playbook called full autopilot.
I won't call it the YOLO mode, but it's
the mode where you are trying to get a lot of PRs merged.
And you want to kind of opt into a full agentic loop.
So it does a lot of things.
It will obviously have agents that go off and implement
those tasks.
And then it will also spawn verification agents
that will actually try to run the code
and make sure it's correct.
And depending on how much reasoning you apply in setup
P-stack, so setup P-stack is a skill in P-stack that lets you
adjust how much multitasking you do on the max level.
It will spawn a swarm of agents who actually run the application
and fuzz the application.
And fuzz meaning they'll actually run it and click around,
make sure that things are working.
And you have lots of bots, almost like
simulating real users.
And for some reason, the project agent
has picked up on some potato nomenclature or terminology
here.
Instead of saying merge, it says mashed.
I don't know why it's saying that.
But that's fun.
It gives that personality.
Mashed.
I think Tater must have told it, yeah, mash it in.
Mash it in.
Because we do have a bot here called Mash.
So I wonder if it's saying that.
That's great.
And what's really cool, too, is while you're doing all this,
I'm seeing the Notion cam board.
Oh, yeah.
It's updating.
So we had a bunch of stuff that was next up that
is now all in progress.
And a few things have moved over to DUNN.
They were waiting to rebase BR21 and land PR19.
So it looks like both of those are in.
Yeah.
That's really cool.
The Notion thing kind of just flies.
It was kind of cool.
If we had an extra monitor in here somewhere,
it's like put the dashboard up on a monitor
and just saw a lot of tasks flying around in real time.
That'd be really cool.
The new real ticket, the ticket burned down.
ETA to the game.
ETA to complete.
Cool.
We're going to see if we've made any progress on our 3D
design prototypes.
Kind of see what we came up with.
Yeah.
Should we take a look?
Let me give me a second.
Let me pull up these PRs.
I think I have one here.
I should probably pull them both up right quick.
PR.
Oh, I forgot to mention about while you're
working on that, that projects is really good at is the fact
that every single agent on the project
is actually a cloud agent.
So I could actually just go off, turn my laptop off,
go and have dinner, go get some boba,
and it's going to keep working.
And oh, it looks like we have your screen up now.
Yeah.
So you're reminding me on the boba thing, but let me forget.
Oh, yeah.
We should get some snacks.
Yeah.
So yeah, I asked earlier an agent to spin up some 3D demos
to get a sense of how we might bring in some 2D or 3D.
Oh, yeah.
Let me zoom in.
It's not going to.
Let me just see if I can just pinch to zoom.
Yeah.
There we go.
For the video.
Yeah.
We'll slow it down a little bit.
And so what's cool about this is a cursor agent,
prototypes and stuff, and then also went ahead and took
a video of how this would look.
And so, eh, did OK at that.
Is this supposed to be 3D?
I think it's told itself this is a 2.5D tape clash.
And so I think it gave itself a couple of different parts.
This is SLAM 3D.
Let's see what SLAM 3D is.
That's kind of cool.
OK, let's see if we can.
Why is it so fast?
Oh, did you put it on?
I think it's just the it doesn't
have a good sense of the game engine yet.
But let's see.
It just goes like, mash, mash, mash.
Yeah.
OK.
There's another one here.
That was a 2.5D.
There's another one I think we had going on.
I almost wonder if you're actually
going to explicitly say, let's use 3JS maybe for the 3D.
I can all try prompting for that.
I was hoping we'd have some other videos to see.
OK, you can see a sense of how these would look.
These are more static.
But a lot of PRs are getting merged.
Nice.
We have our bot factory in full swing.
Love it.
OK.
How's our task list look in Notion?
Oh, cool.
I did actually get the videos in GrokBot.
That's what I was hoping would happen.
So there we go.
We got these videos in GrokBot to take a look at what we just saw.
So we can actually just do this.
In GrokBot, again, the animation speed is not perfect.
But we'll give it some feedback here.
Someone in chat also mentioned that maybe we
should have some game music.
I actually forgot entirely about music.
Oh, we could learn about music.
Or audio.
That can be fun to add later.
Let's actually add that in.
Where's our PM?
Yeah, let's add a task to the Notion list for sound design.
I'm actually curious.
Do we have plug-ins that help you make sound?
How did that work?
I'm not sure.
We'll probably find out.
We'll probably wonder if we could just engineer some quick
sound effects.
Probably do some 8-bit type stuff for you.
That seems like it would be.
Would it be annoying?
It would probably be annoying, yeah.
I mean, we could make it good, though.
Yeah, I'm going to show my bot.
Make a new bot that will help us explore some sound
design for the game.
We have a task on the Notion board,
so it should be able to just pick up that task
and run with it.
I want some really high-level exploration.
Maybe we could explore some styles that are 8-bit music
or something that we're generating.
And it should be not too annoying.
I find annoying sounds are always the worst
when you're especially on a web browser
and you don't expect the music to be playing.
So yeah, let's spin up a bot whose job it is to be our audio engineer
and go figure out some prototypes for that.
Would it be worth, since we're going to generate these songs,
oh, I didn't read the whole problem,
but maybe we could put them all into Notion.
Oh, yeah, that's an idea.
And then we can review it later as a team.
Since we're trying to move more into tracking everything
with Notion.
I also like give your bots feedback.
As soon as Dr. Eggbot spins up a bot here,
I'm going to let it know that we want our audio designs
to live in Notion.
Well, a lot of PRs about merge.
What a good name for a bot.
OK, we have tones, our audio sound engineer.
Make, drop the audio in Notion, BT-Dove.
So we can all listen and check it out.
Roshan, do you want to share the Eggbot promotion again
before we cut back to the main stage?
Oh, yeah, I didn't realize we were losing.
Got so into the build that we are going to be cutting back
to the main stage in just a minute.
So yeah, let me cut over here to our Eggbot promotion.
So for those of you who are just joining
or if you missed this earlier, we
are giving away some free Grokbot
if you want to be able to build the way we've been building
or want to be able to try Grokbot out
for any of these cases you've heard today.
We showed a bunch of really fun personal use cases,
being able to print newsletters.
If we can actually get our camera off of the overlay,
it will make the QR code easy for folks to see
and stop covering it up.
Thank you very much.
If you want some free Grokbot, you can follow these steps.
$200 in value, so a really great deal here.
The first 1,000 users exclusively on stream,
the first 1,000 users who duplicate and create
a bot with Dr. Eggbot will get a chance to get
a free month of Grok Bot.
And so hopefully you guys get to try this out.
And hopefully you've seen us use Dr. Eggbot
over the course of the day to create a bunch of bots of our own.
It's really great.
Highly recommend it.
So up next with that, we're going to go to Grok Bot
for customer support on the main stage,
and we'll be back right after that.
Hey, everyone.
Thank you for joining today's workshop on Grok Bot
for customer support.
My name is David, and I am a software engineer here
at SpaceX AI in the user ops org.
I'm really excited to share what we've been working on
and how we're using Grok Bot for customer support.
So here's the agenda for today.
I'm going to quickly give some context on Grok Bot
in case you haven't been watching the livestream or been
to one of the other sessions.
Then I'll share a few specific use cases for it
around customer support.
Then I'll demo a lot of these.
My goal is that the session is a little bit more demo heavy,
so you can really see it in action.
And finally, we'll finish with some Q&A.
So let's get started.
So first, what is Grok Bot?
Grok Bot is a new product that lets you hand off real work
to an AI coworker.
The interface looks very familiar,
just like a messenger app on your phone or a computer.
But under the hood, it's built to keep working
after you've sent your original message.
So you aren't just chatting back and forth
with quick, simple one-offs here and there.
You're really able to delegate a real project to Grok Bot,
and it can go off and take it from there.
One of my favorite things about Grok Bot
is how flexible it is to the way you work.
So you can start with a single general bot
to help you get set up quickly and easily,
or create a team of specialists that
coordinate around the task and work in parallel
on certain sub-tasks.
And however your team operates, Grok Bot
can fit in and be very useful very quickly.
So why Grok Bot?
Why does it feel like interacting
with a capable coworker rather than just another AI tool?
For me, there are three big reasons.
First, Grok Bot is always on.
So by now, you may have heard that Grok Bots
have their own computer.
All that really means is that they
can work without using yours, which
is a little bit more powerful than you would think.
So if you close your laptop or you
are working on something else, your Grok Bots
can still finish the task you assigned them
without you having to check in constantly
and steer them too much or slowing down your local machine.
There are also routines, which are
cron jobs or event-based triggers
that you can launch your Grok Bots with
and make them super reactive.
This way, you don't have to be online at the exact moment.
You want them to run or start working on the task.
And these are simple, or these are super simple to set up.
All you have to do is tell it, create a routine at this time
or on this event, just like a normal conversation,
and it will set it up for you.
Second, it is really easy to use.
The interface is familiar for a reason.
You don't have to be an engineer that
is familiar with the ins and outs of an IDE
to use bots effectively.
You can just talk with it normally
like you would a friend or teammate on Slack.
And finally, it fits how you actually work.
There are already connectors for most tools you use.
You just have to go into the marketplace and search for them,
and there is likely one for you.
So you can plug Grok Bot immediately
into your ticketing system, whether that's
plain, Zendesk, Intercom, where your team chats like Slack,
where your knowledge base is like Notion.
And then from there, you can use the bots and routines
like building blocks that fit the way your team actually works.
And one really powerful thing about Grok Bot
is if there is a missing piece, you can likely
have Grok Bot build it.
Grok Bot has access to Cloud agents.
So if there is something that you're missing,
you can just have it tell it to spin up a Cloud agent
to build a certain connector or a certain thing,
and it can go off and do it for you.
So you can get creative and build around,
and you're not stuck waiting on N's roadmap or a third party
vendor to add support for the thing you need.
Cool.
Now we'll get into some customer support use cases.
So the big one is always, can it answer support tickets?
The answer is yes, and I'll show this later in the demo.
I know this can be scary at first
to let an agent reply to your customers.
So you can definitely build up to it.
So you can crawl, then walk, then run.
At first, you can have it just read tickets,
maybe give you a summary and the root issue of what
the user is asking about.
And maybe it can draft a response.
Then you can have it add the draft
to a note in your ticketing system on the ticket
so you can sort of see it before you press send.
And finally, when you're confident,
then you can have an answer and actually respond
to the ticket and the user.
There's also things you can do around the guard rails
and environment you give Grokbot.
So you can set up evals and traces fairly easily
so you know what it's thinking and what actions it will take
before it publishes.
So when you can add traces to those draft steps
and then sort of make sure it's behaving the way you want it
to before going on.
Cool.
The second one.
So at scale, you may have a lot of support tickets
with a ton of different customer states.
And it can be really challenging to find the things
you should care about in that exact moment that
need your attention.
Grokbot can make this a lot easier through alerting.
So you can spin up a bot that looks for certain things.
For example, maybe your team is hyper-focused on churn
this quarter.
And you want to know when someone
writes in that is threatening to churn,
that has been a customer for six months or more.
Anyone on your team can spin up a Grokbot
that you have connected to your ticketing system.
You can just tell it to create a routine that
looks through your tickets every hour.
Try it classifies if a user is threatening to churn
and has been a customer for a certain period of time.
And then send you an alert in a Slack channel
so everyone has visibility.
And another one that maybe is more powerful than you think
or is harder to get to than you think
is an internal question and answer agent.
So if you've used other support agents,
they are primarily focused on customer replies.
It's surprisingly cumbersome to leverage the knowledge base.
You've already sort of created or accumulated
to answer your own teammates' questions.
You may have someone in GTM that is trying
to get up to speed on today's release about Cloud agents
so they can come prepared to a customer call or a TSE manager
looking for changes to the internal refund policy
over time and if that has impacted certain customers.
You have already done the hard work
of creating this knowledge base of both public info.
So think your Docs and Help Center as well as likely
some internal info.
So you might have suggested operating procedures
around how your teammates handle refunds
that is not public information.
You should be able to query this intelligently
within Slack, and Grokbot makes this really easy.
And maybe the last one and one of the cooler ones
is it can improve itself.
So finally, you can give Grokbot your traces
or have it look back on the last week of tickets
and sort of ask it to look and try
to find improvements for tickets that maybe could have been
handled better, could have been flagged earlier,
and it can go and do those things for you.
Cool.
So next, we're going to get into the demo.
I have created this demo.
I have a team of four bots.
They are billed.
So it sort of runs the setup and the infrastructure, reply.
So this actually answers users in both our ticketing system
and then Slack.
There is an alert.
So this one usually gets pinged by reply and post an alert
in Slack and tags me, and then tune,
which tries to improve the system as we go.
I want to call out that you definitely do not
have to have these in mind or set them up
before getting started.
In fact, I don't recommend that.
Instead, you can start with one bot, name it a generic name,
and try to teach it one workflow.
Then when the scope grows or you need more than one
running at a time, I recommend breaking them up naturally
then and reorganizing them in a way that makes sense to you.
Cool.
So now I'll get into the demo.
I have Grokbot set up with the bots we mentioned.
And then I have a few things that
might look familiar if you are inside of a support org.
So first, we have a knowledge base.
Right now, I just set this up in Notion as an example.
So we have public docs.
So think of this as like, this could
be your documentation or your help center that
has a few things on product and common issues
like auth and billing and FAQ.
I should have mentioned that I'm going
to use the fly low example that you may have seen
in other presentations.
So this is basically like a pretend airline.
And I'm going to simplify it.
So the only skew we have is a monthly internet subscription
that is billed monthly and is $20 a month.
So we have this public information
that a user could find if they search Google.
We have some internal policies.
So right now, this is stuff that we
want maybe a billing support member
to know if you have a human answering,
but you don't want to share broadly with the public.
So this is just a very simple example of,
if a user asks for a refund, you can approve it
within 14 days and cancel and refund
if they've been subscribed for more than 14 days,
deny the refund.
And then finally, I just have a little bit
of process for the Brockbot agent reply
to use when replying to some of these tickets.
So we just have this loop of what it should do.
Read the ticket, look for the knowledge,
and then decide to reply or hand off, and then act,
leave a note, and yeah.
This is plane.
This is our ticketing system.
So I've already refilled a few example tickets,
and we'll walk through those.
I have Stripe pulled up as well.
So I mentioned there's a subscription
that users may pay for that is basically
the Wi-Fi pass on a plane.
And then I have Slack that I'll pull up for later.
Cool.
So first, let's start with maybe this first ticket.
So I'm going to go through alphabetical.
So this is just a very basic question.
I forgot my password.
How can I sign in?
Or how do I reset it?
So let me ask Brockbot to try to reply to this.
So like I mentioned, I have the Brockbots I mentioned.
There is build.
So I've already set up some of the connectors
to make this a little quicker.
So I've added plane.
I've added notion, superbase, and Slack.
If you aren't familiar, you can just click the Marketplace
and search and click and install.
Cool.
So let's tell reply.
Hi, can you reply to Alex in plane?
And it is going to go off and try to reply.
So let's see.
It's going to look it up.
I pulled up.
So basically, while I wait for it to reply,
it's going to go through this process.
So I've made this loop pretty simple of just what I wanted
to do, how I wanted to behave, and show some thinking.
And we'll see that it replied.
OK, cool.
It replied.
It said it replied.
If I go back into the ticket, you
see that it followed the sort of tracing,
or it followed the process that I gave it.
So it showed some of its thinking,
where it says it can reply with high confidence, the root issue,
and the source that it referenced
to answer the question.
And then it gave the right information.
So these are the exact steps on this public auth
forgot your password.
So if we go to public auth forgot your password,
these are the exact steps.
So that's obviously a pretty basic example.
But let's go on to a harder one.
So this is an example of something
that is not covered in the toy knowledge base we created,
so some SSO octa stuff.
Let's see.
I'm going to try to prompt it so it will try to reply.
But in the instructions, I told it to not reply
unless it's pretty confident.
Try replying to Ben and pointing.
And once again, it's going to go through the exact same process.
If I were to change something in this sort of loop,
it would, I've already told it to make sure
to read this every single time.
So if I were to add maybe seven and some other step,
it would know to do that after every time.
So let's wait on that for a few more seconds.
And let's make sure I have Slack pulled up for later.
OK, nice.
So it says it tried to do that, but there
is no public docs or internal policies, so low confidence
and handoff, which is exactly what we wanted it to do.
And then you'll notice that this is new, so it messaged alert.
So I've set up that if something,
if it looks like maybe an enterprise customer that's
locked out to make sure to alert me so I can know in real time.
So it messaged alert, alert activated, and posted to Slack.
And our alerts DG channel, it is this one.
So yeah, so now I am without too much work,
I can already see like in real time that important tickets
that I need to maybe action on right now.
Let's go on for now.
So I'm going to mark this done for now
and go on to the next one.
So the next one is going to be two refund related tickets.
I mentioned at the beginning that we have an SOP specifically
around that.
So we have two users, Carter and Damon.
If I go into Stripe and click into them,
I've set it up where Carter just subscribed
and is requesting a refund.
So today is September 16, so his renews in exactly a month.
So we should grant him this refund.
And then Damon, you'll see that it renews in about 10 days.
So it's already been call it 20 days, which is,
and our policy is only 14 days within.
So it should deny Damon and grant the refund to Carter.
And it will, we've already set up Stripe,
so it can take these actions for you.
You can set it up to have you approve the actions
or you can tell it let it run loose.
So let's say, OK, now try to answer Carter and Damon.
And this one may take a second because it's
going to run through the loop, make the call.
And then if it needs to, it will
have to run the actions through Stripe.
Let me have those pulled up.
And we'll see this state get changed here shortly.
Let me pass in the customer IDs.
Maybe it'll make it quicker.
It should be on its way now.
So it's thinking it found them now.
And it says both replies are already up.
So let's go look at them.
So it just answered.
For Carter, like I mentioned, it should
have canceled an issue to refund.
It's saying that it did that.
If we go to Carter in Stripe and refresh,
the status should have just changed.
So nice.
It went from active to canceled.
And this payment has been refunded.
And then that's what it said it did.
And then for Damon, it says, we have denied your refund.
It didn't give the full SOP, so it
didn't leak the internal information.
It was just vague.
And then it says, I can schedule a cancellation for you
at the end of your period so you don't
get billed for the next month.
And then if we go to Damon and refresh,
this should all stay the same.
And it does.
Cool.
Great.
OK, so now we'll go on to the next one.
So Elena is asking if she can share her Wi-Fi
pass with another person.
This is something that's not actively in the knowledge base.
So let's see how it handles it.
It would be under public docs.
And it would likely go here.
Cool.
So let's tell reply.
Let's clear that out.
Great.
Can you reply to Elena now?
And it should go from there.
So it's already come back with some thinking.
It's found the ticket.
And it's checking.
It's sort of already classified that pass sharing
is the root issue and looking if it's in public docs.
And now it's saying that it couldn't reply yet
because public docs and FAQ doesn't have pass sharing.
And it's recommending to tell tune,
which is the self-improver, to add it to the knowledge base.
So yes, we'll say add pass sharing to the FAQ.
Say this is not allowed.
So this is an example of it asking before it
doing something by itself.
So for your knowledge base, this is probably something you want
just to make sure you have the final say over what happens
because if this were to go out without you looking
and you didn't check it and it wasn't correct
and 100 people asked about the same thing, then yeah,
that'd be an issue.
OK.
So it says it added it to the knowledge base.
I told it to do it in green so we can delineate it.
And adjust it.
So pass sharing.
No, you cannot share your Wi-Fi pass with another person
for simultaneous use.
Great.
Let's see.
I actually had one more thing pulled up.
OK.
Actually, let's skip that then.
Cool.
So back to Grokbot then.
We've added the knowledge, so now let's try to respond.
So in the ticket, it left a note saying to hand off
that the information was missing.
And it still needs a response.
So let's tell reply.
Can you try again now that the information is added?
And it says it's answering.
And it says it's replied down.
So now we have a new sort of thinking note.
Now it can reply with high confidence.
There's a root issue and it links to the new section
and docs that covers it.
So you cannot share your Wi-Fi pass with another person.
Great.
That's exactly what we wanted.
Let's mark this one as done.
Cool.
That covers a lot of it.
Now let's go to one of the other use cases I mentioned.
So if we go into Slack, we've already
seen that it can send us alerts.
But we have another use case where
you can have your teammates ask the bot you've already set up
to answer customers and the knowledge base
to answer your own teammates.
So let's say I am someone on your billing team
and I want to know what is the refund SOP.
So this is I'm an internal user.
I'm asking a question.
And it should give me the internal knowledge for it.
So that's the most helpful.
So we sent it.
This may take about a minute.
But yeah, we should see us getting a response here
pretty soon.
So it's asking for permission to post in Slack.
Let's say always allow for this.
And it should reply here in a second.
Let's try that again.
Make sure it's running.
See the mess.
OK, it's going.
I ran this right before.
So you can see that this is what would happen.
It would reply.
And go from there.
Let's give it maybe 10 more seconds.
If not, we can go on.
Now it says it's replied.
Great.
So it added the emoji and it replied.
Awesome.
So that's one of the other use cases.
Cool.
So that wraps.
Again, cut the demo there.
So what we learned.
First, you can and should feel comfortable setting
guardrails for your bots.
You saw maybe at the end there it
was even more protective than I wanted to be.
But that's probably better for rights.
You can have them be read only to start, and then work up
to rights, and have manual approvals
for certain actions.
You can also scope permissions to your different bots.
So one bot might have permission to post automatically
to Slack.
One might not.
And make them approve those actions before they do them.
Second, start simple.
So the whole product is still so new.
I don't think there's one meta or one clear playbook.
And the product is meant to be very flexible.
So try to make the bots fit into how you work,
and not vice versa.
Third, try to get a little creative and experiment.
You can really have it build what is missing.
Cool.
Thank you so much.
That is the rest of the presentation.
And we can go into Q&A.
Oh, yeah.
So any questions?
Yes.
What's the price of life for this?
So it uses your usage that you would
have through any of your Grok subscriptions
or currently cursor subscriptions.
So it just tracks usage.
I'll say it can really depend on how involved your loops are.
So if you have classifiers that run before every ticket,
if you have it right traces and evals before doing that,
that can also change.
Right now, the way I use it, it's around $1 to $2
to answer more medium to complex tickets.
And there are ways.
I've already tried to experiment and found ways
to get that down a lot.
So there are a lot of maybe low complexity billing tickets
of a user just asking for a refund
or a user asking about a certain new email they received.
You can sort of bucket those.
You can run a script, have it run a script
to find those first or run that manually
so it has more of a contained sort of set.
And then have it reply all at once
with the script to those tickets.
And I found that I could get that down to about $0.20
a ticket for those low complexity tickets, which
is a huge sort of change.
If you've used any of the other sort of support agents,
you know that the cost per, they usually
charge per resolution.
And that's easily at minimum $1, if not between $1 to $10
order of magnitude.
And if you're having humans respond to those tickets,
that can be even noticeably higher.
And that's just like with half a day of trying to improve it.
I think there's a lot of gains and unlocks there especially.
Yeah.
You're good.
Sorry.
How would you interrogate what's going on
if something goes wrong, especially with communication
in between multiple bots?
Communicate, yeah.
So one thing I didn't show in the demo
is I set up evals and traces for every run,
especially for the reply bot.
So this is pretty basic.
So all it is is you have a Postgres database,
tell it to create a table for a set of evals,
so things you want to test every single time you make a change.
And then another table for traces.
So every time reply runs, I ask it
how long it took, what files it looked at,
what files it ended up choosing to reply.
So usually it's like a filter down list.
And then from there, you can usually decipher where it went
wrong or things like that.
And that's something you set up in the reply bot configuration,
or is that like a meta bot that's
looking at the whole system?
So I set it up just with a connector with Superbase.
So I didn't show it in the demo,
but I just set up a connector to the build
bot with Superbase, told it it has access to Postgres now,
create traces and evals table, write to those tables
every time I ask you to run an eval, or create a new eval,
or run a trace, or answer a ticket,
even if it's internal, external,
even if it's a dry run ticket.
So even if it's just leaving a note on the plane ticket,
it's still writing a trace.
So then I can have a log of how it's thinking about it
and what it's looking at.
And then once you have that, you can also
have the self-improvement bot look at those
and try to improve the system.
I think that's a big unlock.
Awesome, thank you.
Yeah, and I was thinking about customer support
with phone calls.
I'm curious if you've seen someone
has set up Grokbot with a phone.
I'm curious if you've seen any interesting cases of that
yet, or if you've played with it at all.
I haven't done it too much.
I know Matt on the stream has set it up.
He has a good video on Twitter of giving it,
giving his Grokbot a phone number,
and I think trying to make a reservation with that.
I think that's something that's definitely
will be the case and want to explore.
So if you do it, let me know for sure.
I'll play around with it for sure, cool.
How do you guys think about implementing this
for non-technical folks in the enterprise?
I'm kind of concerned if a non-technical user
is writing stuff to Postgres or without guardrails on.
So the, sorry, I might have misheard the first part of it.
You're asking about non-technical users
and how they would plug into this,
and if there's any concerns.
Well, I guess because it's relatively easy
to spin up a bot to do whatever you need.
How do you put the guardrails so that they don't
mess up the production databases or anything like that?
Because it's relatively easy to be like,
oh, refund all the customers that are,
that should be refunded, but then they don't know
the technicalities of some of the backend stuff.
Yeah, that's a great question.
I know there's a lot of effort into making this
more multiplayer shortly.
Right now, I'd say whenever you first set it up
to set the guard, whoever's first setting it up
maybe can be slightly more technical,
or not even more technical, but just aware
of sort of like system architectures of like,
okay, if someone is gonna run this crockbot,
I'm going to give them a template,
and someone non-technical, I'll share a template
with them that says, oh, you can't
update the knowledge base by yourself.
One thing that I've tried that I like a lot is
using, I use Notion as the knowledge base
sort of just as like an easier example,
but you can use GitHub or Origin,
and that's really powerful because the primitives
of GitHub are like, you get PRs,
you get code owners, you get branches, all that stuff.
So instead of this knowledge base
where there's only sort of one,
you could give someone a template
on their self-improvement bot.
For them, you could say, oh, you have to create a PR,
it has to get reviewed by bug bot,
it has to ping me, I have to approve it,
and I can run the building blocks of like,
evals and traces, I can tell it to run the evals
against a specific PR branch instead of just main,
so I can have the output of that,
have some confidence that it's going to behave
how I want it to behave, and then make sure
it gets approved by the code owner
or the person that's most in charge or most technical,
and you'll have confidence then of,
they can still make updates, they can still be helpful,
but they're not sort of, you're not taking on
a ton of additional risk.
Awesome, thank you.
Yeah.
One question from Max, is it more token-efficient
to queue and bulk ask requests?
Sorry, what was that?
Is it more token-efficient to queue and bulk ask requests,
just bulking together?
Yeah, so it can be.
So instead of, I guess if you saw how I was talking to it,
I would just like tell it to reply to Alex,
that is pretty unclear, so I could have been more clear
by giving it a set of ticket IDs.
Whenever I tell it like that, it has to go look,
go find, maybe read, call the plain MCP,
get all of the open tickets, look through,
do a string search on Alex, try to find that.
That is a lot less token-efficient than giving it
more hard details that can look up easier.
I guess one last question for Max.
As Roshan, Matt, and Lauren have been creating
their company online, do you have any recommendations
on what to set up first for a customer support team
using RockBot?
Yeah, that's a great question.
I know maybe their sort of business has changed
a little bit, but I'd say usually there's about,
there's usually like an 80-20 of 20% of use cases
that create 80% of the ticket volume.
I would try to identify those and have something in place
and make sure those are in the knowledge base first
and have RockBot have really good knowledge
and SOPs there and run evals and test
and make sure everything it can handle, it is,
and then yeah, put RockBot in front of it
and try to answer, cool, amazing.
I think I am out of time and am going to send it back
to the studio.
Can you mic packets on?
Yeah, I can actually share my screen.
Awesome, welcome back everyone.
Hope everyone enjoyed that last talk.
We're winding up our day pretty soon here
and I think it's been a pretty fun one.
We got a bunch of stuff done.
We have an app running and we're really excited
about some of the progress we've made today.
We thought we'd wrap up just showing you
some of the things that we were working on
in the background during that last segment.
A few things that we kicked off before we got started,
if you want to bring my screen up here on the menu.
We kicked off a few bots that were working
on a number of tasks.
Again, for those who are just joining,
we're building a gaming company and a gaming business
as part of our 72 hour live stream here
where we ship a product by Thursday.
And what's been really fun about this is actually,
we're starting to get a little more creative with it.
And so one of the things I did before we went off
onto the last segment was spin up a bot here
that's our audio engineer who's been working
on a bunch of cool audio.
And unfortunately, can we get a mic for RockBot?
I think that'd be really helpful
so we can kind of go through some of these.
Oh, love it.
Okay, I turn this up as loud as I can.
Thank you so much.
So our bot here has been dumping some audio
into a Notion Talk.
We thought it'd be fun to go through these live
and see what we came up with.
So we have some tones that we didn't like,
but let's take a look at some of these lobby songs
for our game.
A little quiet.
That sounds very calm.
It does sound very calm.
Very soothing.
But this is kind of wild.
The bot just kind of came up with these.
And if you haven't seen it before,
this is using Strudel, which is really cool.
So I just told the bot to learn how to make Strudel apps.
And you can just go in here and hit play
and just kind of make some pretty cool music.
Maybe not the exact vibe for our game
since I think we want something a little less
chiptuney maybe or a little less pixel art.
So what I also did was ask my bot here
to give me some prompts for Suno
and just generated some tracks on Suno.
So let's see how some of these sound.
All right, that's a little too sad.
It's a kind of somber, yeah.
Let's see what else we got.
I don't like it.
That feels more awkward.
It's also a little like whimsical.
Very whimsical, yes.
I feel like I'm a wizard about to go on a quest.
Okay, those are pretty similar.
All right, we're not a rom com.
And then right before we came on stream,
I tried to generate a few more.
So I haven't actually heard these before.
Let's see if they work.
Whoa, damn, that's some good battle music.
I don't like that.
Okay, a few more.
Oh, this is good for the draft room
while we're kind of waiting and you're building your team.
Draft room energy.
Okay, I kind of like these.
I feel like we got something here
that we might be able to play with.
Yeah, thank you very much.
Grokbot microphone.
Thank you, production.
Awesome, yeah.
So yeah, I feel like we have
some pretty good art direction happening, right?
We have some UI that we've built.
But maybe to kind of share where we're ending up,
Lauren, you wanna show how the app is looking?
Please switch to Lauren's screen on the screen.
Switch my screen.
A lot of things don't work yet,
but we've hooked up the backend.
So I've logged into my real X account
and there's a leaderboard with nobody in it yet.
I can start a new match.
I don't have any bots yet.
And I just realized there's a bug.
So I can't actually add any bots yet.
But when this works,
I will be able to import any bot with a link.
I'll probably have to think a little bit about how to like,
I feel like this UI is not very user friendly,
but will iterate.
But yeah, for now you will just like,
paste a Dr. Egg bot link in here, you'll create it.
Then it shows up and you can actually start playing a game.
But right now, yeah.
This is really cool.
While you're doing that,
I just logged in as well on my end
and I can log into the X.
Oh, okay.
So we have logging into the X working.
Oh, did you log in already?
I just did.
So we have a atRochen underscore X.
I see.
Well, yeah, I think I need to fix the leaderboard.
Okay.
I would expect the two of us to show up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that's the bug I need to fix.
Gold, yeah.
Yeah, we're both gold at 1,000.
But hey, we both have accounts.
That's pretty cool.
We didn't have accounts a long ago.
And very soon, maybe tomorrow we'll come back with,
I think we're gonna go and get this deployed.
Maybe think of an actual good name for this game
and start playing tomorrow with chat.
Yeah.
You're excited to tune in tomorrow.
We're gonna get everyone in on this game.
We gotta make it go viral.
We have one day to grow our business.
Yeah, we're gonna iterate.
We're gonna make it really, really fun.
And we'll get feedback.
We'll have a little factory going.
Yeah.
And we'll try to make this game real.
Yeah, PRs are being merged.
Like our bots, we had some bots earlier
that are kind of listening for all the PRs.
And it's a constant stream.
I don't know, Lauren, if you wanna show us
what you're looking at.
Well, I mean, my bots are just chugging on.
I have so many bots now.
Like since we last talked, I have,
well, we have WISC, our game designer.
We have Crumb, a new bot that I just made
who is our play tester, who is actually just going in
to the application and just like clicking around
and making sure it works.
So my idea here is that I wanna have a play tester bot
that's just gonna keep playing the game,
checking for bugs, but I haven't taught it
how to like, you know, give feedback on the game itself.
That would be really interesting to set up.
And then I also obviously have,
oh, another thing I kicked off, which I recommend doing
since we're kind of like close to the end
of the stream very soon,
is I often like talk to Dr. Eggbot,
you know, as I create new bots,
just think about like, here's what I told it.
You know, zoom out from a high level,
consider my goals, review all our bots.
Like where are our bottlenecks?
How can we speed up and tighten my workflow?
And then Dr. Eggbot will actually look
at all the transcripts, the chats of all the bots
that you've created and analyze it
and try to figure out like,
where can you improve your workflow?
So it's got a few things like bottlenecks,
you know, the cereal factory, human merge,
yeah, that's a bottleneck, right?
It merged, so it waits on me.
Lauren is the interrupt bus.
So, you know, I'm still kind of like playing a lot of,
I'm still very in the loop right now,
which I sort of want at least
for the while we're prototyping.
But as we start to actually, you know, get feedback
and I'm going to try and make this more autopilot.
But yeah.
The autopilot part is super cool
because then it's just like, you know,
we get to just basically be directors of features, right?
We can say we want to do X
and then like the whole engine behind this
will just like go and build features for us,
make sure it's play tested, do our QA,
make sure there's no regressions.
I'm really excited when we get to that.
I'm hoping like tomorrow we can just rip
a bunch of features in.
I think this will be really cool.
So yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Matt, any updates on your end?
If anyone wants to?
Yeah, so we've been working on the ads side,
just cranked along there.
And then I also was just testing out the app.
So going to have the ads marketplace up,
hopefully tomorrow I think we're going to crank there.
This is my writing bot template that is currently open,
but we pop on over to I think the ads MVP.
Haven't tested this out just yet.
We're going to need to take a look
at what we're doing in the database
and probably like run through some of this.
I also haven't refactored like basically
rebased onto all the changes that Lauren made.
So a little bit behind here,
but that'll be a sprint for tomorrow.
Nice.
Cool.
I feel like we had a pretty good day, right?
I think we ended up making a lot of progress.
We went from no app to an app,
and not just an app,
but like an app with an engine and a bunch of bots
that have basically done all the workforce today.
We got to spend some time looking at Cursor,
which I think was great,
getting to use some agents
and show off things like multitask mode and design mode.
We got to make some music.
It's pretty fun.
We talked to a bunch of fun guests.
So yeah, overall, I think it's been a really great day
and pretty excited to come back tomorrow.
I have a bug.
Oh.
I'm fixing that, yeah.
No, you're already on it.
I want to say this.
Hey, Jonathan.
Yeah, very soon.
Like tonight, I think we'll have like a few games.
Okay, sick.
Maybe we can see how fun it is.
Nice.
You know, kind of get some cool ideas tomorrow.
Love it.
Before we wrap,
wanted to switch back to my screen to remind you all
that you can win some free GrokBot.
So if you want to build what we've been building,
build the way we've been building,
install PStack, install Dr. Eggbot,
become acquainted with all these pots
that we've created today.
You can follow these steps to get a free month of GrokBot,
which is $200 in value.
So a free month of GrokBot at a really great tier as well.
You just need to duplicate
and create a bot with Dr. Eggbot
and use this QR code to do so.
You will get a free month of GrokBot.
This is only available to our first 1,000 users
and claim the offer exclusively
for folks who are watching on stream.
So if you want some free GrokBot, get in there.
Definitely get yourself set up.
We'll be back tomorrow to share even more
of how we continue to build this app.
And I'm excited to finish strong.
Sounds good.
Thanks y'all for watching.
Thanks Chat.
See you tomorrow.